Iron Age Castle wa wa hill fort size built time area form county Berkshire Dorset Wiltshire	0
Iron Age Castle wa become hill fort BritainSharples pp	0
archaeologist Niall Sharples definition fact	0
area wa bank ditch bank ditch wa shallow	0
hill fort expansion wa unique wa series developed hill fort	0
hill fort hill fort Iron Age use wa case Dorset	0
developed hill fort Dorset	0
abandonment hill fort area developed hill fort built indicates developed hill fort important.Sharples pp	0
developed hill fort Berkshire Dorset Wiltshire access resource water.Cunliffe pp	0
emergence developed hill fort ha Iron Age society complex.Cunliffe pp	0
emergence dominant hill fort area indicates inhabitant hill fort warfare	0
dearth evidence destruction increase artefact craft industry suggest reason change wa	0
Hill fort become centre trade.Sharples pp	0
possibility multiple ring ditch developed hill fort term multivallate defensive ditch rampart Castle defence statement power authority.Cunliffe p.	0
hill fort Danebury % site ha excavated.Payne Corney Cunliffe p.	0
developed hill fort status predecessor Cunliffe state Castle monumental defence indicate wa status developed hill forts.Cunliffe p.	0
Castle westward ditch wa Hog Hill	0
peak hill hill fort dry valley	0
shaft dug valley wa water source.Sharples p.	0
ditch enclosure wa work defence elaborate	0
rampart wa rampart ditch	0
south fort rampart ditch steepness slope hill rampart extend way round rampart built side	0
time entrance wa addition earthwork approach site.Sharples pp	0
four-post structure hill fort found Castle	0
purpose site square archaeologist result ha structure granaries.Sharples pp	0
presence suggests fort wa control area food supply.Sharples p.	0
evidence ha house Castle site reconstruction 5th century BC site ha quarry provide material rampart evidence	0
house built rampart defence complete.Sharples p.	0
Castle wa Iron Age inhabitant roundhouse	0
house row size reorganisation indicates power elite Iron Age society.Sharples pp	0
Bronze object pin jewellery rivet found site Iron Age	0
wa source tin copper ore demonstrates distance trade southwest	0
bronze wa Castle evidence reworked.Sharples pp	0
quality iron ore found area hill fort doe centre iron production period hill fort Berkshire Dorset Wiltshire exhibit trace iron production.Sharples p.	0
Iron Age pottery found Castle wa ndash ndash source afield Iron Age % pottery area Poole Harbour away.Sharples p.	0
long-range trade ha evidence relationship group people area emergence tribal identities.Sharples pp	0
Sharples state developed hill fort Castle town agriculture storage Sharples p.	0
Cunliffe fellow-archaeologists Mark Corney Andrew Payne describe developed hill fort town-like settlement form proto-urbanism.Payne Corney Cunliffe pp	0