Montgomery official biographer foundation Operation Cobra wa laid June.Williams p. Montgomery plan time Army Saint-L么 Coutances southward thrust Caumont towards Vire Mortain Saint-L么 towards Villedieu Avranches	9
pressure wa kept Cotentin Peninsula towards Haye-du-Puits Valognes capture Cherbourg wa immediate priority	9
Cherbourg seizure Collins VII Corps Montgomery timetable wa thrust Caumont wa adopted.Esposito p.78-80 conclusion Operation Charnwood cancellation Army towards Saint-L么 Wilmot p. p. Montgomery met Dempsey discus Army move.Trew p. meeting progress flank wa	9
plan breakout attempt Operation Cobra Army July.Blumenson p. p.32D'Este p.338Weigley p.136Pogue p.197Williams p. idea Montgomery p. directive meeting strategy day draw enemy attention Army sector Dempsey wa strength armour ease way Brad	9
accomplish Operation Goodwood wa Trew p. Eisenhower operation support air force bomber	9
briefed subordinate commander Cobra plan phase	9
effort control Collins VII Corps	9
phase breakthrough attack Eddy Hobbs infantry division punch hole zone hold flank penetration Huebner Infantry division depth position resistance	9
phase exploitation force ndash division pas opening defense west.Hastings p. phase position become phase permit advance southwest end bocage cut seize Brittany peninsula.Esposito pp	9
ndash Army intelligence counterattack occur day Cobra launch attack date consist operation	9
Cobra wa attack front 'broad front air support.Hastings pp	9
ndash Fighter-bombers concentrate defense belt south Saint-L么 ndash Periers road Spaatz bomber bomb depth line resistance.Williams p. wa destruction shock value intense bombardment weaken defense addition divisional artillery Corps-level unit provide support medium light artillery battalion	9
thousand tube divisional corp artillery p. artillery round operation VII Corps VIII Corps.Griess p. p. attempt overcome mobility constraint bocage operation side Rhino modification M4 Sherman M5A1 Stuart tank M10 tank destroyer fitting hedge-breaching 'tusks path Norman hedgerows.Hastings p. tank road US armor maneuver practice device believed.Zaloga p.3 eve Cobra sixty percent Army tank equipped.Weigley p.149 preserve security forbade use Cobra wa	9
p.207 M4 medium tank M5A1 light tank M10 tank destroyer available.Zaloga p.30	9