Somerset ha km mi road	2
route include M5 motorway A303 A37 A38 A39 access county area narrow lane	2
Rail service Main Line Yeovil Taunton Line Heart Wessex Line Weymouth Plymouth Line	2
Somerset Coal wa built century cost transportation coal ''heavy produce	2
junction Cam valley terminal basin Paulton use tramway	2
km mi branch Midford wa built tramway wa laid path	2
tramway wa Somerset Dorset Railway S DJR Athill Robin	2
''The Somerset Dorset Railway	2
century saw improvement Somerset road introduction turnpike building canal railway	2
Nineteenth-century canal Bridgwater Taunton Westport Glastonbury Chard	2
Dorset Somerset wa wa	2
usefulness canal wa recreation	2
century saw construction railway Somerset	2
county wa pre-1923 railway company Great Railway GWR	2
''A history railway Great Volume Country	2
branch Midland Railway MR Bath Park Martin	2
Shepperton Ian Allan ISBN 0-7110-2063-9. Somerset Dorset Railway Awdry Christopher	2
ISBN 0-7110-0024-7. Railway L SWR .Williams	2
''The Railway v. year v. Growth consolidation	2
Newton ISBN 0-7153-4188-X ISBN 0-7153-5940-1 line GWR use today branch line	2
line Somerset Dorset Railway Atthill Robin Nock O.	2
''The Somerset Dorset Railway	2
ISBN 0-7153-4164-2. ha branch Midland Railway Bath Park St Philips L SWR part present Main Line	2
branch line East Somerset Railways ownership heritage line	2
fifth railway wa light railway Clevedon Portishead Railway	2
Somerset Mineral Railway iron ore Brendon Hills Watchet	2
1960s pier Clevedon Portishead Minehead paddle steamer P Campbell ran service Cardiff Ilfracombe Island	2
pier wa reason Somerset Dorset Railway wa provide link Channel Channel	2
pier shortest pier UK.Handley Chris	2
''Maritime Activities Somerset Dorset Railway	2
1970s Royal Portbury Dock wa provide capacity Port	2
long-distance holiday traffic county Cornwall Somerset marker journey	2
North ndash south traffic move county M5 Motorway.Charlesworth	2
Traffic east travel A303 road M4 Motorway east ndash west M5 limit county	2