Wilhelm II public symbolise horror war wa cousin	7
Queen mother wa daughter Teck descendant Royal	7
paternal grandfather wa Prince Saxe-Coburg Gotha child bore title Prince Princess Saxe-Coburg Gotha Duchess Saxony	7
brother-in-law cousin subject bore title Duchess Teck Prince Princess Prince Princess Hesse Rhine Prince Princess Schleswig-Holstein-Sonderburg-Augustenburg	7
G. Wells alien court alien	7
V Order-in-Council name Royal German-sounding Saxe-Coburg Gotha Windsor appease nationalist	7
Windsor surname descendant Queen Victoria living woman family descendant	7
relative subject use title style British-sounding surname	7
overnight cousin Prince Mountbatten Marquess Milford brother-in-law Teck Cambridge Marquess Cambridge	7
Others Princess Marie Louise Schleswig-Holstein Princess Helena Victoria Schleswig-Holstein territorial designation	7
Letters Patent style Royal Highness titular dignity Prince Princess Great Ireland child Sovereign child son Sovereign eldest living son eldest living son Prince Wales.Nicolson p. Letters Patent title Royal Highness Highness Serene Highness titular dignity Prince Princess cease title	7
Relatives Royal fought side Prince Ernst Hanover Cumberland Teviotdale male-line grandson III Prince Eduard Albany Saxe-Coburg Gotha male-line grandson Queen Victoria cut peerage Order-in-Council provision Titles Deprivation	7
Garter flag St Chapel Windsor Castle pressure mother Queen	7
Tsar Nicholas II Russia cousin mother sister wa Revolution Government asylum Tsar family condition people fear revolution Isles think presence Romanovs seem inappropriate circumstances.Sinclair p. Nicolson p. claim Lord Mountbatten Burma Lloyd wa rescue Romanovs record secretary Lord Stamfordham suggest V rescue advice Lloyd p. planning rescue wa MI1 branch secret service Bolshevik position wider difficulty conduct war plan wa put operation.Sinclair p. Tsar immediate family Russia Bolshevik	7
year Nicholas mother aunt Maria Feodorovna Dagmar Denmark member family Crimea ship	7
month end war son lifetime ill-health	7
wa death Queen anxiety u years…The break family circle bear people kind ha u	7