action film ''Blade Runner ha level film noir convention femme fatale protagonist-narration version dark shadowy cinematography outlook hero include humanity	5
literate science fiction film philosophy religion implication human mastery engineering context drama hubris draw image Noah flood source ''Frankenstein	5
theme mortality chess game Tyrell Immortal game Scott ha wa coincidental.Sammon p. ''Blade Runner delf implication technology environment society past literature symbolism theme film noir	5
tension past present future future Blade Runner high-tech place decayed	5
Scott reporter Lynn ''The Observer described film dark feel	5
Director Scott idea pain wake brother skin cancer death	5
wa ill visit wa	5
level paranoia exists manifestation power omnipresent police light power replicants	5
Control environment scale hand hand absence life animal extinct	5
backdrop clarifies people off-world colony	5
theme Blade Runner example cyberpunk concept film	5
film use eye variety theme image call question reality ability perceive it.Bukatman pp	5
element provide uncertainty ''Blade Runner theme humanity	5
order discover replicants empathy test number question treatment animal indicator someone humanity	5
replicants human character lack empathy replicants show compassion concern time mass humanity street cold	5
film put doubt Deckard human force audience reevaluate mean human.Kerman Judith	5
Blade Runner Issues Scott Blade Runner Android Dream Sheep	5
ISBN 0-87972-510-9 question Deckard human replicant ha controversy film release.Bukatman pp	5
Deeley Harrison Deckard human Fancher ambiguity.Sammon p. Scott ha vision Deckard replicant	5
''New Times film ’ s theme dehumanization ha	5
ha matter speculation debate certainty Deckard replicant-hunting cop replicant	5
Scott “ ’ s replicant	5
wa replicant. ” Deckard dream sequence Director Cut Gaff parting-gift origami Deckard replicant Gaff access Deckard memory	5
interpretation Deckard replicant challenged others imagery show character human replicant share dream recognise affinity absence decisive answer film theme.Bukatman p. inherent ambiguity uncertainty film richness ha viewer perspective	5