version wa met controversy UK film critic	5
Dilys Powell ''The Times “ …17th century burning Vincent Price ’ s prize torture-overseer	5
nauseating. ” ''The felt film wa “ sadism. ” Hinxman ''The Telegraph “ extravaganza. ” critic felt film wa worth accolade	5
Taylor ''Times Review film “ …is horror film ha pretension anything win Reeves reputation subject…Mr	5
ha achievement horror film film period. ” ''Films “ ''Witchfinder ha explicit ‘ message ’ doe something spring despair	5
film…Matthew Hopkins Price ’ s performance	5
''Witchfinder horror film one… ” Film Bulletin ha film outcry nastiness violence tone film torture death plenty stress film vivid sense time joint stray group soldier skirmish attacker wood hang wayside battle commence bloody crime name religion Matthew Hopkins	5
''Witchfinder Review Film Bulletin Vol	5
p. Playwright wa ''Witchfinder	5
column ''The Listener day film release felt horror film laugh Reeves humorless movie film	5
wa experience mean feel dirty	5
Reeves wa response reaction wa proof decision include extreme violence wa correct approach material	5
letter ''The Listener Reeves thing form entertainment conditioning audience accept enjoy violence Violence sordid	5
Insofar show screen people shock recognition fact	5
wish wash `dirty film	5
proof fact ''Witchfinder work	5
AIP head Arkoff Nicholson portion budget tax write-off film quality	5
Nicholson told Heyward gotten	5
Everybody think production Poe series past year	5
Arkoff Reeves brought element Vincent time	5
Vincent wa savage picture	5
film wa subject censorship wa AIP mix drive-in grindhouses	5
attempt link film Roger Corman ’ s Edgar Allan Poe series film wa ''The Conqueror Worm	5
Brief prologue epilogue narration Price Poe ’ s poem justify title	5
Danny ''Cult Movies book film critic release “ trade reviewer saw entry AIP ’ s Edgar Allan Poe series…and dismal notice future scarce	5
ISBN 0-517-20185-2 ''Hollywood Citizen News wa film “ disgrace producer scripters sad commentary art filmmaking…a film bestial brutality sadism wonder custom country. ” trade journal ''Box Office “ Fans horror film glad Vincent Price portrait gallery stomach-churning gore imaginable… ” ''Variety Dwyer evidence talent principal Reeves mediocre script direction	5
lack support movie wa success stateside AIP ''Cinefantastique magazine	5
biography Reeves claim film U.S	5
film AIP minor fracas	5
group sailor movie base theater title week saw movie theater release title	5
money manager tipped trashcans threw popcorn screen tore theatre	5
manager mind paid sailor price ticket sent bill AIP damage	5
release spring critic film UK Pirie film book ''A Heritage Horror film ''Time “ …one mature statement history cinema…The performance excellent film ha countryside way. ” Danny “ ''The Conqueror Worm film way Reeves ’ s achievement wa maintain momentum film end woman time Sara screaming. ” Derek Malcolm ''Witchfinder part series ''The Century Films list movie Century	5
Malcolm film ''Witchfinder transcends genre sheer panache	5
Hoberman ''Village Voice film “ …has cult item part director Reeves drug overdose film release bleak story evil Reeves shot location movie ha robust quality Price overripe performance…it remains evocation Puritanism mass deception. ” book ''Madness Virgil ’ s ‘ Aeneid ’ Fratantuono described ''Witchfinder theme Virgil epic ''Aeneid image nature fury madness power corrupt hero	5
Fratantuono ha film Reeves “ ha point Virgil ’ s epic madness conclusion. ” Fratantuono	5
''Madness Virgil Aeneid Books	5