met time Council Prince Eugene – Count Wratislaw – village Mundelsheim half-way Danube Rhine.Falkner ''Blenheim p. Field Commander Prince Großheppach.Falkner ''Blenheim p.	9
Eugene doubt reliability wa friend Elector Bavaria	9
conference wa Eugene return men Lines Stollhofen Rhine eye Villeroi Tallard prevent aid army Danube	9
force combine men march Danube seek Elector Marsin reinforced.Chandler Commander p. destination Tallard Villeroi met Landau Alsace construct action plan Bavaria rigidity command system wa variation plan Versailles.Chandler Commander p. Count Mérode-Westerloo commander troop Tallard army – thing delayed march Alsace	9
Approval Tallard wa reinforce Marsin Elector Danube Black battalion squadron Villeroi wa pin Allies Lines Stollhofen Allies move force Danube wa join Marshal Tallard de Coignies men protect Alsace	9
Tallard ’ s army Rhine march	9
distance mile km weeks.Lynn p.	9
Lynn state march-rate wa period mile km day	9
stand wa distance fine condition troop	9
Thanks effect wear tear kept minimum	9
Captain Parker described march discipline – country Allies commissar u manner man horse … soldier nothing pitch tent boil kettle lie rest	9
march loss spy sick left	9
response manoeuvre Elector Marsin disadvantage men force camp Dillingen north bank Danube	9
attack Dillingen lack siege gun – wa bring Countries supply assurance contrary.Falkner ''Blenheim p. Allies base provision river	9
key fortress Schellenberg height town Donauwörth	9
Count Jean d'Arco sent men camp hold town grassy hill bloody battle casualty side Schellenberg succumbed Donauwörth surrender afterwards	9
Elector position Dillingen wa position fortification Augsburg.Falkner ''Blenheim p. Tallard march dilemma Eugene	9
Allies Danube Eugene try cut Tallard hasten reinforce	9
''Prince Eugen Savoy p. withdrew Rhine Danube Villeroi move south link Elector Marsin	9
Eugene troop Lines Stollhofen rest army forestall Tallard	9
number Eugene disrupt Tallard march Marshal progress wa	9
Tallard force troop march – cavalry horse glanders mountain pass wagon provision	9
peasant Tallard problem Mérode-Westerloo bemoan – peasantry thousand men army wa Black	9
Tallard besieging town Villingen day enterprise approach Eugene	9
Elector Augsburg wa Tallard wa way Black	9
news Elector policy inaction wait reinforcements.Chandler Commander p. reticence fight undertake policy spoliation Bavaria burning building crop land south Danube	9
aim put pressure Elector fight term Tallard reinforcement ruin Bavaria base army attack pursue Franconia stage withdraw northwards.Falkner ''Blenheim p. destruction siege Rain cause Prince Eugene lament … Donauwörth action admire performance conclude ha home objective	9
Spencer ''Blenheim p. place force army	9