alt=Very angle show space church nave dome arch transept side chancel image show way gold mosaic gleam contrast dark shadow	0
alt=Wide angle view show pew chancel Jane Stanford ha described aversion blank space Gregg p. church dimly lit cavern mosaic surface vibrant stained-glass window	0
church feature foliate ornament wall mosaic Byzantine manner	0
stained-glass window Lamb York.Hall p. chandelier Art Nouveau tradition gold decorative pattern cast pot metal	0
church bronze door angel motif church	0
door narthex vestibule mosaic wall stone detail	0
variety style motif hand craftsman	0
mosaic adorns floor depicts Lamb symbol gospel writer Matthew angel Mark lion Luke ox eagle	0
symbol area church.Gregg p. cross adorns wooden door lead nave Latin epigraph side doors.Gregg p. narthex organ gallery	0
nave ha aisle side clerestory window	0
timber ceiling wa Trinity Church hammer beam chancel	0
floor church slope downward towards	0
space arch stout column capital	0
transept apse balcony concave balustrade	0
base dome decorative gilt band vine	0
Jane Stanford dome decoration mosaic tile variety symbol church builder thought dome decoration	0
spandrel pendentives mosaic angel tip tip cloud	0
angel earthquake angel downward wa earthquake section left .Gregg p. chancel Hall contains work kind seldom	0
floor chancel curve outward body church marble step	0
sanctuary marble altar rail altar Carrara marble L.M	0
altar support simple brass cross color mosaic	0
Gregg p. cross wa van Erp wa memory Jane Stanford	0
altar mosaic reproduction Roselli Supper	0
wall chancel twelve niche mosaic tile	0
hold candle held statue twelve apostle destroyed	0
legend cherub stone niche pillar capital illustration child living campus time church construction	0
west side chancel stand brass lectern form reading angel Jane Stanford brought husband anniversary birth p. glass window apse depict nativity crucifixion ascension Christ	0
mosaic show angel left cross right crown	0
longer section chancel wall side window mosaic choir angel	0
tier mosaic representation prophet king	0
mosaic abound transept clerestory choir loft end church	0
series mosaic transept depict Old Testament figure east side saint west side	0
Jane Stanford direction alternate male female	0
arch balcony rail pillar church relief team men year scaffolding.Gregg p. pillar entrance west transept inscription member Stanford family	0
earthquake west transept wa chapel	0
altar chair chapel Bay Area artist Gail Fredell chapel altar Salvatti mosaic church reconstruction earthquake.Gregg pp	0