retirement Hassett tour captaincy wa competition.Cashman pp	8
cricket wa ndash wa season ndash player stake claim	8
century Queensland wa maintain form passing fifty inning	8
Wales won Sheffield Shield leadership.Perry pp	8
selector captaincy option captain XI played Hassett XI testimonial match	8
start season wa captain incumbent vice-captain	8
wa deputy Victoria Ian wa team captaincy	8
wa speculation Queensland board member Wales delegate remainder Johnson.Perry pp	8
ndash Test century year opening Test Brisbane	8
skipper Len won toss sent Perry p. p.	8
lay foundation score inning victory	8
pair rate player struck bowling Tyson wa bowler era.Perry pp	8
century batsman series wa bruise body fend ball risk catch.Robinson pp	8
Test Sydney injury team time Tests.McHarg p.	8
Control surprising move Richie Benaud vice-captain match	8
Benaud batsman ten Test match wa member team	8
Benaud situation wa sought advice veteran player Ray Lindwall Harvey Test years.Cashman pp	8
won toss bat pitch match time-wasting	8
inning lead low-scoring match batting collapse face Tyson pace barrage day.Benaud p. p. pp	8
tailwind Tyson extreme pace slip cordon stood m wicket.Piesse p.	8
performance score disappointment team defeat	8
pas Tests ndash hat-trick loss wa Fifth Test series p.	8
Test century season passing fifty occasion	8
farewell wa ndash tour Indies	8
struck Jamaica tour match recall Test team.Perry pp	8
Test victory Jamaica Test century drawn Test Port Trinidad	8
Test win Fourth Test dysentery	8
Test inning Fifth Test won inning seal series ndash	8
tour colour first-class match	8
Sydney tour wife Valerie breast cancer absence	8
illness return distract cricket.Pollard p. p.	8
wife condition year removal breast age wife condition wa terminal marriage	8
century first-class appearance country Indies record	8
wa century debut appearance ground	8
wa player commentator character goodwill ability	8
childhood mentor wa man worth Tyson cricket genteel equanimity aloof le cordial .McHarg p. p.	8
commentator Arlott wa cricketer time ndash relaxed .McHarg p.	8