Express mission Division Infantry Regiment Battalion Infantry Regiment	9
destroyer Lieutenant Tadayoshi Sano commander Infantry Division staff troop	9
Hyakutake troop help stop attack west Matanikau sent Regiment unit reinforce Oka force	9
Takeo Itō commander Division Infantry command defense Mount Austen.Frank p. p. p. p.	9
time Ito troop 124th Infantry Regiments unit inland line Mount point west	9
force Maj. Takeyosho Inagaki Battalion Infantry northeast slope Mount	9
Colonel Oka part 124th Infantry unit held center line Mount Matanikau Col. Masaichi Suemura Battalions Infantry ground west Matanikau	9
Regiment wa Colonel Sadashichi Doi	9
Doi wa date artillery fire	9
Suemura command Doi death p.	9
Regiment unit place position	9
attempt deliver rest Division equipment Naval	9
troop division island supply ammunition equipment	9
failure attempt recapture Field.Frank p.	9
difficulty troop air naval attack supply chain ship base	9
supply island sustain troop men day malnutrition disease ground air attack	9
army troop campaign number	9
le fit combat duty.Frank p. p.	9
opposition Army leader retaken Allies Headquarters approval Emperor evacuation force island establishment line defense Solomons Georgia	9
evacuation effort force ''Operation ケ号作戦 execute operation p. p. Griffith p.	9
meantime US deliver troop	9
infantry regiment US Army Division 164th	9
addition US Army 147th Infantry Regiment Marine Division Marine Regiment	9
reinforcement artillery construction aviation naval support units.Frank p. Griffith p. p. p. p.	9
Division infantry regiment guard unit	9
164th wa North Dakota	9
147th part Infantry Division	9
US Army Alexander Patch Division Vandegrift commander force Tulagi	9
day 5th Marine Regiment island rest Marine Division end month	9
Patch wa eliminate force	9
Patch told Millard Harmon US Army force troop accomplish mission	9
response Harmon Infantry Division wa process Hawaii area ship	9
unit stage week week	9
addition rest Marine Division unit Marine Regiment time period	9
force men.Miller p. p. p. p. p. Zimmerman p. p. Griffith p.	9
time Marine Division type disease malaria	9
Marine Regiment Marine Division rejoin parent unit Marine Division	9
US Army Infantry Division Regiment Regiment Regiment	9
Marine Division headquarter unit Marine Regiment Marine weapon support unit	9
US Marston commander Marine Division wa time rank Patch	9
Alphonse Carre Marine Division	9
number Marines Tulagi wa	9