Messiaen relationship organ autumn Dupré organ course	6
Dupré Messiaen organ console sat hour Dupré instrument week play Johann Bach ''Fantasia minor standard.Hill Simeone p. Messiaen Église de la Sainte-Trinité organist Quef wa ill	6
Quef post vacant Dupré Tournemire Widor others Messiaen candidacy	6
application Messiaen letter recommendation Widor appointment wa Simeone pp	6
Messiaen organist la Sainte-Trinité sixty year	6
Messiaen violinist fellow composer Claire Delbos	6
marriage compose work play ''Thème et variation violin piano year piece celebrate happiness song cycle ''Poèmes pour Mi Messiaen	6
''Mi wa Messiaen affectionate nickname wife	6
Messiaen marriage tragedy wife memory operation spent rest life mental institutions.Yvonne Loriod Hill p. Messiaen André Jolivet Daniel-Lesur Yves group ''La Jeune Young	6
manifesto frivolity predominant music Jean Cocteau manifesto ''Le coq et l'arlequin favour living music impetus sincerity generosity conscientiousness .from programme opening concert ''La Jeune Griffiths p. Messiaen career public phase music wa time wa public commission concert	6
ondes Martenot response commission piece accompany light- water-shows Seine ''Paris Exposition Messiaen interest ondes Martenot instrument ''Fêtes de belle eaux six.Hill Simeone pp	6
part instrument subsequent composition	6
period Messiaen multi-movement organ work	6
suite ''L'Ascension Ascension organ version movement movement ''Transports de joie d'une âme devant la gloire du Christ qui est la sienne Ecstasies soul glory Christ glory	6
cycle ''La Nativité du Seigneur Nativity Lord ''Les corp glorieux body	6
toccata ''La Nativité ''Dieu parmi u ha become favourite recital piece	6
outbreak World II Messiaen wa army combatant eyesight.Griffiths p. wa Verdun wa Görlitz wa prison camp Stalag VIII-A	6
violinist cellist clarinettist fellow prisoner	6
trio trio ''Quatuor pour la fin du temp Quartet End Time	6
wa camp audience prisoner prison guard composer piano condition	6
introspection reflection camp life bore fruit music masterpiece	6
end time title allusion Apocalypse work subject refers way Messiaen rhythm harmony time way music predecessor contemporaries.See discussion Griffiths Chapter ''A Technique End Time pp	6