factory steel mill meat-packing plant Side saw period immigration 1840s World II	2
immigrant neighborhood adjacent zone	2
Americans State Streets area Black Belt World II spread Side	2
Black Belt meaning term ghetto arose discriminatory estate practice threat violence neighborhood	2
Post-Reconstruction southerner number population quadruple	2
century number Great Migration Americans foot left disfranchisement job opportunity education	2
population % Side Black Belt	2
block State wa block	2
Side problem wa place Americans vibrant community business music food culture	2
condition saw opportunity child	2
time Side descendant immigrant move	2
housing pressure civic unrest city complexity wa succession group	2
resident mean newer housing developed suburb migrant city. change south side	2
Side ha history segregation	2
housing case Side debate case ''Hansberry v. U.	2
challenged restriction Park Subdivision	2
construction Ryan barrier neighborhood neighborhood	2
decade century poorest housing condition States Authority ha high-rise public housing mixed-income lower-density development Plan Transformation	2
CHA public housing project mile State torn	2
Chinatown gate sector redevelopment	2
Neighborhood rehabilitation case gentrification part Park Woodlawn Bridgeport Park	2
Pullman redevelopment example work progress	2
Chinatown Side ha surge growth	2
ha become destination tourist cornerstone city community	2
Loop mid-decade construction suggests Side Caucasians year	2
Side offer outdoor amenity mile public lakefront park beach border side	2
Segregation meant Side left	2
Mid-century restructuring meat steel industry meant job	2
Americans middle-class job left Civil Rights Movement change housing Side concentration family	2
business amenity peak day	2
population resides Village Lawndale area south	2
Hyde Park home Side population synagogue Landmark Isaiah	2
gang prominent Side neighborhood century immigrant territory immigrant migrant	2
1960s gang Lords public image thuggish venture government grant	2
gang gender line include % female composition	2
deep Side ha population % zip code %	2