Griswold anthology ''The Poets Poetry wa comprehensive kind date	4
critic Gaylord Clark wa Griswold book become permanent literature age nation	4
anthology Griswold build reputation 1840s 1850sMeyers edition printing month	4
editor collection exception poet mark anthology act martyrdom service mus .Bayless book wa wa edition Griswold death Henry Stoddard	4
time ''The Poets Poetry ha graveyard poet writer obscurityBayless become historian Pattee resurrection	4
Pattee book collection trash worthlessness .Pattee scene Griswold vindictive	4
historian Perry Griswold wa era deviousness ample documentation prove suppose le invention Dickens .Miller anthology Writers ''Female Poets become dictator approval writer sought power.Quinn impress author voiced opinion Griswold character	4
Ann Stephens truth .Silverman friend knew consummate liar Is Griswold fact	4
friend vindictive men met	4
Author Cornelius Mathews Griswold writer exploit innocent fish avoid Griswold Hook .Miller review Griswold anthology ''Saturday Museum Poe Quinn fate	4
Forgotten ha sink oblivion landmark tell spoken hereafter servant trust	4
Harrison ed. ''The Works Edgar Allan Poe T. Y. Crowell vol XVII	4
Griswold verse Griswold temperament ''A Critics ''But stay Tityrus Griswold lead ''The flock pluck feed on— ''A loud-cackling swarm feather warm ''He perfect — swan rest	4
''Pattee Griswold wa proponent schoolchildren poetry addition poetry	4
anthology ''Readings Poetry Use Schools wa purpose.Bayless knowledge poetry wa claim read poem mdash volumes.Brooks Van Wyck	4
P. Dutton Company ha patriotism phrase person knew contributor ''Graham	4
Pilgrims man woman ha anything subject ha research	4
Oliver Holmes Sr. Griswold literature kind naturalist subject author memory perfect fauna thing feed ink	4
Evert Augustus Duyckinck thought possession mind force monomania .Lewis W. B	4
''The Adam Innocence Tragedy Tradition Nineteenth Century	4
Poet Pendleton Cooke Griswold sincerity .Parks Edd Winfield	4
Athens GA Georgia Press	4
1850s Griswold nationalism trend reading literature	4
absurd notion create literature	4
Publicly Griswold establishment copyright work time editor ''The Brother Jonathan	4
editor advantage state thing declares	4
wa chosen represent publishing industry spring discus need copyright law	4