TF17 wa south Rossel Island	9
time Fletcher sent Crace cruiser destroyer force Task TG block Jomard Passage	9
Fletcher understood Crace operating air cover TF17 carrier locate attack carrier	9
detachment Crace warship anti-aircraft defense Fletcher carrier	9
Fletcher risk wa order invasion force slip Port Moresby wa carriers.Lundstrom ''Pearl Harbor Midway pp	9
Cressman p. Millot pp	9
Henry p. Morison p.	9
time TG17.3 cruiser ''Chicago ''Australia ''Hobart destroyer ''Walke ''Perkins ''Farragut	9
''Farragut wa TF17 screen Millot Morison	9
Takagi carrier force wa north location vicinity Louisiades Fletcher send SBD dive bomber scout search area	9
meantime Takagi east Fletcher Type carrier bomber scout TF17	9
Hara Fletcher ship south Takagi send aircraft search area	9
time Gotō cruiser ''Kinugasa ''Furutaka E7K2 Type floatplane search southeast Louisiades	9
search floatplane Deboyne Type Tulagi Type bomber Rabaul	9
side rest carrier attack aircraft launch enemy wa located.Lundstrom ''Pearl Harbor Midway pp	9
time TF17 Takagi aircraft Lundstrom p.	9
day Inoue ''I -class submarine deploy south intercept ship battle Lundstrom p.	9
carrier dive bomber head towards position carrier	9
Takagi carrier scout ''Shōkaku ship degree Takagi	9
scout carrier cruiser destroyer	9
''Shōkaku scout aircraft sighting.Lundstrom ''Pearl Harbor Midway p. Cressman p. Dull p. Lundstrom p.	9
''Shōkaku aircraft ''Neosho ''Sims	9
carrier Hara Takagi concurrence aircraft	9
aircraft—18 Zero fighter Type dive bomber torpedo aircraft—began ''Shōkaku ''Zuikaku way towards sighting.Lundstrom ''Pearl Harbor Midway pp	9
Hoyt p. Cressman p. Millot pp	9
Shigekazu Shimazaki ''Zuikaku torpedo bomber attack	9
''Furutaka aircraft found Fletcher carrier Inoue headquarters Rabaul report Takagi	9
Takagi Hara report continue strike ship south carrier towards distance ''Furutaka contact.Lundstrom ''Pearl Harbor Midway pp	9
Cressman p. Millot p. Lundstrom pp	9
Cressman report scout SBD Nielsen shot Aichi E13A Deboyne crew plane commander Eiichi Ogata	9
SBD destroyed E13 ''Furutaka Chuichi Matsumoto	9
Takagi Hara report mean carrier force operating groups.Bullard p.	9
SBD Nielsen Gotō force invasion convoy	9
Nielsen error message carrier cruiser TF17.Lundstrom ''Pearl Harbor Midway p. Hoyt p. Cressman p. Dull p. Millot pp	9
Henry p. Morison p.	9
SBD system wa board peg hole transmission ship type	9
Nielsen case board wa Cressman	9
Gotō unit wa Distant Cover Force Marumo wa Cover Force Support	9
Millot Morison state Nielsen Marushige cruiser Gotō	9
Marushige Marumo cruiser force	9
Lundstrom state Nielsen Gotō	9
Fletcher carrier force launch carrier aircraft attack	9
strike aircraft—18 Wildcat fighter SBD dive bomber TBD Devastator torpedo bombers—was way	9
Gotō force ''Shōhō Nielsen thought cruiser destroyer	9
Fletcher report flight States Army B-17s aircraft carrier ten transport warship south Nielsen	9
B-17s saw thing Nielsen ''Shōhō Gotō cruiser Port Moresby Invasion Force	9
B-17 wa carrier force Fletcher strike force towards target.Lundstrom ''Pearl Harbor Midway pp	9
Henry p. Morison pp	9
Lundstrom B-17 wa cruiser Cressman	9
USACMH Vol p. state B-17s	9
TF17 combat air patrol CAP shot Type Tulagi Lundstrom ''Pearl Harbor Midway pp	9
Ten F4Fs SBDs TBDs ''Lexington F4F SBD TBD Cressman Lundstrom	9
''Kinugasa floatplane launch strike force Lundstrom p.	9
B-17s report bombed ''Kamikawa Maru Deboyne minor damage Lundstrom p.	9
''Neosho center left burning sinking completion dive bombing attack	9
Takagi strike force target area ''Neosho ''Sims vain carrier	9
''Shōkaku scout aircraft mistaken identification oiler destroyer aircraft carrier	9
Takagi carrier invasion convoy invasion force extreme danger	9
Takagi aircraft attack ''Neosho ''Sims return carrier	9
torpedo bomber fighter mission towards carrier ordnance dive bomber ships.A ''Shōkaku torpedo plane Reefs ''Pearl Harbor Midway pp	9
Cressman p. Millot pp	9
''Shōkaku scout aircraft target area assist strike force ship sufficient fuel return carrier Reefs photo right	9
crew destroyer Cressman p.	9
airman Tulagi strike attempt capture Cressman p.	9
dive bomber ''Sims rest ''Neosho	9
destroyer wa hit bomb broke half sank crew	9
''Neosho wa hit bomb	9
dive bomber hit anti-aircraft fire crashed oiler	9
power ''Neosho wa left sinking	9
power ''Neosho wa notify Fletcher radio wa attack trouble detail wa coordinate position.ONI p. Lundstrom ''Pearl Harbor Midway pp	9
Cressman p. p. Millot pp	9
source Hoyt Millot Morison state ''Neosho wa horizontal bomber strike	9
fact wa torpedo aircraft target designators oiler strike force Lundstrom p.	9
dive bomber crashed ''Neosho wa Petty Officer Class Shigeo Ishizuka Petty Officer Class Masayoshi rear gunner/observer Werneth p.	9
Sixteen survivor ''Sims aboard ''Neosho rescue day	9
captain ''Sims Willford Hyman wa attack	9
''Neosho crewman Oscar V. Peterson wa Medal Honor effort ship spite fatal injury attack	9
time attack ''Neosho crew officer men	9
crewman officer panicked ship attack	9
men ship rest vanished ONI pp	9
Phillips Hoyt p. Morison pp	9
strike aircraft ''Shōhō distance northeast Island deployed attack	9
carrier wa Zeros Type fighter combat air patrol CAP rest carrier aircraft deck strike carrier	9
Gotō cruiser carrier diamond formation ''Shōhō corners.Lundstrom ''Pearl Harbor Midway pp	9
cruiser ''Shōhō Hoyt pp	9
Millot p. Dull p. Lundstrom pp	9
''Shōhō wa strike torpedo plane Zeros belowdecks attack	9
Zeros attack attack commenced	9
''Senshi Sōshō official history specifies Gotō cruiser order warn carrier aircraft provide anti-aircraft support Lundstrom p.	9
carrier defense doctrine time maneuvering fighter defense avoid air attack anti-aircraft fire warship Lundstrom	9
''Lexington air group Commander Ault hit ''Shōhō bomb torpedo damage	9
air group burning carrier bomb torpedo	9
air attack Gotō withdrew warship north sent destroyer ''Sazanami rescue survivor	9
aircraft attack SBDs ''Lexington	9
''Shōhō aircraft complement wa CAP fighter pilot ditch Deboyne	9
message signal TF17 success mission ''Lexington SBD pilot squadron commander radioed Scratch top	9
Chart bomb torpedo hit ''Shōhō p. Lundstrom ''Pearl Harbor Midway pp	9
IJN Shoho Cressman pp	9
Dull p. Lundstrom pp	9
Hata p. Morison pp	9
Willmott p. States Strategic Survey p.	9
phrase wa ''Chicago Tribune war correspondent Johnston article account	9
''Lexington officer Captain Frederick Sherman officer squadron VS-2 word flattop standard slang aircraft carrier	9
''Shōhō captain Izawa Ishinosuke	9
''Sazanami wa ''Shōhō plane guard destroyer	9
Zeros Type fighter shot attack	9
Type pilot wa Shiro Ishikawa	9
Zero pilot wa Nōtomi commander ''Shōhō fighter group Lundstrom	9