position southeast Rossel Island Hara torpedo bomber search area bearing degree south carrier	9
search Type Tulagi Type bomber Rabaul	9
carrier force southwest wa Gotō cruiser ''Kinugasa ''Furutaka support	9
invasion convoy Gotō towards point east Woodlark Island await outcome carrier battle	9
night warm frontal zone low-hanging cloud hide carrier north east carrier visibility .Lundstrom ''Pearl Harbor Midway pp	9
Dull p. Lundstrom pp	9
carrier search aircraft ''Shōkaku ''Zuikaku	9
floatplane Deboyne area south Louisiades	9
day loss force time aircraft fighter dive bomber torpedo bomber Lundstrom p.	9
foreground ''Lexington prepare launch aircraft sunrise	9
TF17 operating Fitch control southeast Lousiades SBDs conduct search	9
sky carrier visibility.Lundstrom ''Pearl Harbor Midway pp	9
Hoyt p. Cressman p. Woolridge p. Millot pp	9
Dull p. Lundstrom pp	9
Twelve SBDs search area carrier	9
SBDs sector fly close-in anti-submarine patrol duty return TF17	9
time aircraft strength TF17 wa fighter dive bomber torpedo plane Lundstrom p. SBDs close-in anti-submarine patrol fighter ship CAP Lundstrom p.	9
Fletcher destroyer ''Monaghan try ''Neosho	9
''Monaghan day search coordinate tanker message wa locate TF17	9
TF17 ''Monaghan sent message Nimitz MacArthur TF17 maintain radio silence Cressman p. Hoyt p. Lundstrom p.	9
Fitch wa Fletcher wa control carrier Lundstrom p.	9
Parker p. Fletcher wa Fleet Radio Unit onboard intelligence team carrier northeast position	9
''Lexington SBD G. carrier hole cloud TF17	9
minute ''Shōkaku search plane TF17 Hara	9
side launch strike aircraft.Lundstrom ''Pearl Harbor Midway pp	9
Cressman p. Woolridge pp	9
warrant officer wa middle-seat observer plane Petty Officer Class Tsuguo Gotō	9
radioman wa Petty Officer Class Seijirō Werneth p.	9
Radio interception analyst TF17 message Fletcher carrier location wa	9
report carrier south position	9
SBD stayed station carrier help guide strike Morison	9
carrier strike fighter dive bomber torpedo plane Lieutenant Commander Takahashi	9
group fighter dive bomber torpedo plane wa way	9
''Lexington group fighter dive bomber torpedo plane wa	9
carrier warship force head location speed order shorten distance aircraft fly return legs.Lundstrom ''Pearl Harbor Midway pp	9
Cressman p. Millot p. Dull pp	9
odd number fighter part ''Lexington attack VF-2 Wildcats Doc Sellstrom wa launch preparation wa stay	9
TF17 scout aircraft SBDs anti-submarine patrol	9
strike force fighter dive bomber torpedo plane ''Shōkaku fighter dive bomber torpedo plane ''Zuikaku	9
fighter Type dive bomber Type ''kanbaku torpedo plane Type ''kankō	9
Takahashi wa ''Shōkaku ''kanbaku	9
south Takagi carrier range TBD torpedo plane turn attack Lunstrom p.	9
CAP Wildcats shot Type scout aircraft Lundstrom p.	9
dive bomber O. Burch carrier torpedo squadron conduct attack	9
time ''Shōkaku ''Zuikaku ''Zuikaku hidden rain squall low-hanging cloud	9
carrier CAP Zero fighter	9
dive bomber commenced attack ''Shōkaku hit maneuvering carrier bomb forecastle damage carrier flight hangar deck	9
dive bomber CAP Zeros shot attack.Lundstrom ''Pearl Harbor Midway pp	9
Dull p. Lundstrom pp	9
D'Albas p. Hata pp	9
hit wa SBD pilot Powers wa shot CAP Zero dive	9
Tetsuzō Iwamoto wa CAP pilot time	9
Cressman state Iwamoto flew ''Shōkaku Hata p. state wa ''Zuikaku	9
VS-5 squadron SBD crewed Davis Chafee A. wa shot CAP Zero attack	9
attack CAP Zero flown Takeo Miyazawa wa shot Wildcat CAP Zero flown Hisashi Ichinose wa shot Wildcat Elbert Scott McCuskey	9
Lundstrom state Zeros ''Zuikaku	9
Hata state Miyazawa wa member ''Shōkaku fighter group torpedo plane Zero Hata p.	9
CAP future ace Yoshinao Okabe Hata pp	9
Aces Yoshimi Minami Sadamu member ''Shōkaku fighter group time Hata p. Hata doe CAP strike escort	9
dive bomber ''Shōkaku carrier bomb damage	9
dive bomber dove ''Zuikaku bomb	9
rest ''Lexington dive bomber carrier cloud	9
''Lexington TBDs ''Shōkaku torpedo	9
CAP Zeros patrol time shot ''Pearl Harbor Midway pp	9
Dull p. Lundstrom pp	9
''Lexington bomber pilot wa Bass	9
Wildcat pilot VF-2 squadron B	9
Bull Bain Dale W. Peterson Lundstrom	9
CAP claimed shot aircraft Hata p.	9
flight deck crew ''Shōkaku wa conduct aircraft operation	9
captain Takaji permission Takagi Hara withdraw battle Takagi	9
''Shōkaku destroyer northeast.Lundstrom ''Pearl Harbor Midway pp	9
Hoyt p. Cressman p. Millot pp	9
Parshall p. Dull p. Lundstrom p. IJN Shokaku report	9
CAP fighter pilot claimed shot aircraft attack cost Zeros destroyed	9
loss attack SBDs Wildcats ''Lexington	9
aircraft subsequent return carrier	9
destroyer ''Shōkaku retirement ''Ushio ''Yugure	9