government appoint Chief Justice Victoria	9
Blamey wa end service	9
wa duty year Director effort build Army again.Sayers ''Ned p. wa leader Services Contingent coronation Queen Elizabeth II	9
saw soldier Queen Guard Palace part procession	9
wa Order St Palace	9
time wa commander order charity work.Sayers ''Ned pp	9
ndash connection comrade World Wars	9
way coronation Herrings stayed Eichelbergers North	9
friend letter Eichelberger death	9
Herrings guest Dwight Johns wife	9
D.C. reunion MacArthur staff reunion held	9
government backing idea twenty Leif Sverdrup Casey Chase Eddleman LeGrande A. Diller wife visit commemorative function held Melbourne Sydney Brisbane	9
MacArthur Blamey wa commander wa country.Sayers ''Ned pp	9
ndash twenty year Chief Justice wa period change growth administration law	9
period office number judge fourteen growth case	9
reputation fine judge administrator	9
set Chief Justice Law Reform try justice Victoria court wa abreast time committee observance service arrange service opening year	9
Chief Justice stayed Lieutenant Governor birthday position record years.Innes Prue Age Melbourne	9
service Lieutenant Governor wa Commander Commander Order St St Birthday Honours	9
speech occasion Chief Justice Victoria opening Services League Conference retirement Lieutenant Governor protester soldier	9
People throw stone Americans stop think Americans	9
remark rebuke State Opposition Leader Wilkes representative Crown	9
subject controversy Parliament World II death sentence Papuans darkest secret history .Jones ''A Reed pp	9
ndash Papuans offence murder treason	9
claimed convention circumstance wartime	9
Papuans execution planter soldier airman soldier Infantry Battalion	9
ANGAU execution Higaturu 1943.Sayers ''Ned pp	9
ndash wa president Scouts Victoria year wa president Scouts	9
wa chairman trustee Shrine Remembrance trustee death chairman trustee	9
wa fellow College Oxford honorary DCL Oxford honorary bencher Inner Temple honorary LLD Monash 1973.Sayers ''Ned pp	9
wa Church year wa chancellor Melbourne church office held layman	9
Camberwell Victoria nursing home	9
wa state St Melbourne month before.Hilton ''Dr	9
wartime portrait fifty prominent Australians background	9