Harihara nephew protege poet Raghavanka Hampi style 10th-century poet Ranna wa ''shatpadi metre literature epic ''Harishchandra .Sastri p. p. Seshagiri Rao language ha story way	4
tradition inspiration develops ''shatpadi metre.Sahitya Akademi p. Prakash p. narration ha elegiac verse Chandramati death son Lohitashva snake bite.Sahitya Akademi p. Raghavanka wa guru Harihara	4
strict Shaiva principle appease guru ''Siddharama charitra ''Siddharama Purana life eulogy compassionate 12th-century Veerashaiva saint Siddharama Sonnalige ''Somanatha charitra propagandist work describes life saint Somayya Adaiah Lakshmeshwar humiliation Jain girl revenge ''Viresvara charita story blind wrath Shaiva warrior Virabhadra ''Hariharamahatva account life Harisvara Hampi ''Sarabha charitra	4
lost.Sastri p. Jain scholar minister builder temple army commander Janna ''Yashodhara Charite unique set story verse sadomasochism transmigration soul passion awry cautionary human conduct	4
Vadiraja Sanskrit name interpretation imagery style.Sahitya Akademi p. story poet tell infatuation man friend wife	4
friend man abducts wife dy grief	4
Overcome repentance burn pyre woman.Sahitya Akademi p. P. pp	4
ndash story infatuation reach peak Janna writes attraction Amrutamati queen mahout Ashtavakra plea queen kick whip lash	4
story ha interest researchers.Shiva Prakash p. honour work Janna title ''Kavichakravarthi Emperor poet patron Veera Ballala II.Narasimhacharya p. ''Anathanatha Purana account life 14th tirthankar Ananthanatha.Sahitya Akademi p. p. Andayya path wa literature ''Madana Vijaya Triumph cupid ndash pure word ''desya Sanskrit word ''tadbhava Sanskrit word ''tatsamas	4
rebuttal meant prove literature Sanskrit word wa possible.Sahitya Akademi p. poem narrates story moon god Shiva abode Himalayas	4
anger god love Manmata Shiva arrow Shiva	4
work name ''Sobagina Suggi Beauty ''Kavane Gella Poets defender .Sastri p. ha place Jain Andayya	4
possibility wa subtle weapon conflict dominant JainsNarasimhacharya p. popularity wa rise historians.Nagaraj p. Mallikarjuna Jain anthology poem ''Suktisudharnava Gems poet court Vira Someshwara.Rice E.P	4
p. ndash observation scholar undertaking	4
anthology insight taste period hence qualifies history literature performs function guide poet method bridging gap intelligentsia folk poetry.Nagaraj p. guide work nature poem king royalty poem 12th-century vachana canon Veerashaiva folk literature	4
selection poem contribution Harihara Veerashaiva writer	4
suggests compromise author attempt include rebel	4
writer century Bhanduvarma author ''Harivamsabhyudaya ''Jiva sambhodana latter bearing renunciation soul Maghanandycharya author ''Sastrasara Samuccaya-tiku Singh p. Hastimalla worte ''Purvapurana Chandrama author ''Karkala Gomateshvara charite Singh p. Sisumayana form composition ''sangatya	4
poem ''Tripuradahana triple fortress ''Anjanacharita	4
latter work wa Ravisena Sanskrit ''Padma charitra .Sastri p. Somaraja Veerashaiva scholar eulogy Udbhata ruler Gersoppa ''Sringarasara ''Udbhatakavya .Narasimhacharya p. Jain writer Parsva Pandita author ''Paravanathapurana Gunavarma II author story Jain tirthankar Pushpadanta ''Pushpadanta purana Ratta king Saundatti .E.P.Rice pp	4
ndash Polalva Dandanatha commander minister builder Harihareshwara temple Harihar ''Haricharitra	4
wa Veera Ballala II successor Vira Narasimha II	4
Somanatha book ''Somesvarasataka .Sastri p.	4