Vaishnava movement region found momentum arrival philosopher Ramanujacharya ndash	4
persecution Chola wa Shaiva Ramanujacharya sought refuge Tondanur Melkote.Kamath p. event impact Vaishnava literature Hoysala land time	4
Madhvacharya ndash propounder ''Dvaita philosophy impact Vaishnava literature Sanskrit language	4
body ''haridasa sahitya haridasa literature .Shiva Prakash p. Vasudeva Pajaka village Udupi learnt Vedas Upanishads guru Achyutapreksha	4
wa ''sanyasa asceticism name Madhvacharya Anandatirtha .Kamath p. disagreed view guru travel	4
scholar philosopher time won Naraharitirtha minister become Madhvacharya disciple	4
Adi Shankaracharya ndash philosophy monism Ramanujacharya philosophy monism Madhvacharya taught philosophy dualism .Kamath pp	4
Madhvacharya taught devotion Hindu god Vishnu ''Jnanamarga path knowledge path devotion help soul attain elevation ''Athmonathi	4
wa accept devotion Hindu deity well.Shiva Prakash p. work Sanskrit ''Dwadasha devotion god Vishnu found expression ''Gita Bhashya ''Gita Tatparya Nirnaya ''Mahabharata Tatparya Nirnaya ''Bhagavata Tatparya Nirnaya ''Mayavada ''Vishnu Tattwa Nirnaya	4
propagate monastery Udupi Uttaradhi monastery Raghavendra monastery Mantralayam Andhra Pradesh Nanjanagud Mysore .Kamath pp	4
ndash Madhvacharya Vidyatirtha author ''Rudraprshnabhashya absorbed Sayanacharya brother Vidyaranya patron saint founder Vijayanagara empire 14th century.K	4
T. Pandurangi Kamath pp	4
ndash wa Hoysala Ramanatha commentary ''Samaveda Sastri p. Shadgurusishya commentary ''Aitareya ''Aranyaka ''Sarvanukramani	4
family hereditary poet name held title Vidyacharkravarti poet laureate Hoysala court	4
''Gadyakarnamrita description war Hoysala king Vira Narasimha II Pandyas century.Sastri p. grandson title court king Veera Ballala III poem ''Rukminikalyana ''kandas chapter commentary poetics ''Alankarasarvasva ''Kavyaprakasa	4
Devi sister Madhvacharya Trivikrama disciple commentary philosophy	4
Trivikrama ascribed poem story Usha Aniruddha ''Ushaharana	4
Narayana Pandita ''Madhwavijaya ''Manimanjari poem ''Parijataharana	4
Jain writer Ramachandra Maladhari ''Gurupanchasmriti	4