Harihara Harisvara family ''karnikas accountant Hampi wa Veerashaiva writer wa part ''Vachana tradition	4
ha poet poet poet mass	4
poetry course effort wa inspiration generation poet follow.Sahitya Akademi p. Akademi pp	4
ndash p. Padmarasa court poet Narasimha king Harihara patron.Sahitya Akademi p. master metre ''Girijakalyana Marriage mountain born goddess ndash Parvati tradition ''champu style tell story marriage god Shiva Parvati.Sastri pp	4
ndash p. anecdote Harihara wa mortal struck protege Raghavanka landmark work ''Harishchandra c. .Nagara p. Harihara ''ragale metre.Sahitya Akademi pp	4
ndash biographer language biography ''Basavarajadevara ragale detail protagonist belief time.Shiva Prakash p. Akademi pp	4
ndash group poem ''Nambiyanana ragale ''Shivaganada ragale ''Saranacharitamanasa ndash holy lake life devotee saint Nambiyana.Shiva Prakash p. pp	4
ndash P. p. ''sataka metre ''Pampa sataka ''ashtaka metre ''Mudige ashtaka Akademi p. Vaishnava writer brahmin writer Smartha sect repute Rudrabhatta ''Jagannatha Vijaya style transition ancient medieval Prakash p. Chandramouli minister court Veera Ballala II wa patron	4
''champu metre life god	4
god fight Banasura ''Vishnupurana .Sastri p. Nemichandra court poet Veera Ballala II Silhara ''Lilavati Prabandham fiction hence novel bent.Shiva Prakash p. ''champu metre ancient town Banavasi background narrates love story prince princess marry obstacle	4
story c. Sanskrit ''Vasavadatta Subhandu.Rice P. p. work ''Neminathapurana account death hence ''Ardhanemi incomplete Nemi detail life Jain tirthankar Neminatha life god Jain angle.Sahitya Akademi p. p. Palkuriki Somanatha Andhra Pradesh foremost Shaiva Shiva-following poet century	4
Historians time place birth death faith	4
wa adept Sanskrit Telugu language	4
wa devotee founder Veerashaiva movement propagate faith.Sahitya Akademi p. wa born brahmin Shaiva faith scholar Bandaru Tammayya wa born ''Jangama follower Shaiva faith .Sahitya Akademi p. time birth ha centuryNarasimhacharya p. century.Seshayya Sahitya Akademi p. ''Silasampadane ''Sahasragananama ''Pancharatna	4
poem ''ragale metre ''Basava ragale ''Basavadhya ragale ''Sadguru ragale	4
Vaishnava poet debates.Sastri p. personality century Jain writer	4
include Aggala ''Chandraprabhapurana account life eighth Jain tirthankar Chandraprabha Sujanottamsa panegyric Gomateshwara Shravanabelagola Vritta Vilasa ''Sastra sara ''Dharmaparikshe	4
latter wa Vilasa version Sanskrit name Amitagati c.	4
''champu author narrates story princess Benares vice god discussion brahmin	4
author question credibility Hanuman Hindu monkey god Vanaras monkey-like humanoid Hindu epic	4
work information beliefs.Rice p. P. pp	4
Padmarasa Veerashaiva poet Narasimha ''Dikshabodhe ''ragale metre	4
become protagonist work ''Padmarajapurana descendant Padmanaka c. Akademi p. brahmin poet Deva romance piece ''Kusumavali brahmin poet century treatise ''Sringara-ratnakara ''rasa flavor sentiment.Narasimhacharya pp	4
Sumanobana wa ''Katakacharya teacher Narasimha	4
wa priest Devagiri Seuna Yadava capital.Sahitya Akademi pp	4