USAF DoD conceal incident part USAF policy comment storage movement weapon apparent belief incident generate public concern	9
fact DoD incident report statement press interest	9
Details incident DoD official Times newspaper article incident Missteps Bunker response news briefing Press Geoff wa time wa public danger personnel custody weapon time	9
USAF day incident USAF Minot munition squadron commander airman	9
USAF Doug wa Keys lead investigation incident	9
USAF inventory warhead wa checked warhead	9
addition DoD advisory panel Defense Science study mishap part review procedure weapon	9
USAF Keys wa ACC commander Corley decade Keys call career Gilmore Force Investigates Nuke Transfer Spokesman Says Randolph Force release munition transfer investigation result Warrick Missteps Bunker USDoD DoD Press Maj. Gen. Newton USAF Corley command ACC Generals Minot mishap	9
Force Wynne USAF Newton deputy chief staff operation plan requirement investigation report ha erosion adherence weapons-handling standard Minot Force Base Barksdale Force Base number airman location procedure	9
USDoD DoD Press Maj. Gen. Newton	9
Colonel Emig commander 5th Bomb Colonel Cynthia commander 5th Maintenance Minot Colonel Todd commander Barksdale Operations officer 5th Munitions Squadron action command position	9
5th Bomb personnel certification handle weaponry conduct mission	9
airman rank personnel reliability program certifications.Holmes Minot bomb commander Minot Nuke Handlers Inspection Times	9
inspector office USAF command handle weapon conduct immediate Nuclear Surety Inspections LNSIs unit oversight Defense Threat Reduction Force release munition transfer investigation result COs nuke mistake Force Relieves Commanders Nuclear Weapons Incident USDoD DoD Press Maj. Gen. Newton Pincus Colonels Force Commands Randolph Force release munition transfer investigation result	9
ACC commander Corley matter USAF Lieutenant Norman Seip commander Force authority determine charge action personnel incident	9
Seip investigation charge anyone involved.Starr Force officer duty nuke USDoD DoD Press Maj. Gen. Newton Minot Nuke Handlers Inspection Times	9
USAF Welch wa Gates concern USAF official investigation blame midlevel officer lead Defense Science advisory panel study mishap part review procedure policy weapon	9
addition USAF Ribbon Review USAF Peyer member recommendation Force capability perform weapon responsibility .USDoD DoD Press Maj. Gen. Newton nuke deficiency	9
DoD conduct bottom-up review procedures.Pincus Colonels Force Commands USDoD DoD Press Maj. Gen. Newton Force Relieves Commanders Nuclear Weapons Incident COs nuke mistake Generals Minot mishap Nuclear Focus Has Studies	9