release ''Return Jedi name ''Jabba Hutt ha become mass medium repulsive obesity corruption	5
name device mdash simile metaphor mdash illustrate character flaw	5
example ''Under Duvet Keyes reference problem gluttony writes wheel birthday cake feel Jabba Hutt moment	5
Keyes ''Under Duvet Shoes Reviews Blues Builders Babies Families Calamities HarperCollins p. ISBN	5
novel ''Steps Exes Novel Laura Jabba Hutt weight character father girl call Janice parent Jabba Hutt Wookiee	5
Jabba Janice father seem right speak term	5
Laura ''Steps Exes Novel HarperCollins p. ISBN	5
book humor culture ''The Dharma Star Wars writer Matthew attempt show similarity Buddhist aspect ''Star Wars fiction	5
insists person decision Jabba Hutt person proper concept dharma	5
book reinforces idea Jabba name negativity way right livelihood compare trade Jabba Hutt	5
Jabba ha fat stubby finger pot dark side	5
dealt spice trade—an illicit drug Star Wars galaxy	5
transacts business slave trade	5
ha slave fed Rancor creature kept dungeon	5
Jabba deception violence maintain position.Matthew ''The Dharma Star Wars Mass	5
Wisdom Publications p. ISBN	5
literature character name ha become term disparagement	5
someone look Jabba Hutt understood slur impugn person weight and/or appearance.For example Fat Wars Obesity Empire Strikes	5
term medium attack prominent figure	5
instance actress comedian Roseanne W. vitriolic attack weight hand ''The Observer columnist ''Star Wars blob monster Jabba Hutt.W	5
''The Woman Weight Prejudice Carlsbad Gürze Books p. ISBN	5
episode television series ''South Park Starvin Marvin Space Children Fund spokeswoman Struthers portrayed Hutt herself food relief meant Ethiopians	5
Starvin Marvin Space Episode ''South Park DVD	5
reference Guy episode Too Sexy Fat mention husky ancestor Jabba Griffin	5
Movie Connections sense term Jabba Hutt ha represent greed anarchy business world.Koenraad Star Wars Myth Popular Culture Spring p.	5
instance Jordan biographer term disparage Bulls manager Jerry comment Jordan player multi-million dollar contract Jabba Hutt image medium gathering opening camp question prospect Bulls Phil imminent future 'Organizations win championship	5
Players coach part organization	5
''One Shot Story Jordan Comeback Martin Press p. ISBN	5
Jabba Hutt ha become mean caricature politics	5
example opponent legislator Jackie depict politician ''Star Wars character	5
''Los News ha cartoon overweight Jabba Hutt-like figure ''New Times human Jabba Hutt consumes	5
Mallon ''California Dictatorship Xlibris p. ISBN	5
G. Ouchi term describe inefficient bureaucracy public school system layer fat school district Jabba Hutt—the pirate leader ''Star Wars	5
G. Ouchi Schools Work Plan Children Education Need Simon Schuster p. ISBN	5