appearance Jabba Hutt Star Wars Universe literature wa Marvel Comics adaptation ''A Hope	5
''Six Galaxy Jabba Hut	5
''In Mortal Combat Archie Jabba Hutt ''Hut tall humanoid walrus-like face topknot bright uniform	5
sequel ''Star Wars Marvel kept story Jabba Han Solo Chewbacca hideaway use	5
circumstance force Jabba lift bounty Solo Chewbacca return Tatooine adventure Luke Skywalker mdash ha planet order recruit pilot Rebel Alliance	5
course adventure Solo kill space pirate bust operation Jabba	5
Jabba renews reward Solo head Solo kill bounty hunter tell	5
Solo mention incident bounty hunter ran Ord opening scene ''The Empire Strikes	5
Marvel artist Jabba character Mosep Binneed alien briefly Mos Eisley cantina scene ''A Hope .Roy ''Marvel Star Wars Six Galaxy Marvel .Archie ''Marvel Star Wars Jabba Hut	5
Marvel .Archie ''Marvel Star Wars Mortal Combat Marvel .Jabba Hutt Scenes	5
mass market paperback novelization Lucas ''Star Wars script describes Jabba mobile tub muscle suet topped shaggy skull detail character appearance species.George Lucas ''Star Wars Adventures Luke Skywalker paperback Del p. ISBN 0-345-26079-1	5
Universe novel adopt character image film	5
elaborate background event ''Star Wars film	5
example ''Zorba Hutt Revenge adult novel Hollace Davids reveals Jabba father crime lord Zorba Hutt Jabba wa born year event ''A Hope year time death ''Return Jedi .Paul Davids Hollace Davids ''Zorba Hutt Revenge Bantam ISBN 0-553-15889-9	5
Ann Crispin novel ''The Hutt Gambit explains Jabba Hutt Han Solo become business associate portrays event lead bounty Han head.A	5
Crispin ''The Hutt Gambit Bantam ISBN 0-553-57416-7	5
Universe anthology Dark Horse ''Jabba Hutt Art Deal —likewise detail Jabba Hutt rise head Desilijic clan role underworld ''Star Wars universe establishment crime syndicate Tatooine ''Star Wars galaxy Outer Rim Territories.Jim ''Jabba Hutt Art Deal Dark Horse Comics ISBN	5
''Tales Jabba Palace collection story science fiction author Anderson piece life Jabba Hutt minion palace relationship day life	5
story reveal Hutt servant loyal fact	5
Jabba Hutt ''Return Jedi courtier join force rival Tatooine family Hutt homeworld Nal Hutta claim palace fortune empire.Kevin Anderson ed. ''Tales Jabba Palace paperback Bantam ISBN 0-553-56815-9	5
Timothy Zahn novel ''Heir Empire reveals smuggler Talon replaces Jabba fish pond move headquarters Hutt empire Tatooine.Timothy Zahn ''Heir Empire paperback Bantam p. ISBN 0-553-29612-4	5