weekend Fleet battleship port weekend time	9
turn spending time port—six Pye battleship task force weekend weekend Halsey aircraft carrier task force	9
Halsey afford speed top speed	9
battleship aircraft carrier dash reinforce Island Marine detachment fighter wa Pye turn rest port harbor wa wa battleship morning.Lord pp	9
sun ''Nevada 7th ship band wa Colors plane horizon attack Harbor	9
Aft ''Arizona attack ''Nevada wa battleship Island wa maneuver battleship present	9
wa drydock time attack	9
ship Battleship Row order north south ''Nevada wa outboard	9
wa bottom row ''Nevada ability maneuver ''Nevada	9
''California wa undergo material inspection watertight integrity wa maximum wa hit bomb torpedo	9
result sank attack hit bomb torpedo	9
comparison ''Nevada bomb torpedo wa afloat wa Hospital Point	9
gunner fire engineer raise steam Type Mod torpedo Frame keel p. torpedo bulkhead held joint list	9
''Nevada list counter-flooding gunner shot plane	9
past Ten-Ten length foot	9
''Nevada wa struck bomb	9
struck port director platform base stack deck	9
turret inboard port waterway blew hole deck	9
struck forecastle Frame side deck ship gasoline tank leakage vapor tank intense fire ship	9
gasoline fire Turret damage magazine	9
day attack gun battleship standard-weight main-battery projectile heavier projectile penetration charge exchange slight decrease range	9
projectile powder charge magazine ''Nevada crew break projectile anticipation powder charge Sunday.Sabin A. USN	9
Comment Discussion States Naval Proceedings	9
bomb damage evident ''Nevada wa proceed west side Island prevent sunk channel cork rest fleet bottle	9
Bonner p. wa Hospital Point Wallin pp	9
help force plane hit bottom	9
men aboard salvage operation overcome hydrogen sulfide gas paper meat.Wallin p. ship minimum bomb hit torpedo hit ten bomb hit area sufficient size indicate struck bomb	9
day attack crewman ran repel boarder drill broomstick baseball bat arm practice invasion Hawaii	9
time homeless record left attack food shelter uniform	9