''Star Wars Universe literature elaborates Palpatine role ''Star Wars fiction film	5
appearance Palpatine ''Star Wars literature wa Dean Foster Lucas Novels Novelizations Collections novelization script ''A Hope ''Star Wars Adventures Luke Skywalker .George Lucas ''Star Wars Adventures Luke Skywalker paperback Del p. ISBN 0-345-26079-1	5
Foster characterizes Palpatine Senator president Emperor advisor	5
Palpatine appearance Universe ''Dark Empire series book Veitch Cam Kennedy	5
series set year ''Return Jedi Palpatine Emperor Palpatine	5
spirit return netherworld Force aid Sith ghost posse body Jeng Droga Palpatine elite spy assassin Emperor Hands	5
Droga flees secret base planet Byss Emperor advisor Sate Pestage exorcises Palpatine spirit channel clone Palpatine death	5
Palpatine attempt resume control galaxy plan Luke Skywalker Jedi Master	5
destroys Palpatine tank defeat Emperor Princess Leia help.Tom Veitch ''Dark Empire anthology Dark Horse Comics ISBN	5
Palpatine fate ''Dark Empire II ''Empire End series	5
''Dark Empire II series detail Emperor reborn Byss clone body	5
Palpatine try rebuild Empire Rebel Alliance grows weak.Tom Veitch ''Dark Empire II anthology Dark Horse Comics ISBN	5
''Empire End guard bribe Palpatine supervisor tamper Emperor DNA sample	5
cause clone deteriorate rate	5
Palpatine attempt posse body Solo infant son Princess Leia Han Solo clone body dy Luke Skywalker	5
Palpatine blaster shot Han spirit Jedi Empatojayos Brand strength prevent Palpatine spirit	5
Brand dy Palpatine spirit netherworld Sith Lord all.Tom Veitch ''Empire End anthology Dark Horse Comics ISBN	5
Novels focus Palpatine role Emperor	5
''Shadows Empire Perry ''The Armor W. Jeter mdash set ''The Empire Strikes ''Return Jedi mdash show Palpatine crime lord Prince Xizor bounty hunter Boba Fett fight enemies.Steve Perry ''Shadows Empire Bantam ISBN 0-553-57413-2.K	5
W. Jeter ''The Armor paperback Bantam p. ISBN 0-553-57885-5	5
Barbara novel ''Children Jedi set year ''Return Jedi feature woman Roganda Ismaren claim Palpatine son Irek.Barbara ''Children Jedi paperback Bantam ISBN 0-553-57293-8	5
''Jedi Prince series novel introduces insane mutant Triclops wa Palpatine son.Paul Hollace Davids ''Mission Mount Yoda ISBN 0-553-15890-2	5
DNA Palpatine woman wa born cast left forgotten	5
Triclops son Jedi Prince Palpatine grandson	5
Terry novelization ''The Phantom Menace ''Star Wars writer role Palpatine ''A Hope politician Sith Lord	5
Rob Williams ''Star Wars Tales Reaves novel ''Darth Maul Shadow Hunter explain Darth relationship apprentice Darth Maul.Rob Williams ''Star Wars Tales Dark Horse Comics .Michael Reaves ''Darth Maul Shadow Hunter paperback Del ISBN 0-345-43541-9	5
''Cloak Deception Luceno Reaves novel detail Darth encourages Federation build army battle droids preparation invasion Naboo	5
''Cloak Deception focus Palpatine career	5
becomes confidante Finis Valorum Padmé Amidala queen Naboo.James Luceno ''Cloak Deception paperback Del ISBN 0-345-44297-0	5
Palpatine role Clone Wars Darth novel Matthew Stover ''Shatterpoint Barnes ''The Cestus Deception Sean ''Yoda Dark Luceno ''Labyrinth Evil	5
release ''Revenge Sith ''Star Wars literature Palpatine role creation Empire	5
Ostrander ''Star Wars Loyalties chronicle Emperor Palpatine sends Darth Vader assassinate Sagoro Autem captain want nothing government plan defect.John Ostrander ''Star Wars Loyalties Dark Horse Comics	5
Luceno novel ''Dark Lord Rise Darth Vader set ''Revenge Sith Emperor sends Darth Vader planet discover clone trooper carry Order Jedi	5
Palpatine hope mission teach Vader mean Sith crush remnant Skywalker.James Luceno ''Dark Lord Rise Darth Vader Del ISBN 0-345-47733-2	5