illness year walk aid stick wa pregnant child.Battiscombe p. undertook tour Austria Egypt visit brother Crimean battlefield harem Ismail	7
Turkey woman sit dinner Sultan Abdülâziz .Duff pp	7
Biographers agree marriage wa way wife attention attack typhoid fever disease wa father brought reconciliation.Duff p. Magnus Battiscombe pp	7
others point frequent pregnancy period use family letter deny existence rift.Battiscombe p. wa quarter society apparent disinterest illness fever.Hough pp	7
marriage company woman actress Langtry Daisy Countess Warwick Agnes society matron Alice	7
knowledge Alice visit lay dying.Battiscombe p. Priestley p. herself faithful marriage.Battiscombe pp	7
degree deafness hereditary otosclerosis isolation spent time home child pets.Battiscombe p. Duff p. sixth pregnancy tragedy infant son day life	7
plea privacy Queen Victoria period court element press describe birth abortion arrangement mummery .Duff p. month Prince Wales wa absent tour dismay wa left	7
Prince group spend time	7
Prince tour friend wa Lord Aylesford wa told wife wa man Lord Blandford wa	7
Aylesford wa seek divorce	7
Lord Blandford brother Lord Randolph Churchill lover elopement	7
threat divorce Lady Aylesford sought dissuade husband Lord Aylesford wa adamant reconsider	7
attempt pressure Lord Aylesford drop divorce suit Lady Aylesford Lord Randolph Churchill told divorce wa proceed subpoena husband witness implicate scandal	7
threat advice Duchess Teck Queen Prince Wales	7
Lord Randolph Churchill year afterwards Prince Wales speak him.Battiscombe pp	7
spent spring period ill health brother Hellenes.Battiscombe p. wa Turkey towards Russia sister wa Tsarevitch revision border Turkey favour Greeks.Battiscombe pp	7
son spent year company boy sent worldwide cruise part naval education	7
farewell wa tearful letter dreadfully.Battiscombe pp	7
Saint Petersburg assassination Alexander II Russia represent provide comfort sister wa Tsarina.Battiscombe pp	7
Duff p. undertook public duty word Queen Victoria spare strain fatigue function	7
bazaar attends concert visit hospital place complains endeavour prove ha tiresome duty	7
Queen Victoria Duff p. interest Hospital	7
Merrick Elephant Man wa patient met.Battiscombe pp	7
Crowds Battiscombe p. visit Ireland rare moment public hostility Cork hotbed nationalism	7
husband booed crowd thousand people brandishing stick flag	7
way ordeal press portrayed visit light crowd	7
Telegraph Battiscombe p. part visit Doctorate Trinity College Dublin.Battiscombe p. death eldest son Prince Victor Clarence Avondale wa blow room possession kept left Prince left death pp	7
Duff p. angel happiness	7
Duff p. letter child indicate devoted.Battiscombe pp	7
brother-in-law Alexander III Russia nephew Nicholas II Russia Tsar	7
widowed sister Dowager Empress Maria leant support slept prayed stayed beside sister week Alexander burial.Battiscombe p. Duff pp	7