county Greater Manchester wa history constituent settlement part century	2
evidence Iron Age inhabitation Mellor Nevell Redhead p. activity settlement Chochion area Brigantes	2
Stretford wa part land Brigantes tribe lay border Cornovii side River Mersey.Bayliss p.	2
remains 1st-century fort Castlefield Manchester Castleshaw Roman fort Saddleworth evidence Roman occupation	2
region wa Domesday Book Redhead state wa survey wa sparsity population.Redhead Norman Hyde Pevsner p.	2
Ages Greater Manchester lay Salfordshire – ancient division county Lancashire	2
Salfordshire parish township Rochdale market town centre woollen trade	2
development Greater Manchester tradition flannel cloth production system trade.Frangopulo p. ix.Frangopulo pp	2
Revolution system Greater Manchester heritage textile manufacture Revolution infrastructure support sector	2
township Manchester rate turn century part process urbanisation brought boom textile processing.Aspin p.	2
Places Bury Oldham played role nation end century become mill town world.Cowhig pp	2
wa Manchester wa settlement city world marketplace cotton goods.Kidd pp	2
Manchester wa challenge city world success need government reform region city wa p.	2
18th century trader name ''Manchesterthum meaning Greater Manchester name region Manchester.Frangopulo p.	2
term Greater Manchester start century	2
wa report put response wa creation	2
report county set recognise Manchester commerce area part South-Lancashire part Cheshire borough minor authority radius mile Manchester .Swarbrick ''Greater Manchester Future Government Cities pp	2
book ''Cities Evolution planner Geddes Lancashire realises Greater .Frangopulo p.	2
Conurbations tend build-up historic county boundary Greater Manchester exception	2
Greater Manchester lay ancient county boundary Lancashire area south Mersey Tame Cheshire	2
Saddleworth area part part Yorkshire south-east part Derbyshire	2
area Greater Manchester part county Cheshire Lancashire Yorkshire county borough	2
1970s system demarcation wa described archaic inadequate pace impact motor travel increase government responsibility	2
''Manchester Evening Chronicle brought fore issue unity area headline Greater Manchester – Ratepayers Salvation	2
demand exploration possibility merger public service Manchester municipality .Frangopulo p.	2
issue wa civic leader area time Manchester Salford	2
Mayor Salford support idea day service Manchester Salford district Greater Manchester	2
Proposals World decade pace proposal government reform area quickened.Frangopulo p.	2
Lancashire Council system meet need county Lancashire Manchester district	2
proposal creation Manchester Council body	2
census UK reporting South-East Lancashire conurbation	2