Winchester Chronicle Winchester Parker Chronicle manuscript Chronicle survives	4
wa Old Minster Winchester towards end reign	4
manuscript begin genealogy chronicle entry year BC	4
scribe year entry interval 10th century scribe	4
manuscript becomes recensions entry	4
book copy Laws Ine bound entry wa Canterbury time eleventh century	4
Latin ''Acta Lanfranci cover church event	4
list pope Archbishops Canterbury sent pallium	4
manuscript wa Matthew Parker Archbishop Canterbury master Corpus Christi College Cambridge dissolution monastery college death	4
form part Parker Library.	4
Abingdon Chronicle wa scribe half 10th century	4
begin entry BC end entry	4
manuscript MS. Cotton Tiberius Aiii f. wa introduction chronicle contains genealogy doe extends 10th century	4
wa Abingdon mid-11th century wa composition	4
end list pope archbishop Canterbury sent pallium.	4
Abingdon Chronicle II material annals Abingdon wa	4
Old translation Orosius world history menologium verse law world humanity	4
copy chronicle BC scribe entry scribe entry difference scribe wa copy Chronicle	4
scribe Register cover year focus Aethelflaed	4
manuscript stop middle description Stamford Bridge	4
Worcester Chronicle middle century	4
text material Bede History set 8th-century annals	4
thought entry Archbishop Wulfstan	4
contains information manuscript affair ha wa copy court	4
Worcester held person—Oswald Ealdwulf Wulfstan explain recension wa found Worcester	4
century part manuscript eighteen page substitute entry source	4
page Joscelyn wa secretary Matthew Parker.	4
Chronicle fire monastery destroyed building	4
copy Chronicle kept time case copy wa version—most Canterbury	4
manuscript wa time scribe	4
scribe material Abbey version	4
Canterbury wa Register doe poem Brunanburh copy Chronicle	4
scribe annals entry interval record	4
wa Laud Archbishop Canterbury Laud Chronicle.	4
Canterbury Epitome copy Chronicle wa Christ Church Canterbury scribe note	4
version Old Latin entry Old wa Latin version	4
version scribe version scribe	4
introductory material chronicle doe include Brunanburh poem	4
manuscript ha annotation interlineations scribe scribe	4
/ Copy Winchester Chronicle wa Winchester	4
wa copy wa episcopal list suggests copy wa	4
manuscript wa destroyed fire Cotton wa	4
transcript Laurence Nowell century wa Wheloc edition Chronicle	4
Fragment consists leaf annals	4
entry phrase Winchester hence thought manuscript wa Winchester	4
manuscript relationship manuscript established.	4
Easter Table Chronicle Part wa scribe	4
annals hand Christ Church Canterbury	4
point manuscript wa St Augustine Abbey Canterbury	4
Caligula A.15 Provenance description manuscript history	4