Sergeant book ''A Century Chess remark Gossip play wa estimate .Sergeant p.	8
Forster note Gossip wa self-esteem	8
''The Times portrays Chess Winter Chessboard Kings Ways Looks Great Players ''The Times p.	8
Gossip beard look old-time monk	8
ha cranium bald top medium height	8
belief chessplayers world think everything beaten champion tournament	8
deliberate player nip flask brandy stand table	8
fact seem derive inspiration content played excellent game	8
Diggle observes Gossip developed 'a knack people corn print win offhand game player Bird Zukertort	8
example ''Columbia Chess Chronicle lecture day Steinitz Gambit	8
worthless analysis opening Gossip Winter ''Columbia Chess Chronicle pp	8
order point theory time prevent chessplayers analysis incompetent chess editor object Steinitz Gambit ha depreciate originality inventor try drag level shallow incompetency self-conceit submit variation rate posse merit hollow twaddle journal	8
Hooper Whyld note Gossip talent enemy attribute reception book opinion book time example Bird wa	8
measure talent controversy letter Pollock match Whyld ''The Shamrock	8
ha crank ha game forfeit	8
ha libel suit chess column ''Herald	8
committee call match draw	8
Chess historian Winter observes Gossip ha target mockery	8
note Hooper Whyld edition ''The Oxford Companion Chess light relief edition mention performance Hooper Whyld p. Hooper Whyld pp	8
Yakov Damsky ''The Batsford Book Chess Records question player distinction level opines Gossip feel competition .Damsky p.	8
Mike Fox book ''The Chess Addict write player ’ ve chess history claimant all-time grandpatzer title Hatfeild Dingley Gossip	8
record tournament anyone history Breslau Manchester win loss draw	8
Hooper Whyld overlook result tournament won game bottom.Winter	8
Gossip point score finisher Baird point Nicholas MacLeod point	8
ChessGames.com outcome tournament won tournament outright Chigorin place	8
article Whyld notice Gossip result suggests history ha unfair verdict .Whyld p.	8
Today FIDE World Chess Federation award Grandmaster title player Elo rating lesser Master FIDE Master title player respectively.Under FIDE player achieve Grandmaster title grandmaster norm event game rating point	8
player achieve Master title requisite Master norm rating point	8
FIDE player achieves rating FIDE Master title	8
Arpad Elo calculation Gossip strength peak wa equivalent Elo rating p.	8
assessment system Chessmetrics calculates Gossip rating wa number world 1889.Sonas Chessmetrics Player Profile Gossip	8
comparison world player time Chessmetrics rating	8
Chessmetrics rank Gossip number world period opportunity high-level competition rarer.Fine pp	8
Diggle Chessmetrics considers Gossip performance % opponent rating performance rating tournament	8
Gossip lifetime ''Deutsche Schachzeitung tabulation player percentage score tournament Cambridge Springs ranked number living player world.Forster p. table ''Deutsche Schachzeitung pp	8
Diggle writes fault Gossip wa man dauntless courage infinite capacity work become author reception edition ''Chess-Player	8
style wa show well-read man	8