Lieutenant Teofilo Marxuach wa officer day El Morro Castle	9
''Odenwald built World II war ship name wa supply ship force way Juan Bay deliver supply submarine	9
Lt. Marxuach order fire ship wall fort	9
Sergeant Encarnacion Correa machine gun fire effect	9
Marxuach cannon Rosa battery fire shot ''Odenwald stop return port supply	9
shot Lt. Marxuach States World	9
Odenwald wa States ''SS Newport	9
country World Puerto Ricans States citizenship	9
result Puerto Ricans exception woman draft	9
draft conscription lottery Puerto wa held island capital Juan	9
draft number wa picked Yaeger daughter governor Puerto Yager	9
number picked wa Juan Eustaquio Correa	9
Correa Puerto Forces States	9
Porto Regiment Infantry wa sent guard Panama defense Panama Zone Puerto Ricans World wa Lieutenant Frederick Lois Riefkohl US Puerto Cross	9
Cross medal Medal Honor wa Lt. Riefkohl action engagement enemy submarine	9
Lt. Riefkohl wa Puerto graduate States Naval Academy World II	9
Army wa shortage physician anesthesia salary specialty operating room	9
Army woman physician contract employee	9
Puerto woman doctor serve Army contract wa Dolores Piňero Juan	9
wa Juan base hospital anesthesiologist morning laboratory afternoon	9
Puerto Ricans Infantry Regiment wa Afro-Americans	9
fight counterpart fight member unit uniform	9
fought Front reputation nickname Hell Fighters Germans	9
wa Rafael Hernandez Marin Puerto composer	9
wa ''Croix de Guerre battlefield gallantry	9
USMC plane Curtiss C-3 Culebra Puerto	9
Marine aviation wa existence expansion Marine Corps air component Puerto played rule entrance World	9
Lieutenant Marine Section School island Culebra	9
number Marine Aviators avid desire Naval Aviation.Corum p.23	9
Marine Aviation wa Staes Naval Aviation	9
creation Marine Corps Aviation Company Puerto officer men.Sherrod p.4-5	9
Lt. Félix Rigau Carrera Curtiss JN-4 Lieutenant Felix Rigau Carrera Sabana Grande pilot training pilot school Seattle Minneapolis Minnesota	9
aviation training wa Lieutenant Marine Squadron deployed Marine Aviation Force p.4-5	9
Rigau Carrera unit bomber fighter support ''Day Rigau Carrera fighter pilot Marines	9
El Mundo Fallece El Aguila Fue Primer Boricua Manejo Avion en la Isla Rojas Daporte Porto Regiment Puerto wa Infantry Regiment Reorganization	9
need Puerto Guard unit apparent Luis Esteves instructor Puerto Officers Porto Regiment Infantry Camp Casas Puerto	9
request wa met approval government Puerto Legislature	9
regiment Puerto Guard wa Luis Esteves official Commandant Puerto Guard	9
Puerto Infantry Juan Chowon W.W. Pub	9
Presidio Press ISBN 0-89141-056-2	9