science fiction magazine appearance Stories pulp magazine Gernsback	4
science fiction genre time end field wa boom Nicholls Clute Genre SF Edwards Nicholls Science-Fiction Stableford Stories Edwards Nicholls SF Magazines Nicholls Clute Science Fiction	4
World II attendant paper shortage demise title	4
1940s market recover again.Edwards Nicholls SF Magazines Nicholls Clute ''Encyclopedia Science Fiction p.	4
magazine field commenced publication publishing date period ''History Science Fiction Magazine Vol	4
''Imagination wa middle publishing boom	4
groundwork wa laid Clark company publish issue ''Imagination wa Evanston Raymond Palmer	4
editor Stories end magazine Clark name date ''Fate spring Worlds issue wa ''Transformations pp	4
magazine editor N. Webster pseudonym Palmer wa conflict interest	4
issue Worlds Webster Palmer edit issue pretense wa masthead listing editor editorial wa Rap Raymond A. Palmer	4
World Science Fiction Convention Cincinnati held weekend ndash Palmer left described plan Clark	4
met Bea Mahaffey science fiction fan convention assistant editor.Ashley ''History SF Magazine Vol	4
online index ''Fate Worlds Palmer plan magazine ''Imagination	4
Material issue mid-1950 summer Palmer basement stair wa left waist	4
wa work Worlds ''Imagination wa Mahaffey coped inexperience	4
assistant Marge Budwig Saunder wa read slush pile help	4
magazine issue schedule news stand	4
year decision move Palmer want relocate ''Imagination	4
Palmer preparation publishing company Greenleaf left ''Imagination editor publisher.Ashley ''History SF Magazine Vol	4
companion magazine Tales addition company Greenleaf wa publisher ''Rogue men magazine ''Playboy	4
liquidation News Company distributor meant magazine distributor	4
Independent distributor magazine format digest-size science fiction magazine	4
format revenue case attract advertising income kept magazine afloat	4
end title result ''Imagination victim ''Imagination sister magazine invest money ''Rogue	4
issue ''Imagination wa issue Tales ''Space Travel issue.Michael ''Transformations pp	4
wa indication magazine end issue ''Imagination letter book review column issues.See issue	4
Online index Circulation figure 1960s example statement circulation Statement ''Analog Science Fiction/Science Fact vol	4
comparison ''Magazine Fantasy Science Fiction year circulation copy issue Fall ''Transformations p.	4