Gernsback editorial issue tale reading mdash ''Time Machines p.	4
scientifiction story power understood fiction entertain instruct.Ashley ''Time Machines p.	4
belief value science fiction wa attitude public towards pulp magazine wa trash .Carter ''Creation Tomorrow p.	4
issue reprint serialization ''Off Comet Jules Verne	4
Gernsback approach wa Verne novel	4
G. Wells Accelerator Edgar Allan Poe Facts Case Valdemar Gernsback put name author cover	4
magazine ''Science Invention Man Atom G. Peyton Wertenbacker mdash Allan	4
wa Austin Hall Man Earth .Ashley ''Time Machines p. ndash	4
issue Gernsback competition write story cover drawn illustrator prize	4
winner wa Cyril G. Wates story Gernsback	4
entrant become writer wa Clare Winger story Fate Poseidonia place competition wa issue F.C	4
entrant wa A. Hyatt Verrill Voice Inner World	4
letter column Discussions feature issue	4
science fiction reader community nobody fiction	4
Gernsback habit publishing address correspondent meant letter column fan correspond	4
Science fiction fandom trace letter column competitor historian field author Lester del ha introduction letter column event history science fiction .del ''World Science Fiction p.	4
example fan genre others letter Hess McIntyre FL	4
excerpt read “ plea help experimental station part public view desire touch chap caliber want opportunity inclination so. ” Letter Stories Vol	4
wa attract high-quality material Gernsback slowness author help	4
Wells Murray Leinster Gernsback pay story	4
payment pulp writer volume submission	4
writer quality story wa weak.Ashley ''Time Machines p. ndash	4
Gernsback audience wa le invention story adventure	4
A. Merritt ''The Pool serialization wa success wa basis story wa reader	4
cover garish juvenile reader complain	4
Raymond Palmer become editor magazine friend wa stop buying reason parent dislike cover illustration	4
Discussions Stories p. ''Time Machines p.	4
Gernsback sober cover issue lurid cover	4
combination quality fiction garish artwork ha critic comment Gernsback ghetto science fiction ''Time Machines p. ha creation market science fiction mature genre.del ''World Science Fiction p.	4
writer end time Stanton Coblentz continue longer Williamson	4
''The Skylark Space wa space opera found market ''Argosy printing science fiction.Ashley ''Time Machines p.	4
saw copy issue Sloane ndash issues.Sanders ''Smith pp	4
wa success Sloane sequel installment published.Moskowitz ''Seekers p.	4
wa issue Armageddon ndash AD Francis Nowlan wa appearance Buck Rogers print.Ashley ''Time Machines p.	4