Vaishnava author treatment Hindu epic Mahabharata Bhagavata Vedanta subject Hindu puranic traditions.Narasimhacharya p. wa age Vyasa Vaishnava poet doyen medieval epic poetry	4
Historians drawn parallel Adikavi Pampa c. Vyasa difference style	4
master respective period Pampa stylist age Vyasa generalist medieval age	4
Pampa product ''marga Sanskritic-mainstream period literature Vyasa flexibility ''desi ''shatpadi metre range language metaphor simile humour vulgarity.Shiva Prakash pp	4
Vyasa ''Gadugina Bharata Vyasa tradition	4
title work reference ''Gadagu Gadag author	4
ten chapter Hindu epic Mahabharata ''Karnata Bharata ''Kumaravyasa Bharata	4
dedication deity Gadag emphasis divinity grace Hindu	4
Pampa Jain interpretation epic ''Vikramarjuna Vijaya Pandava Arjuna hero Draupadi Arjuna wife prince loyal companion lofty Vyasa portrays character exception deeply human	4
depiction character coward Uttara noteworthy.Rice E.P	4
p. Akademi p. aspect work sense humour poet hero	4
work mark transition literature modern.Sastri p. use metaphor Vyasa title ''Rupaka Samrajya Chakravarti Emperor land Metaphors	4
chapter epic Timmanna court	4
poet work ''Krishnaraya Bharata patron king.Narasimhacharya p. p. ''Airavata Vyasa recount episode Mahabharata story elephant ridden Indra	4
Vyasa adaptation epic wa Valmiki pseudonym Narahari village wa	4
Mahabharata adaptation veers Jain version Nagachandra	4
Nagachandra ''champu metre Sanskrit work sought portray tragic hero	4
departure version Valmiki Jain epic end Rama asceticism ''nirvana .Sastri p. Valmiki account Valmiki tradition ''shatpadi metre author devotion Rama incarnation Vishnu	4
author epic wa Shiva conversation consort Parvati	4
version epic villain suitor Swayamvara ''lit ceremony choice husband	4
failure bride hand result jealousy towards Rama bridegroom	4
story progress Hanuman service heaped encomium status creator	4
end story war Rama realises Rama none Vishnu hastens die hand achieve salvation	4
chapter war ''Yuddhakanda prominence chapter	4
ha century folk theatre Yakshagana draw episode enactment.Sahitya Akademi p. influence Puranic tradition Madhavacharya narration opportunity glorify hero Rama	4
author ha abstraction graceful level predecessor Vyasa.Sahitya Akademi p. Bhagavata Sanskrit ''acharyas guru meant effect mass way life belief	4
Chatu Vitthalanatha court poet Raya successor Achyuta Raya wa translate Bhagavata stanza section	4
work version ''shatpadi metre	4
name colophon Sadananda Yati Nityatma Sukayogi scholar attribute work group others alternate name writer.Sahitya Akademi p. work cover ten avatar Vishnu depiction supreme Lord	4
purana cover story Vishnu devotee Prahlad Dhruva detail story demon Vritasura Hiranyakasipu others sought attain salvation hand Vishnu	4
epic influence composition Haridasas	4
epic period significance people	4
Chatu Vitthalanatha fuller version portion epic Mahabharata well.Sastri p. writer century Tirumala Bhatta ''Siva Ramendra ''Saundarya ''tripadi metre .Narasimhacharya pp	4