period nature sufficient evidence secular wa court	4
carry information life grandeur provincial court royal wedding ceremony	4
work refer town planning fortification ordnance detail Vijayanagara city irrigation reservoir merchant shop variety commodity	4
occasion author dwell city reflect view life.Sinopoli p. found work description artist relationship court	4
poet bard composer painter sculptor dancer performer wrestler	4
Others mention leader ambassador concubine accountant goldsmith moneylender servant door keepers.Sinopoli pp	4
Writings genre romance fiction erotica folk song composition	4
wealth literature subject astronomy meteorology science medicine astrology grammar philosophy poetry prosody biography history lexicon encyclopedia era.Narasimhacharya pp	4
Manjaraja book medicine ''Khagendra Mani 5th century Pujyapada.Rice E.P	4
p. Padmananka biography ancestor Padmarasa Hoysala minister poet work ''Padmaraja Purana	4
detail Hoysala empire personality poet Harihara Raghavanka.Sahitya Akademi p. Chandrashekara Chrakavi court poet Deva Raya II account Virupaksha temple precinct settlement Pampapura Hampi ''Pampasthana Sinopoli p. Mangaraja II lexicon ''Mangaraja Nighantu Abhinava Chandra account science book ''Asva Vaidya 14th century	4
Malla ''Manmathavijaya 14th century	4
15th century Madhava Sanskrit poem Dandi ''Madhavalankara Isvara prosody ''Kavijihva .Narasimhacharya pp	4
Deparaja member royal family ''Amaruka collection story ''Sobagina Sone form narration author wife.Sahitya Akademi p. p. ''Sobagina Sone wa Deva Raya II	4
contains detail king expedition hunter him.Kotraiah Sinopoli pp	4
Nanjunda feudatory prince history eulogy prince Ramanatha Rama ''Ramanatha Charite ''Kumara Rama Sangatya ''sangatya metre	4
poem prince heroic dawn Muslim invasion	4
work combine folk epic literature	4
protagonist reject advance stepmother death	4
minister achieves martyrdom Muslim invader capital.Sahitya Akademi p. Jain Srutakirti Mysore Sanskrit poem Hoysala lady Vijayakumari ''Vijayakumari Charite	4
detail city Vijayanagara royal capital shop guild business	4
text describes human settlement note people mundane duty barbering pot-making carpentry fort wall street them.Kotraiah Sinopoli pp	4
Salva poem ''Rasa Ratnakar ''Sharada Vilas	4
''rasa sentiment flavour latter portion ''dhvani meaning poem	4
Thimma ''Navarasalankara century discus flavour.Narasimhacharya p. century lexicon Lingamantri ''Kabbigarakaipidi Devottama ''Nanaratha Ratnakara	4
turn 17th century Deva grammar	4
''Karnataka line Sanskrit grammar work.Sahitya Akademi p.	4