''Vachana poetry developed reaction Hindu society peak popularity century	4
poetry risen position Vijayanagara period.Shiva Prakash p. Muslim invasion 14th century scholar Hindu lore	4
Veerashaiva anthologist 15th century collect Shaiva ''vachana poem palm leaf manuscript	4
nature poem anthologist commentary hidden meaning esoteric significance.Sahitya Akademi p. aspect work wa translation Shaiva canon Sanskrit order.Nagraj p. anthology ''Ganabhasita Ratnamale Prabhudeva ''Visesanubhava Satsthala Channaviracharya century ''Bedagina Vachanagalu Siddha Basavaraja	4
unique ''Shunyasampadane zero wa versions.Sahitya Akademi pp	4
wa Shivaganaprasadi Mahadevaiah set pattern	4
poem anthology form dialogue patron saint Allama Prabhu ''Sharanas devotee wa meant rekindle spirit century	4
Halage Arya Gummalapura Siddhalinga Yati Gulur Siddaveeranodaya versions.Shiva Prakash p. ''vachana poem decline passing era century latter day ''vachanakaras Tontada Siddhesavara Siddhalinga Yati Shaiva saint guru Virupaksha Raya II revival	4
''Shatsthala collection poems.Sastri p. Virakta Tontadarya life Tontada Siddhesavara theme ''Siddhesvara Purana .Rice p. Virakta Tontadarya Gummalapura Siddhalinga Siddhalingeshwara Ghanalingideva ''vachana poet recreate glory day poet expediency exist	4
literature resurgence towards 15th century attempt synthesise Veerashaiva advaitha philosophy trend century.Sahitya Akademi p. Prominent wa Nijaguna Shivayogi tradition petty chieftain region Mysore district Shaiva saint devotional song ''Kaivalya sahitya ''Tattva Padagalu song pathway emancipation	4
Shivayogi song reflective Yoga	4
metre language exception ''shatpadi metre	4
Shivayogi include encyclopaedia ''Vivekachintamani wa Marathi language Sanskrit language 18th century	4
categorises topic subject cover array poetics dance drama musicology erotics.Sahitya Akademi p. translation ''Shiva Yoga Sanskrit wa elucidate Shaiva philosophy benefit ignorant language.Rice E.P	4
p. post-Vijayanagara era ''Kaivalya tradition way	4
follower Nijaguna Shivayogi school wa elitist nature Mahalingaranga wa branch kept ''vachana tradition alive.Shiva Prakash p. poet-saints ''vachana tradition Shivayogi Sadakshari collection song ''Subodhasara Chidananda Avadhuta 17th century Sarpabhushana Shivayogi 18th century	4
vast body literature need	4