Veerashaiva writer devotee Hindu Shiva form exposition Shaivism	4
development literature period wa saint century Veerashaiva movement Allama Prabhu others protagonist writings.Nagaraj p. way ''shatpadi metre tradition work ''Basavapurana c.1369 form century Hoysala poet Raghavanka	4
work biography Veerashaiva ''purana	4
wa biography Hoysala poet Harihara author poem protagonist life ''Basavaraja Ragale Telugu Palkuriki Somanatha century	4
acknowledges eulogises predecessor personalities.Sahitya Akademi p. author start birth weave episode ''sharanas devotee Hindu Shiva Allama Prabhu—into life history	4
person devotee Shiva incarnation Nandi man miracle mission sent Veerashaiva faith earth	4
work ''aswasas division sixty-one ''sandhis chapter verse	4
narration story devotee Shiva overcame ego	4
work ''Bhimakaviswara Ragale ''Bhringidandaka .Sahitya Akademi p. pp	4
Chamarasa Jakkanarya patronage Deva Raya II.Rice E.P	4
Chamarasa champion Veerashaiva faith wa rival Vyasa court Deva Raya II	4
''magnum opus ''Prabhulinga Lile wa eulogy century saint Allama Prabhu wa Telugu Tamil language behest patron king Sanskrit Marathi languages.Sahitya Akademi p. story saint incarnation Hindu Ganapathi Parvati form princess Banavasi.Sastri p. stark contrast Vyasa epic Chamarasa spirituality	4
remark poet story mortal Vaishnava epic Mahabharata mortal wa evidence rivalry faiths.Sahitya Akademi p. king prime minister provincial governor encyclopaedia belief rite Veerashaiva faith ''Sivatattva Chintamani	4
work account life progenitor faith follower material student Lingayat movement.Sahitya Akademi p. reference work capital city Vijayanagara suburb	4
Jakkanarya minister court ''Nurondusthala story wa patron Natha Mahalinga Deva poet-saints ''vachana poem book Shaiva philosophy ''shatsthala .Sastri p. E.P	4
p. writer 15th century worthy mention Linga court poet Saluva Narasimha Adrisappa ''Praudaraya Rice B.L	4
p. Bommarasa ''Soundara Purana ''Janavasya Chaturmukha Bommarasa ''Revanasiddhesvara Purana Suranga ''Trisashti Puratanara Charitre Nilakanthacharya ''Aradhya court poet Ummattur chieftain Virananjendra.Narasimhacharya pp	4
Palkuriki Somanatha poet Telugu Singiraja account life ''Maha Basavaraja ''Singiraja Purana protagonist ''vachana poem detail deed information opponent court Bijjala II.Rice E.P	4
p. eminent poet time wa Guru Basava authorship ''Sapta ''shatpadi metre	4
form discussion guru disciple	4
''kavyas poem deal spiritualism extrasensory perception.Sahitya akademi p. Mallanarya Gubbi poet Sanskrit patronage Raya	4
''shatpadi metre ''Bhava Chintaratna ''Satyendra Chole ''Virasaivamrita Purana	4
wa 7th-century Tamil work Chola context Shaiva faith latter encyclopedic proportion content form sport ''lila Shiva life Shaiva saint	4
''Bhava Chintaratna work Nanasambandar Sastri p. Rice E.P	4
p. Virupaksha Pandita head priest Virupaksha Temple Vijayanagara account life deed century saint ''vachana poet Chennabasava	4
''Chenna Basava Purana regard protagonist incarnation Shiva describes glory Shiva devotee	4
book information date Veerashaiva saint ''vachanakaras ''vachana poet .Rice E.P	4
p. addition content insight capital Vijayanagara royal palace market place merchant encampment specialisation division guild worker capacities.Sinopoli p. author century Chermanka ''Chermanka Virabhadraraja ''Virabhadra Vijaya Chennabasavanka ''Mahadevi Purana Nanjunda Ikkeri ''Bhairavaesvara Sadasiva Yogi ''Ramanatha Vilasa	4