morning 5th Marine battalion west Lunga perimeter towards Matanikau	9
direct-fire support mm gun halftracks troop Raider Battalion Marines soldier Company Battalion Infantry pocket east side Matanikau river mouth	9
Company aid comrade Company cross Matanikau casualty Marine gunfire	9
7th Marine battalion position east one-log bridge night.Alexander p. Peatross ''Bless 'em p. ''Pearl Harbor pp	9
''Makin Griffith ''Battle p.	9
Edson commander Battalion 5th Marines action Alexander p.	9
Marine Nasu sent Company Infantry Regiment Battalion Matanikau	9
regiment commander word Marine operation battalion closer river counter Marine operation.Frank pp	9
Rain 7th Marines cross Matanikau	9
Battalion Marines ridge west Matanikau mile Point Cruz	9
Opposite position east bank river Company H Battalion 5th Marines position Company east bank rest Battalion west bank wa withdraw	9
result Marines attack night resume day	9
Unaware Marines position west bank Matanikau commander Maruyama Nasu unit hold place.Jersey ''Hell Islands p. Peatross ''Bless 'em pp	9
Griffith ''Battle p. p. ''Pearl Harbor p. ''Makin	9
night survivor Company men break pocket cross sandbar mouth Matanikau	9
Company soldier overran platoon Raiders attack direction hand-to-hand melee left Marines	9
Company survivor cross river reach line	9
Guidone Marine participant engagement fight wa hour hell	9
wa scream rifle machine gun tracer night– combination fog smoke darkness	9
''Hell Islands p. Peatross ''Bless 'em pp	9
Griffith ''Battle p. p. ''Pearl Harbor p. ''Makin	9
Marines fight Company Marine Raiders Alexander Griffith Peatross Marines	9
Raiders Company thought Battalion 5th Marines rear area pocket Alexander pp	9
morning Marines west Matanikau	9
Battalion 7th Marines Lieutenant Colonel Herman shoreline Point Cruz number troop Matanikau River loss artillery aircraft bombardment	9
west Puller Battalion 7th Marines Battalion Infantry ravine	9
artillery fire ravine Puller fire battalion mortar create Puller word machine extermination	9
troop time escape opposite side ravine cut number Marine rifle machine gun fire	9
intelligence information planning surprise Vandegrift Marine unit west Matanikau disengage return east side river wa ''Pearl Harbor pp	9
unit Puller wa Battalion Infantry Griffith wa Battalion Infantry	9