men Puller battalion west Lunga perimeter morning	9
morning Puller troop patrol Marine Lunga defense	9
Puller battalion camped night climb Mount day.Smith ''Bloody Ridge p.	9
Puller men northeast slope Mount bivouac soldier	9
noise skirmish company Oka Maizuru Battalion	9
Maizuru troop Puller Marines cover fire	9
Oka order towards Matanikau River engagement wa nightfall	9
Puller radioed headquarters help evacuate	9
Vandegrift send Battalion 5th Marine Regiment reinforcement day.Frank p. Zimmerman ''The Campaign p. ''Pearl Harbor p. ''Bloody Ridge p.	9
Lieutenant Colonel Puller unit	9
Puller sent casualty Lunga perimeter company battalion mission company Company headquarters staff night Mount Matanikau River.Smith ''Bloody Ridge p. pp	9
Zimmerman ''The Campaign p.	9
morning Puller troop Matanikau River cross bridge built wa one-log bridge	9
resistance defender bridge Marines north east bank Matanikau sand spit coast mouth river	9
Oka troop Marine attempt cross Matanikau sand spit attempt cross one-log bridge afternoon	9
meantime Griffith Raider battalion Merritt A. Edson commander 5th Marine Regiment Puller troop mouth Matanikau.Zimmerman ''The Campaign pp	9
p. ''Bloody Ridge p.	9
Company Regiment one-log bridge Alexander p.	9
Edson brought plan attack Lieutenant Colonel Merrill member Vandegrift division staff Griffiths Raiders Puller Company cross one-log bridge outflank river mouth/sand spit south	9
time battalion wa attack sand spit	9
attack rest Puller battalion land boat west Point Cruz surprise rear	9
Aircraft Field Marine mm mm artillery provide support operation	9
Marine begin day ''Pearl Harbor p. ''Bloody Ridge p. pp	9
Marine attack morning headway	9
Griffith Raiders advance one-log bridge Matanikau casualty death Griffith	9
unit mouth Matanikau night company 124th Infantry Regiment attack men.Alexander pp	9
p. ''Hell Islands p. Zimmerman ''The Campaign pp	9
Griffith wa shot shoulder brachial plexus night Alexander p.	9
result message Griffith air raid Field Marine communication net Vandegrift Edson Raiders Matanikau	9
Puller battalion wa proceed west Point Cruz	9
company Puller battalion Otho Rogers craft west Point Cruz	9
Rogers Marines inland ridge Hill area	9
Oka seriousness force Rogers Marines west east.Alexander p. p. ''Bloody Ridge p. Zimmerman ''Hell Islands p. ''The Campaign pp	9
Oka unit Puller men ridge Battalion 124th Infantry headquarters unit regimental machinegun platoon Battalion Infantry Gun Unit Company element Battalion Machinegun Unit	9
ridge Rogers men fire direction Oka force	9
Rogers wa hit mortar shell blew half	9
Captain commander company command deployed Marines perimeter defense ridge fight back.Smith ''Bloody Ridge p. pp	9
Marines Hill radio communication call help	9
Marines undershirt spell word H-E-L-P ridge	9
Cactus Force name aircraft operating Field SBD Dauntless operation undershirt message relayed message Edson radio.Zimmerman ''The Campaign pp	9
p. ''Bloody Ridge p.	9
Edson message Raider Battalion reporting failure cross Matanikau	9
reference men west side Matanikau beach help signalman Puller wa hail destroyer USS ''Monssen wa operation	9
aboard ''Monssen Puller destroyer ten craft towards Point Cruz communication ridge signal flag.Smith ''Bloody Ridge p. ''Pearl Harbor pp	9
time Oka troop position cut-off Marines Hill coast	9
''Monssen Puller blast path ridge beach	9
minute destroyer way wa Marines escape beach	9
casualty artillery fire Marines beach Point Cruz	9
Oka troop put fire Marines beach effort Guard crew craft fire cover Marines withdrawal	9
fire Marines craft Lunga perimeter action	9
Guard Signalman Class Munro wa fire craft Marines beach wa Medal Honor date member Guard receive decoration	9
p. Zimmerman ''The Campaign pp	9