summer Shelley couple ’ s joint journey travel book.Moskal “ Introductory note ”	4
point include letter Geneva trip Percy Shelley poem Mont Blanc journal letter text.Moskal “ Introductory note ” middle wa fair copy press ''Frankenstein publication Percy wa ''The Revolt Islam .Moskal Introductory note Nitchie	4
Percy journal section letters.Moskal “ Introductory note ”	4
Advertisements work Chronicle ''The Times promising release	4
wa Shelley ’ s work.Nitchie	4
''History Six Weeks Tour begin Preface Percy Shelley journal section	4
journal consists entry joint Percy Shelley kept trip Continent	4
word journal section Percy ’ s entry verbatim	4
passage sublime Percy ’ s words—passages nature experience terror awe transportation soul majesty nature Percy's.For list sentence verbatim ''The Works Percy Bysshe Shelley Monika.	4
entry Jeanne Moskal editor edition ''Tour nothing phrasing remains	4
section Claire Clairmont ’ s journal	4
Moskal “ Introductory note ”	4
section text consists Letters Residence Months Environs Geneva Summer Year	4
Moskal writes inference version epistle Fanny Shelley stepsister journey.Moskal “ Introductory note ”	4
Moskal note Shelley notebook time material letter notebook kind mix entry Shelleys journal notebook exhibit .Furthermore Letter contains passage found verbatim P. Shelley ’ s letter T. L	4
letter ’ s journal entry Percy letter Peacock.Nitchie	4
section text consists Percy ’ s poem Mont Blanc	4
Lines vale Chamouni wa publication poem lifetime.Colbert	4
ha Percy Shelley scholar Reiman ''History Six Weeks Tour lead Mont Blanc	4
work picturesque travel argue description Alpine scene nineteenth-century audience climax.Colbert	4
''History Six Weeks Tour wa “ Six Weeks ’ Tour ” “ Letters Geneva ” ''Essays Letters Abroad Translations Fragments Percy Bysshe Shelley Shelley	4
work husband include part life friend	4
work indicate authorship.Moskal “ Introductory note ”	4
Moskal explains unity volume volume wa way biography Percy Shelley	4
Percy Shelley father forbade Shelley memoir biography poet.Spark	4
version ''History Six Weeks Tour ha type change Moskal i modernization correction punctuation ii self-distancing relationship Claire Clairmont iii sensitivity identity iv presentation traveler reading circle .Moskal “ Introductory note ”	4
result change Percy Shelley ’ s wa version version	4
Shelley edition minor change version	4