Sheep fall victim poison disease injury	1
prey specie sheep system hide sign illness prevent predator	1
sign ill health sick sheep listless.Wooster p.	1
history money labor sheep husbandry ha prevent sheep ailment	1
shepherd remedy experimentation farm	1
developed country States sheep lack importance drug company perform trial drug ovine use.Smith et al. p.	1
instance shepherd resort extra-label usage drug animal	1
century minority sheep owner alternative treatment homeopathy herbalism medicine treat sheep problem	1
anecdotal evidence effectiveness alternative medicine ha met skepticism journal	1
need drug impediment sheep.Wooster breeder variety preventative measure warn problem	1
buyer avoid outlet clearing house animal flock sick inferior	1
mean flock sheep month	1
preventative program nutrition stress sheep	1
sheep loud way cause produce cortisol stress hormone	1
lead immune system sheep disease	1
Signs stress sheep include teeth restless movement wool wood	1
poison pesticide spray inorganic fertilizer motor oil radiator coolant ethylene glycol antifreeze sweet-tasting .Simmons Ekarius p.	1
Common form preventive medication sheep vaccination treatment parasite	1
parasite prevalent malady sheep fatal productivity flock	1
grazing incubate sheep digestive system cycle	1
medicine drenches flock treat worm worm egg feces ha ass infestation level	1
Afterwards sheep pasture avoid parasite	1
sheep parasite include louse part body sheep keds bot sheep itch mite maggot	1
Keds blood-sucking parasite cause malnutrition productivity fatal	1
Maggots bot fly blow-fly	1
Fly maggot cause destructive condition flystrike	1
Flies lay egg wound wet wool maggot hatch burrow sheep flesh death	1
addition treatment wool sheep rump preventative method	1
Nose bot fly inhabit sheep sinus breathing difficulty discomfort	1
Common sign discharge nasal passage movement head	1
parasite use backliners spray sheep dip	1
array bacterial disease affect sheep	1
Diseases hoof foot rot foot scald occur footbath remedy	1
painful condition cause lameness hinder	1
Ovine Johne disease disease affect sheep	1
Bluetongue disease illness fever inflammation membrane	1
Ovine rinderpest ''peste de petits ruminant fatal disease sheep goat	1
Orf scabby mouth ecthyma soremouth skin disease lesion contact	1
organism cause abortion sheep pregnant woman	1
concern prion disease scrapie virus cause foot-and-mouth disease FMD devastate flock	1
latter pose slight risk human	1
FMD pandemic UK sheep rare breed risk extinction	1