''Von der Tann Jutland part Hipper	9
''Von der Tann wa rearmost battlecruisers Hipper line	9
p. CETIt time section CET congruent perspective	9
hour UTC time zone works. Hipper force Beatty battlecruiser squadron	9
ship fire range yd m	9
''Von der Tann shot	9
Fourteen minute xiv ''Von der Tann hit shell explode sink	9
observer battlecruiser wa saw hit shell ''Von der Tann fore turret	9
interval thirty ship blew	9
Sheets flame dense smoke view	9
p. destruction Beatty force 5th Squadron battlecruisers opening fire yd m	9
p. ''Von der Tann ''Moltke rearmost Hipper squadron fire lead battleship 5th BS	9
Massie p. battlecruisers zig-zagging avoid gunfire ship	9
minute sinking ''Von der Tann wa hit cm shell ''Barham struck beneath waterline section belt armour ''Von der Tann ton water	9
hit ship gear ''Von der Tann s zig-zagging cause fall line port	9
Official History calamity breakdown gear wa ''Von der Tann hand battleship case Dogger action	9
Tarrant p. cm shell battlecruiser struck barbette ''Von der Tann s turret	9
chunk armour plate wa turret struck turret training gear jammed turret degree	9
put turret action duration engagement	9
Tarrant p. ship wa hit cm shell ''Tiger struck turret men	9
shell deck wreckage turret wa traverse starboard rudder engine room wa	9
turret wa action wreckage cut	9
Smoke fire burning practice target turret ship	9
Sections torpedo net ship	9
Tarrant p. ''New ''Von der Tann s destruction sight target fire ''Moltke .Brooks p. range ''Von der Tann ''Barham yd m point ''Von der Tann fire battleship	9
''Von der Tann hit ''Barham damage	9
p. shell ''Von der Tann return target ''New fore aft turret amidships turret longer target ''Barham .Tarrant p. gun turret jammed ''Von der Tann armament.Tarrant p. battle line distract gunner	9
wa longer gun ''Von der Tann wa manoeuvre manner avoid gunfire	9
ship speed kn km/h kn km/h	9
hour half difficulty D turret wa action	9
''Von der Tann shell hit cm shell struck aft tower	9
Shell splinter tower Gunnery Officer rangefinder operator crewman tower	9
Shell fragment debris shaft condenser put light ship out.Tarrant p. minute B turret wa action turret wa order	9
amidships turret difficulty put action battle	9
Tarrant p. Hipper flag ''Moltke battlecruisers increase speed knot fall rear line	9
''Derfflinger battle damage ''Von der Tann dirtiness boiler fire steam knots.Tarrant p. ''Derfflinger ''Von der Tann position astern II Squadron pre-dreadnoughts p. destroyer ''Moresby torpedo rear line ''Von der Tann s bow ship turn starboard avoid hit.Tarrant p. end battle Hipper report Scheer damage ship	9
time ''Derfflinger ''Von der Tann gun operation ''Moltke wa ton water ''Seydlitz wa	9
Hipper wa longer value engagement wa return harbour Commander-in-Chief await development Horns Reef battlefleet	9
Tarrant p. course battle ''Von der Tann s turret gunfire turret failures.Gardiner Gray p. ship wa fast gun amidships turret jammed recoil slide order.Massie p. der Tann wa battery hour turret order end battle Staff p. D turret bent metal oxyacetylene torches—afterwards gun hand	9
battle ''Von der Tann shell calibre shells.Tarrant p.	9