event Scone substance decade	7
story Annals Ireland event time claim Queen Æthelflæd Mercia ruler Norsemen sea coast Northumbria	7
''Annals Ulster record defeat fleet kingdom Ulaid Vikings coast time.Higham ''Kingdom Northumbria pp	7
ndash Annals Ireland FA ''Annals Ulster s.a.	7
period ''Chronicle Kings Alba report death Cormac mac Cuilennáin king Munster eighth year Constantine reign.The ''Annals Ulster state Cormac Woolf p. ndash	7
entry wa read time Domnall king Britons Domnall son Áed wa	7
wa thought record election brother Constantine Domnall kingship Britons Strathclyde wa evidence domination Strathclyde king Alba	7
entry question read Dynfwal Domnall son Áed king Ailech Domnall son Áed Findliath death ''Annals Ulster	7
re-reading Hudson Woolf ''Pictland Alba pp	7
ndash ndash Chronicle Kings Alba p.	7
Smyth ''Warlords Men pp	7
ndash interpretation found work	7
phrase question read ''et Dunenaldus filius Ede elig7	7
death Flann Sinna Niall Glúndub recorded.The ''Annals Ulster record death Flann Niall Woolf p. ndash	7
fleet Cáech Ragnall grandson Ímar Uí Ímair Ímar wa Ireland	7
defeat army Leinster retook Dublin Cáech Hart Ragnall Woolf ''Pictland Alba pp	7
ndash ''Annals Ulster s.a. ndash	7
year Ragnall sea intent king York.Woolf ''Pictland Alba p. ''Annals Ulster s.a.	7
event summer death Queen Æthelflæd Tamworth	7
Æthelflæd Northumbrians submission death put end successor brother Elder wa control Mercia.Higham ''Kingdom Northumbria pp	7
ndash Swanton Chronicle p. s.a.	7
part Northumbria kingdom son Eadulf 913.Keynes Rulers Woolf ''Pictland Alba pp	7
Ragnall invasion north assistance Constantine	7
south face Ragnall battle bank River Tyne Corbridge cross river	7
battle Corbridge ''Chronicle Kings Alba Constantine disagreement wa battle Corbridge	7
''Annals Ulster s.a. Annals Ireland ''Chronicle Kings Alba report battle	7
idea rest ''Historia de Sancto Cuthberto Anderson Annals p.	7
question Woolf ''Pictland Alba pp	7
report battle ''Annals Ulster none king mormaers men Alba	7
use word mormaer knowledge Constantine kingdom bishop bishop royal villa hint institution kingdom.For Mormaers Woolf ''Pictland Alba pp ndash Smyth ''Warlords Men pp	7
institution kingdom Alba Corbridge Ragnall respite	7
south son control Mercia burh Peak army strike north	7
army Dublin Ragnall kinsman struck Mercia met Ragnall king	7
Chronicle state king chose father lord	7
king present Constantine son Eadwulf king Strathclyde Dyfnwal II Owen	7
term record Chronicle time word ''scottas Scots derives describe inhabitant Constantine kingdom report events.Stenton pp	7
ndash Swanton Chronicle p. s.a. Woolf ''Pictland Alba pp	7
realm Saxons Ælfweard Mercians chose Æthelstan Æthelflæd court	7
Ælfweard week father Æthelstan wa king land 925.Keynes Rulers p. Æthelstan Stenton p.	7