Police male brothel Cleveland	7
police interrogation rent boy pimp name client Lord Somerset Equerry Prince Wales.Cook pp	7
time act men client ostracism prosecution year imprisonment labour	7
Cleveland scandal high-ranking figure society	7
Rumours swept upper-class involvement member royal family Prince Victor.Hyde ''The p. rent boy Victor Somerset solicitor Newton spread rumour heat client.Channel	7
Letters Solicitor Augustus Stephenson assistant Hon	7
Cuffe reference Newton threat implicate Victor.Aronson p. Cook pp	7
Hyde ''The Cleveland Scandal p. Prince Wales investigation none client nothing Victor wa proven.Howard	7
Issue p. col. G conclusive evidence involvement club brothel Aronson p. rumour cover-up biographer suppose visit Cleveland Aronson p. wa .Aronson p. others refer involvement rumour unfair .Bradford p. historian Montgomery Hyde evidence wa	7
Hyde ''The Cleveland Scandal p. Somerset sister Lady Waterford brother knew anything Victor sure boy straight line doe boy spends time belief boy innocent wrote.Blanche Beresford Marchioness Waterford Viscount Esher Aronson p. Cook pp	7
letter Somerset friend Lord Esher Somerset denies anything Victor confirms ha heard rumour hope help quash prosecution	7
writes understand Prince Wales annoyed son name thing wa case left place end court	7
Lord Somerset Viscount Esher Cook p. boy name Probyn Montagu thought	7
wise hearing knew others knew matter authority	7
Lord Somerset Viscount Esher Aronson p. Cook pp	7
Hyde ''The Cleveland Scandal p. rumour sixty year official biographer V Harold Nicolson wa told Lord wa schoolboy time scandal Victor male brothel scene solicitor commit perjury	7
solicitor wa struck roll offence wa	7
p. None lawyer case perjury struck scandal Somerset solicitor Newton wa obstruction justice client escape wa week prison	7
twenty year Newton wa struck twelve month misconduct letter clients—the murderer Harvey Crippen.Cook pp	7
wa struck year imprisonment money pretences.Cook pp	7
Hyde ''The Cleveland Scandal p.	7