USAF F-4 action F-4CAIM-7 Sparrow401014 Sidewinder1201022 mm gun3014 tactics2002 F-4D Falcon4 Sparrow422026 Sidewinder0235 mm gun4.5026.5 tactics0022 F-4E Sparrow02810 Sidewinder0044 mm gun0011 mm gun0145 tactics0101 Total33.5866107.5 USAF service F-4 wa F-110 Spectre fact sheet F-110 introduction States Tri-Service aircraft designation system	9
reluctant adopt fighter USAF design Phantom user	9
Force Phantoms F-4Cs 555th Triple Nickel Fighter Squadron Fighter Affairs Office Aviano Base Force	9
flew Phantom Naval Aviator pilot front seat Naval Flight Officer radar intercept officer RIO seat Force flew Phantoms pilot seat	9
policy wa navigator system officer weapon system officer WSO rear seat	9
flew pilot rear seat USAF Phantoms flight control service life	9
F-4Cs Fighter Squadron assignment USAF victory North MiG-17s Sidewinder air-to-air missiles.Dorr Bishop p.	9
Phantom Fighter Squadron aircraft enemy Fighter F-4C jet air-to-air missile MiG-21 Fishbed	9
aircraft leak fuel tank re-sealing flight aircraft found crack outer rib stringer	9
problem aileron control cylinder connector engine compartment fire	9
Reconnaissance debut post-strike reconnaissance mission	9
F-4C wa F-4B flight performance Sidewinder missile F-4Ds Falcons	9
Falcon predecessor wa shoot bomber straight level	9
reliability others sequence seeker-head time useless combat agile fighter	9
F-4Ds Sidewinders Rivet Haste program Dogfight Sparrow become missile USAF pilot	9
Phantoms F-4Ds radar RHAW antenna detect Guideline SAMs.Knaack p.	9
deployment F-4C Southeast Asia USAF Phantoms air superiority ground attack role ground troop bombing sortie Laos North	9
F-105 force underwent attrition bombing role F-4 F-105D wa withdrawn combat primary USAF ordnance delivery system	9
squadron EF-4C Weasel aircraft deployed Thailand duty.Swanborough Bowers p.	9
E prefix wa aircraft F-4C Weasels	9
Sixteen squadron Phantoms deployed others deployed combat assignments.Baugher Joe	9
Peak number combat F-4s Thailand	9
Force Phantom fighter-bombers combat North MiGs SAMs AAA	9
wa squadron Davies p. loss combat North SAMs AAA .Correll T. PDF ''AIR FORCE Magazine	9
attribution USAF Operations Report	9
war end Force F-4 Phantoms	9
US Naval/Marine loss Phantoms F-4/RF-4 Phantoms	9
Weasel F-4G configuration Shrike missile	9
aircraft wa TFW AFB Capt Ritchie USAF ace war	9
WSO Capt DeBellevue highest-scoring ace war victory	9
WSO Capt Feinstein USAF ace war	9
return States DeBellevue Feinstein pilot training Feinstein wa vision waiver USAF pilot F-4	9
USAF F-4s MiG kill Southeast Asia Sparrow Sidewinder Falcon gun mean	9
170th Fighter Squadron/183d Fighter Guard Guard unit transition Phantoms	9
F-4 ANG service wa F-16 Falcon	9
F-4G Weasel Vs Shaikh Isa Bahrain Operation Desert Storm	9
reason wa F-4G wa aircraft USAF inventory suppression enemy air defense SEAD role EF-111 capability AGM-88 HARM missile wa aircraft ultra-long-range LOROP long-range oblique photography camera	9
spite mission wa fatal accident start hostility	9
F-4G wa enemy fire fuel tank aircraft ran fuel airbase	9
USAF Phantoms F-4G Weasel Vs Fighter Squadron	9
flight F-4G Weasel wa 190th Fighter Squadron Guard	9
USAF/ANG F-4 land wa flown Maj Mike Webb Maj Leeder ANG	9
Force operate QF-4 target drone Targets Squadron	9
F-4 remain target role ATRS	9