citizen split issue Civil	3
state tie Ohio River city Pittsburgh Cincinnati time link	3
Unionist tradition Commonwealth history east	3
tie North gain war state	3
slaveholder felt protection slavery wa	3
election sentiment state % vote Breckinridge % % Lincoln le %	3
Allan Nevins election result mean Kentuckians secession coercion secessionist	3
majority coalition supporter wa moderate Unionist position precipitate action extremist side.Nevins pp	3
ndash majority citizen state mediator North	3
Governor Beriah Magoffin sent letter slave state governor agreement North include strict enforcement division territory parallel guarantee use River veto slave legislation	3
Magoffin conference slave state conference state secure concession	3
pace event conference wa held.Harrison ''The Civil pp	3
ndash Governor Magoffin session ask legislator convention decide Commonwealth course conflict.Harrison ''The Civil p. ''Louisville Courier position secessionist legislature Too time ha	3
historic moment past return	3
u time act NOW NEVER	3
Shortridge p. Unionists hand surrender fate state convention moment excitement adopt extreme remedy secession	3
Heck p. Unionist position state right legislator idea immediate secession convention.Shortridge pp	3
ndash send delegate Peace Conference D.C. call convention resolution secession crisis Crittenden Compromise Crittenden.Harrison ''The Civil p. result Fort Sumter Lincoln sent telegram Governor Magoffin Commonwealth supply regiment share request troop war.Harrison ''Kentucky Governors pp	3
ndash Magoffin sympathizer Lincoln D.C	3
send man dollar purpose sister state	3
Magoffin Powell p. house met declaration neutrality war position Governor Magoffin ''The Civil p. election held Unionist candidate won ten seats.Rose pp	3
ndash Confederate sympathizer won Jackson Purchase region wa Tennessee Cumberland Tennessee p. defeat poll wa Rightists election vote cast Unionists ''The Civil p. sympathizer dealt blow election state legislator	3
election veto-proof Unionist majority ndash ndash	3
Magoffin veto protect interest overridden	3
Wilson Porter Shortridge analysis secession longer option pro-Confederate force supporter neutrality	3
Unionists front secessionist agenda	3
Unionists hand way move moderate middle “ definite stand government. ” maneuvering decisive point Confederate force Tennessee town Hickman Columbus	3
ndash legislature resolution Magoffin order Confederate force force state	3
Governor vetoed resolution overrode veto Magoffin order	3
week assistance governor call state militia join force	3
Again overrode veto Magoffin acquiesced.Shortridge p.	3