Between Thao counter-coup contact past decade	9
Thao mdash seize power mdash plot join coup air force chief claimed wa	9
noon fifty tank crew mixture infantry battalion connection seize control headquarters post office radio station Saigon	9
home Gia Palace residence head state Phan Suu	9
country wa stability Phan Huy Quat prime minister day earlier.Moyar p.	9
escape flee Vung Tau	9
plane Tan Son Nhut Base country headquarters rebel tank block runway.Tang p.	9
Thao radio announcement sole objective operation wa described dictator	9
recall Saigon lead Forces Council place retain cabinet	9
Thao league Lam Van wa seize Bien Hoa Base prevent air force chief air power	9
religion Thao wa recruit Diem loyalist Phat.VanDeMark p.	9
attempt seize Bien Hoa Tan Son Nhut bomb rebel	9
force III IV Corps capital disliked rebel action.Moyar pp	9
Thao met meeting Americans power	9
coup midnight loyal ARVN force swept city south loyal Bien Hoa north	9
rebel deal wa struck end revolt exchange removal disputed.Moyar p. p.	9
Thao broadcast message nation radio coup	9
wa case chaos Forces Council adopt vote confidence control.Shaplen pp	9
hiding Thao willingness surrender cooperate government Quat fifty officer coup amnesty	9
exile States family wa sent training pp	9
tribunal Thao death ''in absentia	9
death sentence wa influence Nguyen Chanh Thi wa rival Thao hit squad look	9
conclusion trial wa Forces Council disband control government	9
Thi wa transfer power government return Thao death	9
result Thao choice attempt seize power order Thi manoeuvre	9
half dozen officer forty charge assassinate Quat kidnap Thi supporter Thao authority	9
Thao escape USD bounty wa put ''junta	9
wa circumstance official report claimed injury helicopter ''en route Saigon north city	9
wa death order officials.Shaplen pp	9
report hold priest betrayed Thao claim Nguyen Van Thieu caught	9
memoir claimed Thao wa beating .Ky p.	9
Fall Saigon conspiracy theory Thao underground counterintelligence Office hunt cadre	9