DNA hybridization study relationship Sibley Ahlquist split Procellariiformes family year fossil bone order described genus ''Tytthostonyx ha found rock boundary mya remains incomplete placement Procellariiformes certain.Dyke G. Van Tuinen radiation bird Neornithes molecule morphology fossil record Society molecular evidence suggests storm-petrels diverge stock albatross procellariids petrel splitting	1
taxonomist retain petrel family today distinctiveness	1
procellariid genus splitting family Oligocene fossil Belgium shearwater genus ''Puffinus ''Puffinus raemdonkii ''Puffinus	1
A. Poole Gill ed	1
Academy Sciences PA Ornithologists ’ D.C. genus Miocene	1
basal radiation Procellariiformes Eocene order bird anomaly molecular evolution rate pattern family Rheindt Austin ''Emu G Body Size Effects Rates Cytochrome b Evolution Seabirds Biology Evolution ''see Leach Storm-petrel molecular date tentative	1
genus ''Argyrodyptes ''Pterodromoides fossil	1
''Eopuffinus Paleocene Procellariidae placement Procellariiformes doubtful	1
Sibley Ahlquist taxonomy ha member Procellariiformes Procellariidae family Ciconiiformes change ha	1
procellariid family broken distinct group fulmarine petrel gadfly petrel prion shearwater	1
* fulmarine petrel include procellariids giant petrel fulmar specie Snow Petrel Petrel Cape Petrel	1
fulmarine petrel diverse group habit appearance skull feature prominent nasal tube	1
* gadfly petrel helter-skelter flight specie genus ''Pterodroma specie genus ''Bulweria	1
specie vary medium size hooked bill	1
genus ''Pterodroma split sub genus Origins phylogeny taxonomy gadfly petrel ''Pterodroma spp	1
''Ibis specie split genus	1
* prion comprise specie prion genus ''Pachyptila Petrel	1
past whalebirds specie bill lamella use filter plankton baleen whale name derives association whale bill prion doe Ancient saw	1
* shearwater prey ocean surface specie ha deep	1
shearwater include specie genus ''Puffinus ''Procellaria specie ''Calonectris specie	1
genus shearwater ''Procellaria petrel name	1
study split shearwater genus ''Puffinus clade subgroup Puffinus Neonectris	1
Puffinus 'smaller ''Puffinus shearwater Manx Audubon Shearwaters example Neonectris 'larger ''Puffinus shearwater Sooty Shearwaters example wa Neonectris split genus ''Ardenna	1
Analysis taxonomy nomenclature Procellariformes sequence mitochondrial cytochrome b gene	1
split clade thought ''Puffinus split procellariids genus north Neonectris clade hemisphere.Austin Phylogenetics ''Puffinus Shearwaters Evidence Cytochrome b Sequences Phylogenetics Evolution	1
HTML abstract taxonomy family split group ha challenged research	1
study Nunn Scott fulmarine petrel discrete group family gadfly petrel genus ''Pterodroma	1
petrel genus ''Bulweria longer gadfly petrel closer shearwater genus ''Procellaria	1
genus ''Pseudobulweria ''Lugensa split gadfly petrel genus ''Pterodroma ''Pseudobulweria closer ''Puffinus shearwater ''Pterodroma gadfly petrel V. Attié Pasquet Cytochrome-B evidence validity relationship ''Pseudobulweria ''Bulweria Procellariidae ''Auk :188–195 ''Lugensa Petrel shearwater fulmars.Imber thought ''Lugensa fulmarine petrel Nunn nearer Neonectris ''Puffinus shearwater	1
prion Nunn amongst shearwater group	1
''Calonectris shearwater ''Puffinus clade closer Puffinus clade distant ''Procellaria shearwater	1
relationship genus genus subject debate researcher splitting specie genus family position genus family	1
specie amongst seabird Fiji Petrel time discovery science others breeding ground Shearwater	1
list note taxonomy ''List Procellariidae	1