return Shackleton body Georgia memorial service held honour Trinity Church Montevideo service held St member royal family	3
year biography ''The Life Shackleton Mill	3
book tribute explorer wa effort assist family Shackleton £40,000 debt £1.5	3
initiative wa establishment Shackleton Fund wa assist education child support mother.Fisher p. decade Shackleton status polar hero wa outshone Captain Scott	3
Scott polar party monument glass window statue bust memorial tablets.Jones pp	3
ndash statue Shackleton Edwin Lutyens wa Royal Society headquarters Fisher pp	3
ndash public memorial Shackleton	3
word saw attention Scott mdash forty-page booklet Shackleton OUP part Great Exploits series described historian Stephanie lone example treatment Shackleton sea treatment Scott	3
disparity p. ''Endurance Shackleton Voyage wa	3
wa number book Shackleton light	3
time attitude towards Scott note wa literature Roland Huntford treatment biography ''Scott described attack .Barczewski p. picture Scott truth Fiennes p. kind heroism Scott victim shift twentieth century.Barczewski p. year overtaken public esteem Shackleton popularity erstwhile rival	3
BBC poll determine Britons Shackleton wa ranked eleventh Scott wa place.Barczewski p. Stephanie Capparell Shackleton model leadership book ''Shackleton Way Leadership Lessons Great Explorer	3
Shackleton resonates executive today business world	3
approach leadership guide anyone position authority p. management writer lead Shackleton examplar order chaos	3
Centre Leadership Studies Exeter offer course Shackleton feature management education programme university	3
Shackleton School wa set Outward principle motto Journey Everything	3
Shackleton ha model leader US textbook leadership L Steinke call Shackleton archetype leader calm reflective demeanor becomes toxicity reactive behaviour	3
Athy Heritage Centre-Museum Athy Ireland Shackleton Autumn School held honour memory Shackleton commemorate era heroic polar exploration Shackleton death marked end Heroic Age Exploration period discovery journey exploration continent benefit travel method radio communication	3
preface book ''The Journey World Cherry-Garrard Scott team Terra Expedition joint piece organization Scott Winter Journey Wilson dash Pole nothing devil hole want Shackleton time Wheeler pp	3