Senator chairman Permanent Subcommittee Investigations investigation incident response complaint family member shootdown victim wa anyone shootdown.Verhovek Force Officer Is Army Aircraft Diehl ''Silent Knights p. Piper ''Chain Events p.	9
response complaint DoD response incident Representatives Services Subcommittee Personnel hearing incident examine accident investigation judicial action	9
addition DoD USAF reexamine action personnel shootdown Chiefs Staff review corrective action determine action wa	9
Widnall USAF chief staff Fogleman begin review accountability incident.Washington Blame	9
Schmitt Chief Force Grounds Pilots Piper ''Chain Events p. ndash Diehl ''Silent Knights p.	9
Security hearing wa Congressman Bob Dornan day	9
hearing Pilkington Andrus USAF accident investigation wa Wickson OPC rule engagement VID pas Black Hawks wa inadequate determine helicopter origin	9
USAF Colonel pilot Jerry Cox concern F-15 pilot responsibility actions.Piper ''Chain Events p. ndash ndash Hall ''Michael Son pp	9
Others hearing US Army Stephan Silvasy Chiefs Staff USAF Nolan Sklute USAF Advocate US Lair Director Operations US US Army Captain Nye Eagle Flight pilot USAF Colonel Jerry Cox USAF pilot journalist Times Spinner Wang attorney Hall	9
Fogleman spoke press conference conclusion review accountability USAF personnel shootdown incident	9
investigation found performance evaluation shootdown fact action incident.Schmitt Chief Force Grounds Pilots GAO Operation Comfort Fogleman fact conduct rise prosecution conviction end inquiry appropriateness action	9
Force standard require people display discipline judgement training duty require people	9
Piper ''Chain Events p. ndash	9
Fogleman Wickson Wang Halcli Wilson aviation service duty year	9
Fogleman letter evaluation permanent personnel file Wickson Wang Halcli Wilson Pilkington Emery meet Force standard job knowledge judgment leadership	9
addition decoration O'Brien service OPC wa	9
videotape Fogleman described action incident view standard accountability wa USAF USAF officer officer executive service view Black hawk incident 'tragic series error GAO Operation Comfort Schmitt Chief Force Grounds Pilots Piper ''Chain Events p. Sklute DoD	9
Fogleman found justice system wa work .Sklute DoD	9