Fincher use digital Viper Filmstream camera shoot film	5
Fincher Viper past year Nike Packard Lexus experiment equipment	5
digital camera watch shot resolution experience le equipment failure film thing film damage cost post-production	5
wa use desktop software Cut Pro edit ''Zodiac	5
Fincher interview Dailies end veil look time think 'Oh god work	5
belief ''Zodiac wa shot high-speed film camera slow-motion murder sequence	5
Mann ''Miami effort co-production sister studio DreamWorks Mark Ruffalo shot camera format	5
shot Viper camera file DVCPro HD Cut Pro	5
stage digital source footage wa maintain digital movie	5
digital production ''Superman Returns ''Apocalypto HDCAM tape format	5
Fincher director photography Savides ''Se7en shot opening credit ''The Game	5
Savides script “ wa exposition people phone conversation	5
wa imagine way ”	5
Fincher Savides want repeat look ''Se7en	5
director approach ''Zodiac wa create look mundane audience accept wa truth	5
filmmaker want glamorize killer tell story eye	5
“ story first-person-shooter video game	5
didn ’ t want sort movie killer want ” Fincher	5
Savides experience Viper Filmstream camera wa Fincher	5
Fincher sure camera wa towards film production studio project budget	5
camera “ thing ‘ ’	5
everything wa camera ”	5
Savides felt camera limitation	5
Fincher Savides photograph Eggleston Shore work Seventies photo Zodiac police file	5
men capture look feel period Fincher “ suppose VW bug think show representation time	5
''San Chronicle wa built post office Terminal Annex Building downtown	5
building Sprint subbed Hall Justice Police	5
shot week Bay Area rest time L.A. film budget	5
cast wa Fincher ’ s way perfectionism	5
Gyllenhaal wa director ’ s method interview “	5
’ s point ‘ ’ s work with. ’ reshoot thing	5
’ s risk ” Downey “ time garrote wa	5
think ’ m perfect person work understand gulag ”	5
Fincher “ actor role ’ t resent fact ’ m wait	5
day production shot Mark Jake – ’ s ’ s movie ”	5
Ruffalo director ’ s method “ way enter someone ’ s world actor	5
put expectation experience ’ s push change hold think stubborn journey ’ s disappointment anger ”	5