Zappa relationship long-time manager Herb Cohen	6
breakup wa affair Zappa Cohen wa DiscReet Records signing act Zappa approve.Miles ''Frank Zappa p.	6
Cohen lawsuit Zappa return froze money Zappa Cohen out-of-court settlement MGM right Mothers Invention	6
Zappa access material trial	6
Zappa master copy ''Zoot Allures Bros. bypassing DiscReet.Miles ''Frank Zappa p. pp	6
mid-1970s Zappa material leather four-LP project	6
aspect Zappa styles—rock tune work instrumentals Zappa trademark guitar solo	6
quadruple-LP Bros. Records release it.Lowe ''The Words Zappa p.	6
Zappa agreement Mercury-Phonogram test Halloween release Bros. release right material.Miles ''Frank Zappa p.	6
Zappa Pasadena radio station broadcast listener tape recordings.Slaven Don Quixote p.	6
lawsuit Zappa Bros. Zappa material wa year	6
Bros. part Zappa album promotion.Miles ''Frank Zappa p.	6
wa remains Zappa material four-LP set Mercury-Phonogram e.g. ''Frank Zappa	6
liner note release Gail Zappa state wa box set	6
Zappa right material MGM Bros. contract ''Frank Zappa	6
p. lawsuit meant period Zappa income band	6
Drummer Terry Bozzio band member Napoleon Murphy Brock stayed Mothers Invention bassist Estrada	6
musician bassist O'Hearn singer-guitarist Ray keyboardist Eddie Jobson	6
Zappa guest television show ''Saturday Night .Miles ''Frank Zappa p. Zappa host act show actor sketch	6
performance impromptu collaboration cast member piece Purple Lagoon	6
Samurai Futaba character strange guitar/microphone contraption Zappa conducting.Zappa ''Zappa Liner Notes	6
Zappa song Slime wa voice-over ''SNL booth announcer Don Pardo Peaches En Regalia	6
Zappa Zappa band time addition Ruth Underwood horn section Brecker Christmas album Bros. ''Zappa	6
mix intense instrumentals Black Page song Titties Beer .Lowe ''The Words Zappa p.	6
composition drum kit developed band complexity rhythmic structure change tempo meter passages..	6
''Zappa song sex Enema Bandit Don Pardo opening song	6
song album reference critic content.Miles ''Frank Zappa pp	6
Lowe ''The Words Zappa p.	6
Zappa criticism wa journalist reporting life saw it.Miles ''Frank Zappa p.	6
fight censorship society primitive belief word language corrupt moment hear	6
album Bros. Records Zappa consent ''Studio Tan Dirt suite tune wa midst problems.Lowe ''The Words Zappa p.	6
label artist consent wa Favorites concert music	6