engineering firm Aerotrope sculpture design Performance Structures PSI wa chosen fabricate ability produce weld	0
project PSI recreate design miniature	0
high-density polyurethane foam model wa wa design structure interior component	0
PSI build sculpture ship Panama Seaway	0
plan wa park official decision wa transport panel truck structure task MTH Industries.Sharoff p.	0
thickness steel create sculpture fabrication wa difficult.Gilfoyle p.	0
''Cloud Gate wa weigh completed.Gilfoyle p.	0
weight engineer reconsider sculpture structure	0
roof Park Grill ''Cloud Gate sits built bear weight	0
wall train track North Grant Park garage support weight sculpture form side restaurant	0
wall rest garage foundation bracing piece wa	0
''Cloud Gate member underneath plaza sculpture interior structure tie rod	0
''Cloud Gate polished exterior shell steel structure sculpture	0
piece type stainless steel ring put place	0
construction pipe truss ring	0
truss structure present construction phase	0
sculpture ha inner bracing.Sharoff p. component point wa avoid indentation exterior shell	0
frame wa expand contract sculpture temperature fluctuate	0
result ring sculpture move shell move ring	0
omphalos weld polished ''Cloud Gate interior component construction crew work outer shell comprises stainless steel panel thick	0
Computers robot bending plate wa wheel device.Sharoff p. Metal stiffener panel interior face provide degree rigidity	0
plate interior structure Oakland	0
plate polished percent state protective film sent truck	0
plate linear foot m seam	0
Welders keyhole machine guns.Sharoff p. plate filing wa fitting position	0
construction shell tent wa piece shield public view	0
Construction omphalos plate steel structure underside sculpture downward outermost surfaces.Gilfoyle p.	0
sequence structure sombrero bottom wa complete.Gilfoyle p.	0
shell ''Cloud Gate wa opening Millennium Park wa schedule	0
piece wa opening wa public sculpture state	0
plan wa re-erect tent sculpture public appreciation piece park official month	0
tent wa crew Ironworkers polished seam plate	0
order grind sand seam level side sculpture rope harness harder-to-reach area	0
side portion shell tent wa	0
omphalos wa worker polished section	0
weld ''Cloud Gate underwent five-stage process produce sculpture mirror-like finish	0
cost piece wa time park figure	0
public fund funding donation corporation	0
contract state piece survive year	0
registration article ''Cloud Gate day hand sculpture year liquid detergent	0
cleaning use solution cleaning use Tide	0
addition cleaning work endures periodic vandalism incident name letter tall northeast side sculpture	0