canal built Everglades harm ecosystem drain it.Robertson p. Napoleon Bonaparte majority campaign governor drainage create Empire Everglades .Douglas p. drainage place wa land developer tract acre town Davie region Dade county	2
canal water way field sugarcane.Douglas p. saw population boom demand land described author insanity .Grunwald p. Land wa home structure built case plan construction place	2
landowner eager investment home town land	2
Mangrove tree coast view shallow palm tree	2
Army Corps Engineers construction canal control water Everglades	2
Okeechobee rise fall region wa rain city planner battle water	2
Miami Okeechobee levee fail people south lake	2
year Okeechobee claimed life Okeechobee levee	2
Politicians Everglades four-story wall Herbert Hoover Dike wa built Okeechobee	2
wall cut water source Everglades.Grunwald p. wall construction drought cause wildfire	2
influx human detrimental effect plant animal region melaleuca tree ''Melaleuca quinquenervia help drainage pine brought developer windbreak	2
region timber wa lumber supply	2
Alligators bird frog fish scale	2
Entire rookery bird shot collect plume woman hat century.Tebeau p. ndash impact people region wa diversion water Everglades	2
Canals water level chaos food webs.Grunwald p. ndash Salt water water canal scientist salt water wa Aquifer water source	2
1940s freelance writer reporter ''The Miami Marjory Stoneman research Everglades assignment Miami River	2
land water year ''The Everglades River Grass area detail chapter disappearance	2
river grass sweet water meaning life uniqueness geography century man place wa gesture greed ignorance river fire	2
p. book ha copy publication dedication ecology conservation nickname Dame Everglades Grandmother Everglades anti-Christ singular focus expense interests.Davis	2
'Conservation Is Word Marjory Stoneman Transformation Environmentalism	2
History p. president organization Friends Everglades protest construction Cypress jetport	2
confrontation organization ha grown member preservation Everglades	2
spoke importance Everglades death age	2