''Rokeby Venus wa held Velázquez works.López-Rey quality Aureliano de Berueute ''Velázquez painting 1650s	0
wa found inventory collection Gaspar Méndez de Haro 7th Marquis Carpio Marquis Heliche title	0
Portús p. associate IV	0
Haro wa great-nephew Velázquez patron Count-Duke Olivares libertine	0
art historian Dawson Carr Haro painting woman Carr p. panegyrist taste lower-class woman youth	0
art historian Ángel Aterido painting Madrid art dealer painter Domingo Guerra Coronel wa Haro Coronel death year.Aterido pp	0
Coronel ownership painting raise number question Coronel possession Velázquez name wa Coronel inventory	0
art critic Javier Portús ha omission painting portrayal female nude type work wa dissemination wa .Portús p.	0
Velázquez painting technique offer assistance emphasis colour tone suggest work date mature period	0
estimate origin put completion 1640s 1650s Velázquez visit	0
case breadth dissolution form mark artist period	0
contrast work restraint subtlety culminate masterpiece ''Las Meninas .Gudiol p.	0
painting Haro collection daughter de Haro y Guzmán eighth Marchioness Carpio husband Álvarez de Toledo tenth vol	0
IV family sell painting work Manuel de Godoy favourite chief minister.MacLaren p.	0
hung masterpiece ''The Nude Maja ''The Maja	0
bear similarity Velázquez ''Venus Velázquez nude attempt provoke shame disgust climate 18th-century Spain.Schwarz	0
Pall Mall Press p.	0
ISBN 0-2690-2564-2 ''Venus wa brought wa £500 advice friend Morritt Buchanan art dealer kept agent G.A	0
Bray Carr p. MacLaren p. hung house Rokeby Park Yorkshire—thus painting name	0
painting wa Gallery Art Collections Fund triumph.The painting wa Velázquez work reintroduction public	0
critic Grieg wa Raphael found support idea—and wa discussion possibility Velázquez son-in-law pupil Juan del Mazo artist	0
MacLaren p. dismisses claim signature Juan Bautista Mazo Raphael Mengs bottom left corner accidental mark	0
VII painting £8,000 towards purchase Bray Carr p. Patron Fund thereafter.Smith Saumarez	0
Venus Velazquez Masterpiece Nation	0
Palace Same Raphael Madonna Pinks	0
''New Statesman Volume Issue p.	0