Ashes tour Macartney mdash clearance mdash Frith p. chance batting performance pre-war tour	8
match Leicestershire fast inning victory half time.Pollard p.	8
Surrey Services Oxford match start Tests belt	8
Macartney inning wa opener ten-wicket win Test	8
wa sixth Test win	8
pas county match Middlesex wicket tour	8
match tour wa reflection role specialist batsman post-war year	8
game Gloucestershire start vein run-scoring remainder	8
Macartney inning elegant strokeplay Pollard p. eight-wicket win Test hit century	8
Macartney hit Northamptonshire inning	8
match match Surrey Macartney injury	8
latter match Macartney drop host wicket ball match wa middle.Pollard p.	8
Macartney minute hit hour batting	8
wa dominance Macartney rest men Northamptonshire le days.Haigh p.	8
match Macartney Nottinghamshire Trent Bridge minute	8
Macartney start day crease dismissal Warren	8
chance Macartney philosophy wa signal wa day shine	8
century minute Macartney pavilion	8
Nottinghamshire captain Carr wa drink Macartney heavier bat wa attack	8
Macartney kept promise minute reach minute	8
time wa triple century first-class cricket term minute	8
stand inning time wa batsman day	8
inning Macartney Nip Pellew partnership	8
score won inning day margin first-class match.Pollard p.	8
cricket writer Sumner Reid described Macartney inning destructive inning saw	8
Trumper brilliant genius power masterful technique.Perry pp	8
space day Macartney month	8
Test Test century soil inning	8
wa sedate inning standard Pollard p. victory ndash series lead	8
Warwick men eighth Test win world record decade Indies cricket team	8
cricket writer Gideon wa army generation combat artillery tank sword horse p.	8
Macartney time month passing fifty inning match	8
wicket-taking drought match month success	8
form Warwickshire match Kent	8
Macartney drawn Fifth Test Oval head run-scoring series ndash	8
Macartney Gloucestershire inning victory Tests pas match tour	8
Macartney topped batting aggregate first-class matches.Pollard p.	8
Macartney effort summer Cricketers Year	8
''Wisden Macartney wa degree brilliant batsman present day	8
cricket writer Pollard described Macartney .Pollard p.	8
Macartney display Test Durban wa drawn host wicket hand	8
Test fitness reason Macartney Province	8
inning five-wicket inning half year	8
Test Cape Town Macartney inning chase	8
host agains spin Macartney	8
Australians secure ten-wicket victory	8
Macartney Test series wicket	8
Macartney ndash season five-wicket win MCC match summer	8
fifty season inning Victoria	8
Macartney wicket match season	8
Macartney wicket match state tour	8
Macartney struck form opening match	8
non-first-class match match Canterbury inning	8
match figure Wales Canterbury inning	8
Macartney match figure eight-wicket win	8
Macartney ndash Test series	8
played first-class match stage season wicket	8
withdrawal Macartney competition wa flare-up injury World breakdown	8
year Macartney full-time cricket ndash	8
Macartney help Rest defeat team	8
century Wales won Sheffield Shield match inning	8
performance ball wa inning victory arch-rivals Victoria	8
wicket batsman Bill Woodfull Bill Ponsford Ryder rounder Hunter Hendry played Tests	8
selection tour Macartney inning victory party Tasmania	8