Macartney flair wa Victor Trumper determination Don batsman history	8
style wa Trumper fascination Trumper-like supreme confidence	8
extent anyone era Almanack described Macartney triumph individualism model brilliant batsman history cricket	8
success wa eye hand foot co-ordination	8
Macartney wa man cm	8
batting attempt leg glance yorkers middle stump fine-leg wicket	8
wa team-mates candid criticism praise	8
life batsman explain longer cricket bear half-volleys bowler	8
Cardus wa chivalry cricket sort heroism	8
dauntlessness play brave beauty skill bring tear eye	8
1940s Macartney letter compiler ''Who information life	8
interest manner wicket game	8
sentiment Test batsman Fingleton cricket story G. Macartney	8
combative stylist Macartney élan Kent cricketer Hutchings dub	8
Fingleton inning Macartney strategy shot straight bowler head order rattle seize advantage	8
occasion century lunch day match bat change	8
heaviest bat batch team-mate brought hit	8
Leg Test team-mate Macartney hit Sydney Grade Cricket match	8
occasion wicket hit Macartney grin remark Was fun	8
cricket writer RC bowler Macartney ball fast pace left-arm orthodox spinner speed Derek Underwood	8
wa consistent length faster ball caught batsman guard	8
sticky wicket wa condition wicket inning time first-class career	8
wa attitude impression bowl ten maiden wicket meant	8
off-field activity wa careful money	8
tour hat shop tradition souvenir hat cricketer squad	8
style Macartney hat head life	8
Macartney obsession captain Warwick tour trip hoard manner team gifts.Haigh p.	8
team-mate Trumper Paddington suburb Sydney south shore Chatswood side harbour Macartney	8
Macartney Trumper played Gordon Cricket Club north shore friend	8
Macartney Trumper family backyard turf pitch	8
Trumper relocation frequent meeting Sydney Harbour Bridge wa way side bay wa ferry	8
Trumper wa crown prince age cricket stylish batsman era elegant strokemakers time	8
Trumper influence Macartney counterpart Australians proud play.Haigh p.	8
Macartney Trumper cricketer person wa pall bearer Trumper age	8
Trumper Macartney wa habit act ground umpire decision batsman	8
occasion Macartney felt umpire edge throw wicket wild shot	8
ball Trumper batting partner time luck occasion umpire incorrectly.Haigh p.	8