Coward wa born Teddington suburb	4
parent Sabin Coward piano salesman Violet Agnes Coward daughter Henry Gordon Veitch captain surveyor Royal Navy.Morley p. Noël Coward wa son eldest age six.Morley p. Coward father drive family finance	4
Coward wa bitten bug amateur concert age	4
Chapel Royal Choir School child	4
Coward ''Musicals Theatre TV Film mother sent dance academy Hoare p. Coward engagement wa Prince Mussel child play ''The	4
Theatre ''The Times p. ''Present volume memoir Coward actor-manager Coward deal theatre cast child play Rainbow Ends	4
Coward played piece Theatre End.Hoare pp	4
Theatre ''The Times p. Coward Savoy Theatre ''An Autumn Idyll dancer ballet Coliseum ''A Fowl Harold Owen	4
Savoy Theatre ''The Times p. Coliseum p. Varieties etc p. Italia Conti Coward Liverpool Repertory Theatre year wa cast ''Peter Pan	4
Cult Pan ''The Times p. ''Peter Pan year wa Rainbow Ends	4
Fairies ''The Times p. child actor period Hermione Gingold mother turn naughty boy Castle p. Fabia Esmé Wynne play Micheál MacLíammóir Gertrude Coward memoir orange told dirty story onwards	4
''The Times p. Coward wa protégé lover Streatfeild society painter.Hoare pp	4
Streatfeild Mrs Cooper society friends.Evangeline Julia Marshall society hostess Clement Paston Cooper grandson Paston Cooper	4
Hall brother Walter Marshall d. talent world painter Streatfeild conductor Malcolm Sargent writer Scott Moncrieff Coward	4
Peerage Hall website Streatfeild tuberculosis Mrs Cooper encourage friend protégé frequent guest estate Hall.Hoare pp	4
Coward perform World Prince Wales Theatre ''The tour Amy Brandon company ''Charley Aunt	4
Coward memoir part wa wa kindness care direction	4
endless trouble taught week point comedy use day	4
Coward ''Present p. Coward wa Artists Rifles wa unfit service tubercular tendency wa health ground months.Lesley pp	4
year W. Griffith film ''Hearts World role	4
story magazine help family	4
play ''Ida Collaborates ''Women Whisky friend Esmé Wynne	4
''The Noel Coward Society noelcoward.net solo effort playwright wa ''The Rat Trap wa Everyman Theatre Hampstead	4
Theatre year met McNaughtan name Loraine secretary capacity forty year death	4