Coward play war match popularity pre-war hits.Lahr p. Values address culture clash family actress matrimonial ambition ''South comedy set colony ''Quadrille drama love elopement ''Nude Violin Gielgud Coward satire art.Lesley pp	4
revue ''Sigh wa moderate success p. ''Pacific Seas romance ''Ace Clubs set night club failures.Lesley pp	4
addition friend Cochran Gertrude	4
disappointment period Coward public profile performance Magnus ''The Cart Coronation season co-starring coverage press Haymarket Theatre ''The Times p. Ivor	4
Royal Ancient ''The Manchester p. cabaret act wartime tour troop wa supreme success Café de pp	4
theatre critic Tynan Coward cabaret act Vegas gramophone CD – DRG wa write series television season	4
Coward Martin number Vegas act.Kenrick	4
Coward ''Musicals Theatre TV Film wa production ''Blithe Spirit Claudette Colbert Lauren Bacall Natwick ''This Breed Edna Roger Moore	4
excellent review audience figure moderate.Payne pp	4
1950s Coward write play	4
''After Ball adaptation Fan wa End	4
''Sail set luxury cruise liner wa Coward post-war production pp	4
''The Girl Came Supper adaptation ''The Prince ran months.Lesley p.	4
adaptation ''Blithe Spirit ''High Spirits	4
Coward play include farce ''Look Lulu	4
study age Wings disdain .Simon	4
''The NY Magazine Coward primary purpose play wa entertain attempt modernism felt wa boring audience critic	4
novel ''Pomp Circumstance life colony met success.Payne pp	4
Coward stage success ''Suite Keys trilogy set hotel penthouse suite	4
swan song stage actor act fold	4
Coward ''Plays introduction page	4
trilogy review box office business UK.Morley p. play ''A Song Twilight Coward reticence subject played character	4
Noel Coward Skeleton Feast ''The Times p. star trilogy wa ill travel	4
''Suite Keys play title ''Noël Coward Keys Hume Cronyn.Hoare p. Coward won popularity film career ''Around World Days ''Our Man ''Bunny ''Boom	4
''The Job .Hoare pp	4
Stage film opportunity 1950s invitation compose version ''Pygmalion year ''My Fair Lady wa offer role king stage production ''The Colonel Nicholson film ''The Bridge River .Hoare pp	4
play title role film ''Dr	4
p. year role Humbert Humbert ''Lolita time life film story heroine wa sweet lady	4
Richards p. mid-1960s 1970s production play revue music ''Oh Coward	4
''Cowardy Custard Coward popularity reputation	4
dubbed comeback Dad Renaissance .Hoare p. ''et seq	4
hit revival ''Private Lives York.Morley pp	4
''Hay Fever Edith Evans Theatre Theatre perceptiveness choose play mine cast play telephone directory	4
p. example Dad Renaissance production ''Private Lives Theatre de Lys Elaine Stritch von Furstenberg	4
cast Coward popularity risen theatre poster production Al Hirschfeld caricature Coward caricature wa connection Coward work example album ballet suite LP DRG SL Hirschfeld cover image production star	4
illustration capture Coward image 1960s wa longer smooth sophisticate doyen theatre	4
''The Statesman thought landmark Sixties include emergence Noël Coward man drama	4
wa morning verbal tiddlywinks reporter Dad Renaissance wa beside Forster T. Eliot OMs living playwright	4
''The Statesman Hoare p. ''Time magazine '60s work inconsequentiality exert period charm charm period	4