group radio station market Cincinnati confederation Quality Network	5
year group station System.All source concur MBS cofounder WOR–Newark N.J./New WLW–Cincinnati member Quality Network	5
Sources differ MBS member station WLS AM city Quality Network	5
addition consensus matter degree connection source claim Quality Network exist end others name structure	5
scholar Schwoch put origin System murky dispute	5
claim Schwoch sentence permanent establishment network bound popularity radio program 'The Lone Ranger —is scholar	5
station WOR–Newark Bamberger division R.H. Macy Company WGN subsidiary ''Chicago Tribune WLW–Cincinnati Crosley Radio Company	5
network wa member telephone-line transmission facility enter contract advertiser networked show	5
WOR WGN market bulk leader group	5
System wa Bamberger WGN percent stock—five ten shares.Robinson Cox discussion network history organization historian Elizabeth McLeod	5
Note lead content webpage McLeod network date newspaper article bottom page	5
newspaper article state network commentator Pearson	5
article suggests ''The Lone Ranger rode radio sunset network	5
radio network operation—the System Company wa network affiliate	5
contrast System wa cooperative venture group member	5
majority WOR WGN feature	5
WOR ''The Witch Tale horror anthology series hunner-an'-thirteen-year-old narrator listener douse light	5
draw fire gaze ember ''gaaaaze 'em deep	5
ye sea th jungle land hear chantin savage drum	5
WGN comedy series ''Lum Abner	5
WXYZ ''The Lone Ranger wa demand	5
claimed MBS wa vehicle ''Lum Abner wa le time.For argument MBS wa vehicle ''The Lone Ranger e.g. Olson Head Schwoch	5
counterargument popularity ''Lum Abner e.g. Hilmes Hollis correspondence historian Elizabeth McLeod Mon APR	5
WLW brought wa sheer power billing Nation Station night broadcasting watt ten time clear-channel standard.Whitaker	5
network event—the first-ever night baseball game Cincinnati Reds Phillies.Gorman et al	5
WXYZ join obligation kept ''The Lone Ranger time week spring Age part ''Jerry Haendiges Vintage Radio Logs website	5
hole market wa CKLW Windsor Ontario river M	5
Note article data mention WXYZ history	5
network broadcaster baseball World Series airtime responsibility WGN Bob Elson Quin Ryan WLW series year Fall air network .Alexander Gorman et al	5
broadcast Notre Dame football game autumn relationship decades.See e.g. Patterson	5
income-generating business network wa endeavor start month cooperative advertising M	5