limit location settlement Wales Limestone Plains settlement settler settler origins.Wigmore pp	3
land grant area wa Moore Gillespie p. settlement area construction homestead peninsula stockman	3
Moore site property ''Canberry ''Canberra p. site	3
km² claim future North Canberra	3
boundary Moore claim wa land behalf Campbell wa p.	3
Palmer wa land region wa son Palmer pp	3
''Palmerville Ginninderra Creek Squire wa	3
Ginninderra Village wa site school	3
region school Duntroon adjacent St Church	3
St wa Canberra church wa use p. p.	3
region ten kilometre south Molonglo River today Tuggeranong Plains wa Murdoch p.	3
Waniassa Homestead Tuggeranong Homestead wa McQuoid building Lanyon estate Lanyon built pp	3
Tharwa wa homestead area wa ''Cuppacumbalong wa p.	3
Tharwa official settlement Capital Territory p.	3
south area part Namadgi Park	3
''Naas station Naas river valley built	3
Cotter Cotter River association	3
Gudgenby wa 1840s Gudgenby Homestead wa built time	3
Convict labour wa region bushrangers region runaway convict	3
Tennant wa bushranger region hideout mountain Tharwa Mt Tennant	3
homestead stock food possession arrest p.	3
wa hung crime Sydney	3
lawlessness region appointment resident magistrate	3
magistrate oversaw matter liquor license establishment wa Oaks	3
influx population activity 1850s goldrushes rush	3
gold rush saw establishment communication Sydney region way Cobb coach mail passengers.Wigmore p.	3
post office Ginninderra Lanyon pp	3
Bushranger activity gold rush bushrangers Hall Clarke brother area mail coach gold shipments.Gillespie pp	3
Terence Murray wa born Ireland Sydney family p.	3
property ''Yarralumla area.Fitzgerald p.	3
Land Acts Settlement Acts mechanism land tenure brought break-up property Wales	3
change land tenure focus region grazing agriculture	3
colonial time present-day Canberra wa community name Ginninderra Molonglo Tuggeranong	3
region wa Queanbeyan/Yass district town proximity Canberra	3
village Ginninderra Tharwa developed service community	3
allotment village Hall pastoralist Henry Hall	3
wa town store hotel coachbuilder blacksmith butcher shoemaker saddler dairy.Gillespie pp	3
agronomist Farrer research farm 'Lambrigg bank Murrumbidgee River south present-day Tuggeranong	3
Farrer rust wheat variety wheat grower wa wheat producer.Wigmore p. pp	3
Tharwa Bridge bridge region wa wa bridge Murrumbidgee River.Gillespie pp	3
region control population grown Bureau Statistics	3