Francis Bacon relationship Dyer men temperament artist presence	0
Lacy lover tear artist painting beat drunken rage street half-conscious.Heaney Joe	0
Bacon met Dyer claimed caught man home.Akbar Arifa	0
Dyer wa thirty year grown East End family crime	0
spent life theft juvenile detention center jail	0
Bacon taste men Dyer wa fit masculine	0
Bacon wa Dyer vulnerability nature	0
Dyer wa Bacon self-confidence success Bacon protector father figure insecure man.Peppiatt p.	0
Dyer wa Bacon borderline care appearance	0
chain-smoker Dyer hangover drinking	0
compact build docile personality art critic Peppiatt described air man land decisive punch	0
behaviour affair Bacon wa Dyer money stay le drunk	0
Bacon work extreme subject matter painting portrait friend mid-1960s Dyer presence artist work.Harrison Martin	0
Bacon treatment lover canvass emphasis subject physicality tender	0
artist friend portrayed period Dyer feel effigy	0
painting stature ''raison d'etre meaning Bacon described Dyer brief interlude life death .Peppiatt p.	0
critic Dyer portrait favourite Michel	0
Dyer novelty Bacon circle man bitter ill ease	0
Dyer attention painting brought pretend understand	0
money fink choked pride.Peppiatt p.	0
Bacon money Dyer attract hanger-on accompany bender Soho	0
Withdrawn sober Dyer wa drunk attempt pull Bacon buying round dinner circle	0
Dyer behaviour wore thin—with crony Bacon Bacon friend	0
Bacon associate Dyer nuisance—an intrusion world culture ''their Bacon belonged.Peppiatt p.	0
wa drinking wa contact lover	0
Dyer Bacon opening artist retrospective ''Grand Palais	0
show wa point Bacon career date wa described living painter	0
Dyer wa desperate man wa attend wa wa sense picture	0
draw Bacon attention cannabis Bacon police Norton	0
''Sunday suicide number occasion	0
eve exhibition Bacon Dyer hotel room Bacon spent day people eager meet	0
mid-evening wa Dyer overdose barbiturate wa	0
Bacon retrospective displayed power self-control u aspire	0
Bacon wa deeply loss Dyer friend nanny	0
point death life work.Russell p.	0
stoic appearance time wa broken	0
express critic friend daemon disaster loss version Eumenides.Russell p.	0
Bacon spent remainder stay activity arrangement	0
week comfort Dyer family	0
affair Dyer friend East-End broke tear	0
coffin wa grave attendant bloody fool	0
Bacon stoic month Dyer imagination	0
confront loss number tribute canvass Black Triptych masterpieces.Peppiatt p.	0