Holes wall Texians fire	9
reach barrack Texians west wall west Antonio River	9
cavalry Texians cover ditch	9
Sesma wa send reinforcement Texians	9
Sesma skirmish Texians Edmondson belief number wa inflated.Edmondson p.	9
weapon band Texians wall church foot east prairie	9
cavalry group Dickinson artillery crew cannon cavalry casualty	9
group remain Crockett men wall front church	9
reload rifle club fought knife	9
volley fire wave bayonet Texians group church	9
army outer wall interior Alamo compound church room east west walls.Edmondson p.	9
soldier attention flag roof building	9
Mexicans flag wa location.Lieutenant José Maria Torres flag wa process	9
hour army secure control p.	9
defender barrack rooms.Edmondson p.	9
confusion Texians spike cannon	9
door wa blown soldier fire volley musket dark room charge hand-to-hand combat	9
Too sick battle Bowie bed	9
Eyewitnesses battle account death	9
witness saw soldier enter Bowie room bayonet carry room.Groneman p.	9
Others claimed Bowie shot wa soldier lift head.Hopewell p.	9
historian Wallace Chariton accurate Chariton p. version Bowie cot wall pistol knife	9
Texians die men twelve-pounder cannon chapel.Petite p.	9
shot eighteen-pounder cannon destroyed barricade front church soldier building musket volley	9
Dickinson crew cannon apse soldier door	9
time reload Texians Dickinson Gregorio Esparza grabbed rifle death.Edmondson p.	9
Evans master ordnance tasked gunpowder hand	9
towards powder magazine wa musket ball torch inch powder	9
blast destroyed church woman child hiding sacristy.Tinkle p.	9
soldier sacristy son defender Anthony Wolf stood pull blanket shoulder	9
dark soldier mistook adult Edmondson Wolf ran room grabbed son child cannon ramp rear church musket shot ground	9
die battle wa Jacob Walker Tinkle p. hide Susannah Dickinson wa front women.Lord p.	9
Brigido Guerrero sought refuge sacristy	9
Guerrero Army wa convincing soldier wa prisoner.Edmondson p. p. ndash	9
a.m. battle Alamo wa	9
soldier corpse bayoneting body	9
Texians soldier shoot confusion	9
violence bugler sound retreat	9
minute soldier fire bodies.Tinkle p.	9