islet Gavutu Tanambogo seaplane base naval personnel Yokohama Kure Naval Force laborer 14th Construction Unit.Frank p. p.	9
14th Construction Unit wa Hashimoto Hara Construction Forces	9
islet mound meter ft causeway	9
hill Gavutu Tanambogo Hills Americans height feet.Christ p. p.	9
islet bunker cave hills.Christ p. Griffith p.	9
islet supportive wa machine gun range	9
US islet naval troop construction workers.Zimmerman p. Christ p.	9
Gavutu wa Marine Parachute Battalion men	9
assault wa noon aircraft provide air cover Tulagi Gavutu time.Christ p.	9
naval bombardment seaplane ramp naval craft land Marines location beach dock	9
machine gun fire casualty ten Marines inland attempt crossfire islets.Christ p. p.	9
Marines deploy machine gun provide fire Gavutu cave Marines push inland area	9
Captain Stallings battalion operation officer Marines begin suppressive fire machine gun mortar machine gun emplacement Tanambogo	9
dive bomber bomb Tanambogo volume fire location.Christ p.	9
Stallings command battalion commander stress executive officer Williams wa	9
hour Marines climbed Hill	9
top Marines clearing position hill charge grenade hand-to-hand combat.Christ p. Griffith p. p.	9
top hill Marines put suppressive fire Tanambogo.Christ p.	9
Marine battalion commander Gavutu radioed Rupertus request reinforcement assault Tanambogo.Jersey p. Zimmerman p.	9
battalion commander condition request reinforcement Christ p.	9
defender Tanambogo aircrew maintenance personnel Yokohama	9
Rupertus company Marines Battalion Marine Regiment Island assist Tanambogo spite advice staff company wa	9
Tanambogo wa company assault Tanambogo dark	9
fire naval bombardment islet craft Marines hit fire shore boatcrews boat	9
position wa Marine company commander boat depart marine dozen men causeway cover Gavutu	9
Tanambogo day fighting.Christ p. p. p.	9
Parachute Battalion men day	9
night attack marine Gavutu concealment thunderstorm Vandegrift send reinforcement assist assault Tanambogo	9
Battalion Marines ship wa prepare assault Tanambogo p.	9
wa command Lieutenant Colonel Leroy P. Christ p.	9
Battalion Gavutu defense islet wa p. Christ p.	9
Marines Gavutu fire attack	9
preparation assault carrier dive bomber naval gunfire bombardment	9
carrier aircraft bomb Marines Gavutu carrier aircraft support wa	9
''San Juan shell correct island Tanambogo minute	9
Marine assault craft causeway assistance marine Stuart light tank headway defense	9
tank stuck stump infantry support wa mob airman	9
set fire tank crew beat crewmembers Marine rifle fire	9
Marines body burned-out hulk tank corps Yokohama executive officer seaplane pilot	9
survivor attack tank recall officer Lieutenant Commander Saburo top tank	9
wa time saw .Christ p. p. p. Lundstrom p. Gilbert p.	9
Lieutenant Sweeney tank platoon commander wa tank assault stood tank turret	9
Lundstrom state Miyazaki wa attack tank state Miyazaki wa area time war	9
day Marines cave p. Lundstrom p.	9
attack night hand hand engagement	9
noon resistance Tanambogo ended.Zimmerman p.	9
battle Gavutu Tanambogo defender Marines naval personnel	9
prisoner battle combatant laborer belonging construction unit.Frank p. p. Christ p.	9