Montgomery Shoshone Mine mill south Montgomery Mountain rail spur line mine	2
Cross found gold south side southwestern Nevada hill Bullfrog Mountain.Lingenfelter p. Assays ore sample site value ton Lingenfelter p. ton dollar inflation	2
Word discovery spread Tonopah thousand hopeful prospector speculator Bullfrog Mining District.Lingenfelter pp	2
ndash district gold rush settlement arose mine Rhyolite largest.Lingenfelter p. sprang promising discovery Montgomery Shoshone Mine ore assayed ton Lingenfelter p. equivalent ton	2
two-man camp Rhyolite town people week population	2
saloon table crib prostitution house restaurant half dozen barber public bath house newspaper ''Rhyolite	2
stage coach Goldfield north Rhyolite	2
auto line people Rhyolite Goldfield rail station Vegas Pope-Toledos Steamers car	2
Schwab portrait Montgomery Shoshone Mine	2
Alexander Bob Montgomery owner partner mine industrialist Schwab p. Schwab operation scale worker opening tunnel drift building mill process ore	2
water piped paid line hydroelectric plant foot Sierras Rhyolite Vegas Tonopah Railroad spur line mine.Lingenfelter p. railroad Rhyolite	2
wa Vegas Tonopah Railroad LVTR train city pp	2
ndash depot built California-mission style cost equivalent	2
Bullfrog Goldfield Railroad BGR service north	2
Tonopah Tidewater Railroad TTR service Rhyolite track BGR	2
TTR wa built reach borax-bearing colemanite bed Death gold field	2
people Rhyolite Lingenfelter ''Death Amargosa Land Illusion	2
Elliott cite population ndash ''Nevada Twentieth-Century Mining Boom accurate population figure boom	2
Patera ''Rhyolite Boom Years state estimate peak population town claimed newspaper .Patera p. newspaper people Bullfrog mining district town Rhyolite Bullfrog Gold Beatty camp mine	2
Rhyolite concrete sidewalk light water telephone telegraph line newspaper magazine police fire department hospital school train station railway depot bank stock exchange opera house church building	2
prominent wa three-story Cook	2
cost Lingenfelter p. equivalent	2
cost marble stair stained-glass window luxury	2
building brokerage office post office bank	2
building train depot three-story Overbury Block two-story eight-room school	2
miner T. built Bottle beer liquor bottle	2
building Rhyolite Mining Stock member broker city	2
storefront share Bullfrog company number company mining district	2
Sixty thousand share hand day end week number topped	2