debut album band protopunk record	6
group crude raw critic Lester Bangs Stone song primitive two-chord structure	6
heard Seeds Cheer Question Mark Mysterians Kingsmen	6
difference hype thick overlay teenage-revolution total-energy-thing conceals scrapyard vista clichés noise	6
sound lyric song Troggs group sex-and-raw-sound image couple year	6
review Lester Bangs Stone	6
Stooges Ann Arbor album	6
critic Greil Marcus band singer Iggy Pop sound Chuck Airmobile—after thief part .Marcus p.	6
album wa Cale member experimental rock group Velvet	6
reputation underground rock band VU creation punk rock.Taylor p.	6
1970s Dolls wildness 1950s rock 'n roll fashion glam punk.Harrington p.	6
duo Suicide played spare experimental music confrontational stage act Stooges	6
Coventry club borough Queens Dictators rock vehicle wise-ass attitude humor.Bessman pp	6
Lovers Velvet devotee Jonathan Richman attention style	6
garage rock scene coalesce Rathskeller club Kenmore Square	6
act Kids Lover Felice Alexander Boom Boom Band frontman member Velvet month Mickey Jenkins p.	6
band Death—made blast arrange release deal	6
Ohio underground rock scene Devo Kent Cleveland Eels Mirrors Rocket Tombs	6
Rocket Tombs split Ubu Frankenstein	6
Eels Mirrors broke Styrenes fallout.Klimek Jamie ''Jilmar Jäger Rolf ''Rent Dog	6
Deviants 1960s played range psychedelic style satiric edge penchant spectacle Sex Pistols decade	6
act Fairies vein.Unterberger pp	6
Ziggy Stardust persona Bowie artifice exaggeration central—elements picked Pistols punk pp	6
Doctors Madness built Bowie presentation concept direction become punk	6
Bands pub rock scene music R rock 'n roll	6
scene top act Feelgood wa way others Stranglers Cock Sparrer play role punk explosion	6
pub rock band year wa 101'ers lead singer adopt name Joe Strummer.Robb p.	6
Bands movement afield Düsseldorf punk punk band NEU	6
anti-establishment Zunō Brain Police garage psych folk	6
combo censorship challenge act onstage masturbation.Anderson p.	6
generation garage rock band Stooges MC5 wa closer sound punk Brisbane Saints raw sound Things tour p.	6
Radio expatriate Deniz Tek wa gig Sydney	6