Nirvana alternative rock artist influence punk rock act	6
Nirvana success record company saw punk band profitable.Zuel ''Sydney	6
year ''Dookie hit album years.See e.g. RIAA	6
Bad Religion ''Stranger Than Fiction wa gold.Fucoco	6
punk band indie label Epitaph Bad Religion guitarist Gurewitz mainstream success	6
Epitaph put ''Let Rancid ''Punk Drublic NOFX ''Smash gold	6
''Smash sell copy best-selling independent-label album time	6
MTV radio station played role band crossover success NOFX MTV air videos.Gold Jonathan	6
Year Punk Broke. ” ''SPIN	6
''Dookie sale way host North pop punk band decade.D'Angelo Joe MTV.com	6
Vans Tour mall chain store Topic brought punk mainstream	6
lead Mighty Mighty Bosstones band Operation Ivy Beach Sublime ska punk ska-core mid-1990s	6
Tone band punk rock wave music wa closer roots— ska rpm .Hebdige p.	6
Ska punk band wave ska fusion genre	6
Wolves album Operation Ivy—became record ska revival gold Wolves wa gold	6
''Let Rancid album gold certification	6
Sublime album wa platinum	6
punk revival Gross p.	6
Pop punk band Blink-182 release ''Enema State ''Billboard top ten copy le year	6
pop punk band Sum Simple Plan Yellowcard Charlotte sale decade	6
Idiot number UK chart	6
Jimmy Eat World emo pop punk direction Pierce Carrie ''The Battalion	6
album style Fall hit number ''Infinity	6
revival wa AFI root hardcore skate punk success Sorrow topped chart ''Decemberunderground	6
Alkaline Trio successive top-thirty album number ''Agony Irony	6
Ska punk group Reel Fish Than Jake attract fan	6
punk band Dropkick Murphys sound Oi	6
punk rock tradition wa group Frenzal Rhomb End Bodyjar	6
punk rock visibility concern punk community music wa mainstream	6
signing label MTV punk band buying system punk wa challenge.Myers p.	6
controversy part punk culture Clash wa signing Records.Knowles p.	6
effect commercialization music wa issue	6
scholar Haenfler punk fan 'despise punk rock band Sum Blink .Haenfler p.	6
punk rock wa culture punk market band rebel	6
Marketers style hipness punk rock extent ad campaign automobile Subaru Impreza claimed car wa punk rock .Klein p.	6