Between Marine engineer footbridge Matanikau	9
Marine Army artillery battery gun warship ''San ''Helena ''Sterrett fire west bank Matanikau aircraft B-17 bomber bomb area	9
time Battalion 5th Marine Regiment Matanikau mouth Battalion 5th Marines river inland	9
Marines wa Battalion Infantry Masao Tamura.Shaw p. Griffith ''Battle p. ''Pearl Harbor p. Zimmerman Campaign p. p. Hammel p.	9
resistance ridge south Point Cruz afternoon	9
coast Point Cruz 7th Company Tamura battalion advance	9
hour Company casualty loss officer wa driven towards Matanikau Tamura troop	9
company company Battalion 5th Marines resistance Marine Anthony Casamento others Americans retreat.Zimmerman Campaign p. Hammel p. p. Griffith ''Battle p. ''Pearl Harbor p. p.	9
situation end day Edson Colonel Lieutenant Colonel Merrill Vandegrift staff try encircle defender Point Cruz	9
continue press coast day north envelop adversary west south Point Cruz	9
Tamura battalion loss day Tamura 7th 5th Companies left soldier respectively.Griffith ''Battle p. p.	9
troop verge defense Hyakutake 17th Army headquarters sent troop found on-hand bolster Infantry defensive effort	9
troop Anti-Tank Gun Battalion gun Field Road Construction Unit	9
unit position emplacement south west Point Cruz.Frank p.	9
morning flank men north coast west Point Cruz encirclement defender	9
defense draw coastal trail beach west Point Cruz earth log bunker cave foxhole	9
artillery position day number casualty defenders.Zimmerman Campaign p. Griffith ''Battle p. ''Pearl Harbor p. p.	9
day Company frontal assault bayonet portion defense defender	9
time battalion Marine Regiment past Point Cruz ''Pearl Harbor p. p. Griffith ''Battle p. Zimmerman Campaign p.	9
troop break pocket beaten Marines	9
Between noon Marine company arm mortar demolition charge indirect artillery fire destruction pocket Point Cruz	9
Marine participant A. Nash described battle Marines anti-tank gun mm field artillery piece machineguns body soldier officers.Hammel p. Griffith ''Battle p. p. Zimmerman Campaign p. ''Pearl Harbor p. p.	9
time Marines push coast point west Point Cruz nightfall	9
troop left area oppose Marines advance soldier Infantry frail survivor unit Tenaru Edson Ridge battle naval troop garrison	9
prevent Americans village cut-off retreat Infantry Division threaten rear-area support headquarters unit force	9
Nakaguma despair regimental color death charge force wa officer 17th Army staff.Griffith ''Battle p. p.	9
Marine unit Point east Lunga Perimeter troop Express mission destroyer	9
knowledge body troop wa process Point defeat Field battle Americans conduct attack Lunga Perimeter Point area.Frank p. p. Hammel p. ''Pearl Harbor p. Griffith ''Battle p.	9
discus development Marine leader met morning	9
Edson Vandegrift abandonment shift force counter Point threat	9
day 5th Marines group Lunga Point	9
Marine Battalions Battalion 164th Infantry position west Point Cruz plan hold location	9
route retreat Sendai Division survivor reach day	9
time Nakaguma wa artillery shell.Anderson ''Pearl Harbor p. Griffith ''Battle p. p. Hammel p. p.	9