Between troop Hyakutake troop employ	9
loss position east side Matanikau attack defense coast	9
Hyakutake thrust attack south Field	9
Division troop Infantry Division Lieutenant Masao Maruyama soldier infantry regiment battalion wa march jungle attack defence south east bank Lunga River.Shaw p. Rottman Army p.	9
distract Americans attack south Hyakutake artillery battalion infantry men 124th Infantry Regiments command Tadashi Sumiyoshi attack defense west coastal corridor.Rottman Army p. p. ''Pearl Harbor p. Griffith ''Battle p. Dull p. Morison ''Struggle p.	9
troop time Sendai Infantry Division battalion Infantry Division artillery tank engineer support unit	9
force Battalion 124th Infantry Regiment wa part Infantry Brigade Edson Ridge	9
Sumiyoshi force battalion Infantry Regiment Colonel Nomasu Nakaguma attack Marine defense mouth Matanikau	9
Marine artillery cannon arm fire assault soldier light casualty themselves.Hough ''Pearl Harbor p. p. Rottman Army p. Griffith ''Battle p. p.	9
night Maruyama force frontal assault portion Lunga perimeter	9
Maruyama troop attack Americans killed.Hough ''Pearl Harbor p. p. Griffith ''Battle p. p. ''Cactus Force p. Lundstrom Campaign p.	9
attack Matanikau Oka 124th Infantry Regiment loss	9
Hyakutake attack force retreat	9
half Maruyama survivor retreat area west Matanikau River rest Infantry Regiment Colonel Toshinari Shoji wa told head Point east Lunga perimeter	9
Infantry Regiment position west Matanikau Point Cruz area 124th Infantry Regiment position slope Mount Matanikau Valley.Frank Zimmerman Campaign p. Griffith ''Battle p. ''Pearl Harbor p. Rottman Army p.	9
order exploit victory Vandegrift west Matanikau objective drive artillery range Field cut retreat Maruyama men towards village location 17th Army headquarters	9
Vandegrift battalion 5th Marine Regiment Colonel Merritt Edson Battalion 7th Marine Regiment Colonel	9
battalion Marine Regiment reserve	9
wa artillery Marine Regiment 164th Infantry Regiment CAF aircraft gunfire warship	9
Edson wa command ''Pearl Harbor p. Hammel p. Griffith ''Battle p. p. Anderson p. Zimmerman Campaign p.	9
Matanikau area 124th Infantry Regiments	9
Nakaguma Infantry Matanikau shore inland Oka 124th Infantry line inland river	9
regiment paper battalion understrength battle damage disease malnutrition	9
fact Oka described command half strength	9