force States Fleet Harbor Hawaii	9
attack battleship fleet state war nation	9
goal leader neutralize seize possession resource base defend empire Asia	9
goal force Philippines Thailand Malaya Dutch East Indies Island Gilbert Islands Guam	9
war rest power Great Netherlands Japan.Murray p.	9
attempt maintain initiative extend defensive perimeter south naval battle Midway	9
Midway wa Allies victory capability carrier force	9
point Allies defensive victory opportunity seize initiative Japan.Murray p.	9
Allies chose Solomon Islands protectorate Great Solomon Islands Tulagi target.Loxton p.	9
IJN Tulagi seaplane base	9
concern IJN airfield Lunga Point	9
naval troop Tulagi island personnel construction specialist	9
base protect base Rabaul threaten supply communication line area Fiji Caledonia Samoa Operation FS	9
deploy fighter bomber airfield wa	9
aircraft provide air cover naval force farther Pacific.Alexander p. p. p. p. Lundstrom p. p.	9
plan invade Solomons wa Commander Chief States Fleet	9
deny use island base threaten supply route States use point	9
Roosevelt tacit consent invasion	9
Army Marshall line action command operation Marines carry operation Chester Nimitz proceed planning	9
won argument invasion backing Chiefs	9
conjunction Guinea MacArthur capture Admiralty Islands Bismarck base Rabaul	9
goal wa reconquest Philippines.Morison p. p. ''Cartwheel p.	9
Chiefs Staff theater command Solomons	9
Chester Nimitz Harbor wa commander chief forces.Murray p. p. Lundstrom p.	9
preparation future Marine Alexander Vandegrift wa move Marine Division States	9
land naval air force unit sent base Fiji Samoa Hebrides Caledonia.Loxton p. p.	9
Espiritu Santo Hebrides wa headquarters base ''Operation commencement date set	9
wa Tulagi Cruz Islands	9
reconnaissance airfield construction effort capture wa plan Cruz operation wa dropped.Frank p.	9
signal intelligence movement asset area Allies Port Moresby p.	9
force warship transport vessel Fiji rehearsal p. McGee p.	9
on-scene commander force wa Fletcher flag aircraft carrier USS ''Saratoga	9
force wa Richmond Turner	9
Vandegrift Marine infantry landings.Frank p.	9