Bad weather force vicinity morning p. pp	9
patrol aircraft Tulagi area invasion convoy wa ship storm cloud	9
force split group group Tulagi islands.Frank p. p.	9
force Task Force cruiser light cruiser destroyer transport cargo ship destroyer transport minesweeper	9
warship invasion beach carrier aircraft bombed position target island destroyed seaplane base Tulagi.Hammel p. Lundstrom p.	9
Tulagi island Gavutu Tanambogo Marines.Frank p.	9
IJN personnel naval seaplane base island Marine attacks.Frank p.	9
IJN personnel construction specialist combat troop	9
difficulty Marines island Tulagi Gavutu Tanambogo p. McGee p.	9
defender man Marines killed.Frank p.	9
personnel Island found Marine patrol month	9
contrast Tulagi Gavutu Tanambogo le resistance	9
Vandegrift Marines ashore Point Lunga Point	9
towards Lunga Point resistance rain forest night Lunga Point airfield	9
day resistance Marines way Lunga River airfield	9
naval construction unit combat troop command Captain panicked warship bombardment bombing airfield area west Matanikau River Point Cruz area food supply construction equipment vehicle dead.Jersey p. Morison p. p.	9
operation naval aircraft Rabaul command Sadayoshi Yamada force time afire transport ''George Elliot sank day destroyer USS ''Jarvis .Loxton p.	9
air attack day aircraft combat accident carrier fighters.Frank p.	9
clash Fletcher wa loss carrier fighter aircraft strength threat carrier air attack ship fuel level	9
Fletcher withdrew Solomon Islands area carrier task force p. p.	9
p. Morison p. contend Fletcher fuel situation wa Fletcher wa order provide justification withdrawal battle area	9
result loss air cover Turner withdraw ship le half supply equipment troop ashore unloaded.Hammel p.	9
Turner unload supply Tulagi night depart ship p.	9
night transport group warship command Victor Crutchley force cruiser destroyer Fleet Rabaul Mikawa	9
cruiser sunk cruiser destroyer Savo Island	9
Mikawa wa unaware Fletcher withdrawn carrier Rabaul attack transport	9
Mikawa wa daylight carrier air attack area	9
Turner withdrew naval force Marines ashore equipment provision troop aboard transport	9
Mikawa decision attack transport ship opportunity prove mistake.Morison p.	9