photograph men uniform wooden chair table living room	9
man head table left	9
men table side towards fireplace room wall	9
man head table right left leg right	9
right-hand side table dark ashtray spoon glass left centre table assortment plate coffee cup dish bowl fruit	9
man left ha hand palm camera finger hand left image	9
Mölders wa ''Major command Fighter JG ''Generalmajor Theo Osterkamp day.Aders p.	9
Mölders flew combat sortie JG Supermarine Spitfire flown Officer	9
mission legend Mölders wa hit dogfight Dover ace Sailor Malan splinter wound leg knee left foot	9
''Oberleutnant Leppla shot Spitfire Mölders wa emergency France.Aders p63Kaplan p.	9
Recent research suggests Mölders wa combat Flight Lieutenant J.L	9
Webster mdash wa action mdash Spitfire Squadron.Obermaier p. 19.Shores Williams p.	9
wound kept Mölders month	9
''Generalmajor Osterkamp briefly Geschwader Mölders convalescence	9
Mölders ''Geschwader clearance combat Operation Eagle Attack code name ''Adlertag	9
Adolf Hitler Führer Directive	9
objective wa engage defeat Royal Force RAF achieve air superiority preparation Operation Sealion ''Unternehmen Seelöwe invasion Great Britain.Aders p.	9
Mölders status flew combat mission	9
aide wingman ''Oberleutnant wa shot prisoner war mission ''Oberleutnant Georg Claus place.Aders p.	9
Mölders claimed Hurricanes wa ''Wehrmachtbericht .Obermaier p.	9
''Oberleutnant Victor Mölders brother ''Staffelkapitän wa shot prisoner war 1940.Aders pp	9
Squadron RAF shot Dungeness Mölders victory	9
wa fighter pilot reach number wa Cross Iron Cross Oak Leaves ''Ritterkreuz de Eisernen Kreuzes mit Eichenlaub war	9
award wa Adolf Hitler ''Reichskanzlei	9
award ceremony Hermann Mölders lodge Rominter pp	9
ndash photograph half-length view men outdoors	9
man left field cap pilot leather jacket fur collar Iron Cross displayed front shirt collar	9
man right three-quarter profile wear jacket decoration	9
Mölders unit end win victory	9
Squadron RAF Spitfire ''X4562 wa flown Pilot Officer T. Canterbury.Weal p.	9
Hurricanes brought victory preferential promotion ''Oberstleutnant recognition victory	9
bout influenza kept week wingman combat ''Oberleutnant Georg Claus wa Thames.Obermaier pp	9
Mölders claimed 55th victory mdash p.	9
Mölders member JG spent couple week R R skiing operation RAF Channel pp	9
wingman wa ''Oberleutnant Hartmann p.	9
Mölders claimed victory lengthy vacation stood ''Geschwader wa Channel front	9
logbook combat mission reconnaissance flight combat times.Obermaier p. ndash	9