culture marked degree syncretism pluralism	2
ha preserve tradition custom tradition idea invader immigrant influence part Asia East East Asia	2
caste system describes stratification restriction subcontinent class thousand hereditary group ''jātis caste	2
family value patriarchal joint family norm family area	2
majority Indians marriage parent family member consent bride groom	2
Marriage thought life divorce rate	2
Child marriage practice half woman age	2
cuisine variety style use herb spice	2
staple food region rice south east wheat north .Delphine Roger History Culture Food Asia Spices pepper world subcontinent	2
Chili pepper wa Cuisine. dress varies region colour style depends factor climate	2
Popular style dress include draped garment sari woman dhoti lungi men addition clothes salwar kameez woman kurta–pyjama trouser shirt men	2
festival origin caste creed	2
festival Diwali Ganesh Chaturthi Ugadi Thai Pongal Holi Onam Vijayadasami Durga Puja Eid Bakr-Id Christmas Buddha Jayanti Vaisakhi	2
set holiday twelve state	2
practice part everyday life public affair	2
architecture area diversity culture	2
monument Taj Mahal example Mughal architecture architecture comprises blend ancient varied tradition part country	2
music cover range tradition style	2
music encompasses genre – North Hindustani tradition offshoot form folk music	2
form music include filmi folk music tradition ''bauls form latter	2
dance ha diverse ''folk form	2
folk dance ''bhangra Punjab ''bihu Assam ''chhau Jharkhand ''sambalpuri Orissa ''ghoomar Rajasthan	2
dance form form element dance status Academy Dance Drama	2
''bharatanatyam state Tamil Nadu ''kathak Uttar Pradesh ''kathakali ''mohiniyattam ''kuchipudi Andhra Pradesh ''manipuri Manipur ''odissi Orissa ''sattriya Assam. '1	2
Sangeet Natak Academi Academy Dance Drama Delhi	2
Theatre incorporates music dance dialogue.. Hindu mythology borrowing medieval romance news event theatre ''bhavai state ''jatra ''nautanki ''ramlila North ''tamasha ''burrakatha Andhra Pradesh ''terukkuttu Tamil Nadu ''yakshagana Quote folk-theatre form	2
Assam play name ''Ankia Nat ''Jatra play	2
Bollywood Mumbai Hindi film prolific film industry world..	2
tradition exist Bengali Malayalam Marathi Tamil Telugu language cinemas..	2
work Sanskrit literature – Vedas epic Mahābhārata drama ''Abhijñānaśākuntalam Recognition Śakuntalā poetry ''Mahākāvya	2
– Tamil language ''Sangam literature. '1	2
''Encyclopaedia Quote literature Sanskrit Tamil literature	2
inscription stone century BC Tamil literature proper begin century AD	2
poetry wa epic exception wa secular court poetry member ''sangam academy Sangam literature	2
work stood test time work tradition	2
Tamil literature c. BC–AD consists Anthologies ''Eţţuttokai Ten Poems ''Pattuppāţţu grammar ''Tolkāppiyam 'Old Composition	2
literature Tamil ''Cankam ''Sangam literature	2
writer era language Rabindranath Tagore won Nobel	2