Tennyson adopts aspect Ulysses character source treatment Ulysses account.Stanford p.	4
ancient poet Homer Ulysses Odysseus GreekThe word Ulysses Ulixes Latin form Odysseus source word odyssey	4
poet character Euripides Tennyson margin Euripedes ''Hecabe Ulysses crafty	4
Horace Dante Shakespeare Alexander Pope	4
Homer ''Odyssey poem background eleventh book prophet Tiresias foretells Ulysses return Ithaca voyage begin voyage die peaceful unwarlike death sea	4
conclusion Tennyson poem Ulysses undertaking voyage	4
Tennyson character lover public affair Homer poem	4
Ulisse Dante ''Inferno Tennyson source character Pettigrew p. ha effect poem interpretation	4
Ulisse recall voyage ''Inferno canto Eighth Circle counsellor gift reason	4
Dante treat Ulisse zeal …/ T'explore world evil counselor lust adventure expense family duty Ithaca.Rowlinson p.	4
Tennyson project zeal Ulysses desire knowledge Schwarz	4
gray spirit desire knowledge sinking star Beyond utmost bound human thought	4
poet intention recall character remains evident passage	4
become name recall episode ''Odyssey Demodocus sings Odysseus adventure king presence fame	4
phrase gloom dark sea deep / Moans round voice Tennyson p.	4
Critics influence Shakespeare passage	4
movement savage race hoard sleep feed echo Hamlet soliloquy man / chief market time / sleep feed	4
Tennyson dull pause end / rust ’ d shine use	4
recall Shakespeare Ulysses Cressida c. Cressida III Scene III Stanford p.	4
Perserverance dear lord Keeps honour bright hang fashion rusty mail monumental mockery	4
movement Ulysses passage nineteenth-century English-language poetry present decisive evidence influence Dante.i Robson W. W.	4
Ulysses turn attention kingdom speaks port sea mariner	4
strain discontent weakness age remain poem Tennyson leaf Ulysses strive seek yield Dantesque desire knowledge bound	4
word Dante character exhorts men journey parallel Tennyson Ulysses call men join voyage	4
Dante Ulisse 'O brother 'who Ten thousand peril none sens hold vigil slight u course forgo experience world sun	4
Regard origin —from whence	4
exist brute ye virtue intelligence'.Dante ''Inferno XXVI Robson W. W.	4
critic note Ulysses mariner	4
irony develops Ulysses speech sailors— friend / 'T seek newer world	4
Dante Ulisse ha voyage recount ''Inferno Ulysses monologue recollection Hell.Rowlinson p.	4