degree Tennyson identifies Ulysses ha debate scholar poem	4
Critics Tennyson identifies speaker read Ulysses speech irony	4
interpretation poem developed argument Tennyson doe Ulysses criticism ha inconsistency Ulysses character fault poet	4
Key reading Ulysses context poem	4
reading account Tennyson statement poem— need —and considers undermine Ulysses determination irony stalwartness face life Hallam death	4
Ulysses heroic character determination seek work note face hearth age.Tennyson interpretation monologue	4
passion conviction Tennyson language—and comment poem—signify poet wa age courage persistence	4
Ulysses promotes spirit youth age refusal resign face life	4
twentieth century reader Ulysses	4
meaning poem wa Tennyson stature	4
Paull Baum Ulysses inconsistency Tennyson conception poem Baum Paull	4
ironic interpretation dominant.Hughes p.	4
Baum Ulysses echo Lord hero display emotion introspection rejection responsibility	4
Ulysses resolute utterance— strive seek yield —is undercut irony Baum critic compare line Satan courage submit yield ''Paradise .Baum Pettigrew	4
Ulysses apparent disdain facet ironic perspective	4
declares wife indicates weariness savage race suggests distance son Telemachus	4
reading paragraph tribute Telemachus rejection prudence	4
describe Telemachus— blameless decent —are word connotation Tennyson poetry tradition blameless attribute god hero	4
Chiasson Ulysses faith afterlife Tennyson method indirection affirm need faith Ulysses lack faith lead neglect kingdom family	4
Chiasson regard poem Tennyson canon poem meaning resolve indirection understood illustrates Tennyson conviction sanction thing desire lead brutal repudiation responsibility 'life E	4
Chiasson Tennyson 'Ulysses'—A Re-Interpretation	4
ironic reading found Ulysses longing withdrawal death form quest	4
sense passivity poem critic highlight Tennyson tendency melancholic	4
T. Eliot opines Tennyson tell story	4
Dante treatment Ulysses Tennyson piece elegiac mood .T	4
Ulysses found action hero goal vague poem line refuse yield	4
scholar Herbert Tucker Tennyson ’ s character move time space inwardly.Tucker p.	4
Ulysses experience … arch wherethro' Gleams untravell world margin fade move	4