Abbey Theatre found success crowd production	4
Abbey wa fortunate Synge key member wa foremost English-language dramatist	4
theatre play eminent eminent author Yeats Lady Gregory Moore Martyn Padraic Colum Oliver St Gogarty Higgins MacDonagh Lord Dunsany T. Murray Cousins Lennox Robinson	4
author board wa time Abbey reputation writer theatre	4
Abbey fortune opening Synge ''The Playboy World disturbance	4
trouble ''Playboy Riots part nationalist theatre wa offence Synge use word 'shift wa time symbol O'Shea adultery hence wa slight virtue womanhood.Price ''Synge Drama Methuen pp	4
crowd actor remainder play dumbshow.Isherwood	4
Fellow Returns Darker Mood ''New Times	4
theatre decision call police anger nationalist	4
press opinion rioter protest management Abbey wa shaken	4
chose stage Synge mdash mdash play ''The Tinker fear disturbance	4
year Fay brother association theatre States Lennox Robinson Abbey day-to-day management	4
''The Shewing-Up Blanco Posnet protest	4
subsequent discussion issue theatre journal ''The Arrow	4
year proprietor Abbey Horniman preference course	4
Relations Horniman tense play	4
mark respect death VII Dublin theatre night	4
Robinson kept Abbey open.Leland	4
''The Lie Land Journeys Cork Cork Cork Press p.	4
ISBN Horniman heard Robinson decision connection company.Welch	4
''The Oxford Companion Literature Oxford Oxford Press p.	4
ISBN 0-1986-6158-4 estimate £10,350 mdash worth US dollar mdash project	4
loss Horniman Synge Fays Abbey Robinson drift public interest box office return	4
trend wa time emergence Sean O'Casey heir Synge.Kavanagh pp	4
O'Casey career dramatist ''The Shadow Gunman Abbey	4
wa ''Juno Paycock ''The Stars	4
Theatergoers arose riot play way reminiscent ''Playboy year earlier.Kavanagh p.	4
public reaction Abbey O'Casey play	4
Yeats Lady Gregory Abbey government State gift people	4
government year Finance Blythe government subsidy £850 Abbey	4
company theatre English-speaking world.Kavanagh pp	4
subsidy theatre avoid bankruptcy amount wa rescue difficulty	4
Abbey School Abbey School Ballet set year	4
latter wa Ninette de Valois mdash choreography number Yeats play mdash ran Walker	4
Festival Abbey Ninette de Valois Choreography Part	4
time company space create experimental theatre ''Peacock ground floor theatre	4
Edwards Micheál MacLiammoir Gate Theatre Peacock stage work dramatists.Welsh p.	4
Gate sought work playwright space Abbey period decline	4
story work wa Gate Theatre	4
Denis Johnston play ''Shadowdance Abbey Lady Gregory author “ Old Lady ” title page.Welch	4
''The Oxford Companion Literature Oxford Oxford Press p.	4
ISBN 0-1986-6158-4 Johnston re-title play	4
Gate ''The Old Lady Says 'No ''The Peacock	4
Note critic Ronsley Christine veracity story.Bartlett Rebecca Ann	4
''Choice Books Reviews Titles College Research Libraries p.	4