Norris Edwards land settler immigrant	3
month immigrant wa country purchase merchant license trading tribes.Jackson p.	3
militia colonel Martin Parmer Edwards colonist Nacogdoches Norris Sepulveda commander garrison oppression corruption	3
Edwards wa expulsion order wa ploy disguise involvement plot	3
kangaroo court found men position public office	3
court ''alcalde .Ericson p.	3
action Parmer week Parmer man dispute Norris warrant Parmer arrest	3
Norris office arrest warrant wa voided.Jackson p.	3
fall Edwards gather support Edwards colonist revolt authority	3
year tribe title land East	3
Edwards tribe title north Nacogdoches exchange support plans.Everett p.	3
Edwards brother Nacogdoches settler building town Old Stone Fort.Samora ''et al	3
Edwards colony republic Fredonia	3
hour announcement Fredonians peace treaty Cherokee Chief Fields Dunn Hunter	3
Fields Hunter claimed represent tribe provide warriors.Jackson pp	3
recognition agreement Old Stone Fort flew flag stripe ndash ndash races.Weaver p.	3
Inscribed banner wa motto Independence Liberty Justice	3
Edwards sent messenger request aid States intervene	3
sent invite Austin colonist join rebellion rebuke yourselves delusion ruin	3
Edwards action disturbed colonist loyalty country fear alliance Cherokee	3
authority Cherokee alliance Ellis Bean agent Saucedo chief negotiation Fields	3
Cherokee tribe proper procedure attain land grant official channel government honor land request	3
argument response Cherokee repudiate treaty Edwards.Everett p.	3
news arrest ''alcalde government retaliate	3
Lieutenant Colonel Mateo commander Antonio de Béxar infantry Ericson p. Austin colony ass loyalty settler	3
Austin colonist madman Nacogdoches independence	3
army left Nacogdoches militiaman Austin colony	3
Impatient army response time Norris men retake Old Stone Fort	3
Parmer supporter men Norris force le ten minutes.Jackson p.	3
Bean militiaman Austin colony rode Nacogdoches.Jackson p.	3
time Parmer Edwards Cherokee intention war	3
Cherokee warrior reinforce revolt Edwards supporter	3
Bean Sabine River Edwards brother States.Ericson p.	3
Ahumade soldier chief Saucedo Nacogdoches restore order.Jackson p.	3
Cherokee arm treaty authority question tribe loyalty	3
demonstrate loyalty Cherokee council Fields Hunter	3
tribal law offense enemy tribe death	3
Fields Hunter death reason Cherokee Edwards cohort enemies.Everett p.	3
execution authority commandant Provinces Anastasio Cherokee prompt action.Everett p.	3
amnesty conflict Edwards Martin Parmer Sterne merchant supply rebel force	3
Sterne wa death treason wa condition swear allegiance arm government.Ericson p. upheld oath government Revolution fight provide fund raise company soldier Army	3