Cartier production wa six-part ''The Quatermass Experiment broadcast summer	5
science-fiction story relates human space Quatermass consequence alien presence invades crew rocket flight return Earth body crewmember absorbed consciousness body	5
success ''The Quatermass Experiment ha described Film Screenonline website series 1950s	5
Cartier contribution success wa ''The Times newspaper landmark television drama imagination ability shock disturb	5
success ''The Quatermass Experiment sequel ''Quatermass II ''Quatermass Pit Cartier	5
''Quatermass II amount material location mm film opening drama studio location television.Pixley p.	5
Cartier experience film director cinema-style scenes.Pixley p.	5
appeal ''Quatermass ha Museum Broadcast Communications depiction range fear postwar security	5
result Cartier combination science fiction poignant melodrama audience	5
Screenonline website suggests impact Cartier interpretation script wa factor success attribute originality mass appeal dynamism ''The Quatermass Experiment landmark science fiction cornerstone genre television	5
''Quatermass Cartier one-off drama adaptation Heights ''The Moment Truth ''The Creature .Pixley p.	5
note wa collaboration adaptation Orwell novel ''Nineteen broadcast Cartier work	5
''The Times review day broadcast vividness minute hate wa instance orgy vindictiveness	5
question Commons scene horror play BBC telephone call Cartier life performance ahead.Cooke p.	5
BBC threat assign bodyguard	5
Cartier television defend production studio debate Governors BBC performance planned.Murray p.	5
production time backing Edinburgh speech Royal Society Arts Queen performance.Murray pp	5
''Nineteen success wa television drama UK	5
Cartier spent amount money production	5
money resource adaptation ''Rebecca	5
memo production transmission Cartier production performance ''Rebecca u danger area improvement	5
defend time departmental cost scene load acute state load ''Rebecca Design Supply expenditure costume vast area hall stairway expenditure effort building left impression point department doing.Jacobs p.	5