Henry Harrison governor Territory begin	9
Harrison sought secure title Native land expansion Territory attract settler statehood	9
Harrison land cession treaty Indians Treaty Fort Miami Pottawatomie Lenape tribal leader acre km² States.Langguth p. 164Owens p. Tenskwatawa Prophet movement tribe return way	9
brother Tecumseh wa Treaty Fort prominent leader	9
Tecumseh idea year Shawnee leader Jacket Mohawk leader Brant Native land wa tribe land agreement tribes.Owens p. confront States Tecumseh primary adversary Native leader treaty	9
kill anyone term treaty	9
Tecumseh travel warrior abandon accommodationist chief join resistance Prophetstown	9
Tecumseh Fort treaty wa illegitimate.Langguth pp	9
ndash meeting Harrison Harrison nullify treaty Americans attempt land treaty	9
Harrison demand tribe relation States.Langguth pp	9
ndash meeting Tecumseh Harrison seek alliance hostility broke out.Langguth p. Tensions Americans month interference commerce	9
agent sought secure alliance Native Americans tribe assist defense hostility break tribe reluctant accept offer benefit arrangement	9
confrontation Tecumseh offer alliance supply confederacy firearm ammunition.Langguth p. Tecumseh met Harrison Vincennes Tecumseh Harrison Shawnee brother meant remain peace States	9
Tecumseh south mission recruit Tribes	9
nation appeal faction Creeks Sticks call arm Creek part p. 167Owens p. Harrison left territory business meeting Tecumseh secretary acting-governor	9
Miami tribe year wa quick learn Tecumseh plan war territory militia sent emergency letter return Harrison	9
Harrison force army command militia	9
Harrison communication D.C. march confederacy show force accept peace.Langguth p. 168Owens p. Harrison militia company settlement Maria Creek north Vincennes	9
wa sixty-man company Jackets bright yellow coat Corydon Rangers.The Rangers day territory protect settler raid Native Americans action year	9
force men set towards Prophetstown.Funk p. force army US Infantry Regiment volunteer militia company Rangers	9
army site Terre Haute camped built Fort Harrison supply	9
party Jackets wa Native Americans casualty men forage	9
ration cut supply Wabash River Vincennes	9
army Harrison advance Prophetstown p. 28Owens p.	9