record club reference Jesus College boat material survives nineteenth century.The club record time Sherwood book Sherwood p. x Introduction reference pleasure Oxford letter poem eighteenth century race crew college start nineteenth century.Sherwood pp	8
boat oarsman oar coxswain Eton record school Oxford	8
record inter-college race Jesus College College date p. college boat time boat wa victorious.Hardy p. rower race boat oarsman coxswain attract interest race eights.Sharp p. Students row inn Sandford-on-Thames mile south Oxford race way	8
race start Iffley Lock finish Barge Christ Church Meadow	8
Flags barge indicate order crew	8
Crews set boat s catch bump boat	8
bumped boat bumping boat drop bumping boat start day race bumped boat	8
aim wa become lead boat Head River	8
identification crew wore college colour rudder boat college coat arm	8
Crews Jesus College leek emblem Wales oar distinction.Sharp p. race rower wore hat others Jesus crew wore Tam o'shanters college colour band Jesus crew Jesus College wore p. print Oxford thought depict Jesus College boatIn crew Jesus become Head River	8
rower caught crab boat	8
boat wa bumped Jesus boat rowed claimed wa Head River	8
Jesus men college flag denote boat	8
crew dispute ''Quot homines tot sententiae men opinion leek onion emblem Jesus oar wa row race	8
incident ha picture depiction race Oxford I. T. Serres Marine Painter IV .Sherwood p. print wa month prepare	8
point suggest print depicts scene event pp	8
Races regulation college rower member college	8
race college boat Torpids wa boat le oar race	8
Jesus part race college wa boat p. foundation club date official record inter-college race begin	8
Jesus College VIII competition year position Christ Church VIII bumped successive night Exeter Balliol Queen college Jesus part year competition	8
Jesus College boat rowed place race	8
club fortune varied year	8
overbump crew place boat bumped boat wa position race	8
college boat compete place p. onwards Hardy history college record College ha – college part race year seldom position place	8
college participation race wa place college position place	8
Hardy Jesus College boat reputation faster boat university	8
crew Ladies Challenge Plate Henley Regatta Eton winners.Hardy p. woman VIII college VIII position river thirty years.Baker p. college chaplain Cross set oar club	8
year college magazine Cross supporter club oar purpose.Baker p. VIII 1950s bump reach division point seventh	8
position year wa seventh division ha division 7th division	8
Women Jesus College college wa men college become	8
woman VIII wa Head River Torpids	8
woman VIII won blade division Torpids Eights Week achievement crew described ''Jesus College Record College team decade team decade sport	8
crew won Novices Trophy Wallingford Regatta year	8
woman VIII ha position 7th division	8