Yeats Rhymers Club Rhys Hone group poet met Fleet tavern recite verse	4
collective Tragic Generation Alford Norman	4
Rhymers Club Poets Tragic Generation	4
Edwin Ellis edition work process forgotten poem Vala Zoas	4
essay Shelley Yeats re-read ''Prometheus Unbound place thought book world	4
Yeats Yeats interest mysticism spiritualism occultism astrology	4
read subject life member paranormal research organization Ghost Club wa Emanuel SwedenborgBurke Martin J	4
magic study word book ''The Countess exist	4
life centre think write	4
interest mdash study Hinduism Theosophist Chatterjee occult mdash basis poetry	4
W. aspect Yeats work spectacle grown man mumbo-jumbo magic nonsense	4
Yeats poem wa Isle Statues fantasy work Edmund Spenser model	4
piece ''Dublin Review ha	4
solo publication wa pamphlet ''Mosada Poem print copy paid father	4
wa collection ''The Wanderings Oisin Poems series verse mid-1880s	4
titular poem contains word biographer R.F	4
Foster obscure name repetition rhythm varied poem section .Foster rode sorrow hound Bran Sgeolan Lomair morning misty mild fair.The mist-drops hung fragrant tree blossom hung bees.We rode sadness Gavra	4
Wanderings Oisin lyric Cycle mythology display influence Samuel Ferguson poets.Alspach Use Yeats Writers Folklore Kennedy	4
poem year wa work period disown maturity	4
''Oisin introduces wa become theme appeal life contemplation appeal life action	4
poem meditation theme love esoteric subject include ''Poems ''The ''The Reeds	4
Yeats wa formation Dublin Order	4
society held meeting Yeats chairman	4
year Dublin lodge wa conjunction Chatterjee Society lecture	4
Society hermeticism Rosicrucianism Dawn	4
séances held spirit Leo Africanus claimed Yeats ''Daemon anti-self speculation ''Per Silentia Lunae Claire V. Identity Formation W. Yeats 'A Vision	4
Studies Review Volume Issue	4
wa Dawn motto ''Daemon est Deus inversus mdash ''Devil ''A demon god	4
''Daemon est Deus inversus Madame Blavatsky claim divine Homogeneity contain essence evil motto symbol Light	4
wa recruiter sect ''Isis-Urania temple brought uncle Pollexfen Maud Gonne Florence Farr	4
distaste abstract religion personality cult wa type people met Dawn.Foster wa Order power struggle Farr Macgregor Mathers wa Mathers sent Aleister Crowley repossess Dawn paraphernalia Blythe Road	4
Dawn offshoot Yeats Stella Elizabeth	4
Jacques Molay Tower Yeats Civil	4