mid-1941 Royal Corps tank squadron operation 'A 'B 'C Squadrons	9
'A 'B Squadrons Valentine Infantry tank Mark VIc light tank 'C Squadron wa twelve Tetrarchs Brigade Division.Flint pp	9
ndash 'C Squadron wa order prepare service 'A 'B Squadrons climate.Flint p. squadron Scotland training embarkation disembarkation ship craft prepare action operations.Flint pp	9
ndash element 'C Squadron Tetrarchs part force period war fear government enter conflict side force wa capture number island coast occurred.Flint p.65 fear groundless unit join rest squadron training	9
assignment Operation Ironclad wa invasion Madagascar island world Vichy control	9
Chiefs Staff Madagascar deny port Antsirane naval force Ocean.Flint p. Operation Ironclad wa command Maj. Gen. G. Sturges	9
Commando Independent Brigade 17th brigade group 5th Infantry Division	9
Brigade core invasion force training operation command wa 'B Squadron Valentines 'B Squadron Tetrarchs 'C Squadron unit	9
squadron wa troop Headquarters troop Valentines Tetrarch Valentines Tetrarchs	9
invasion force west coast tip Madagascar Antsirane bay Diego Suarez	9
invasion plan assault beach west side tip force advance approach Antsirane rear	9
Information beach defence port Vichy force wa vague wa defender weapon armour Valentine tank.Flint p. Commando Courrier Bay infantry brigade 'B Squadron Ambararata Bay	9
objective infantry brigade support wa control Antsirane town infantry 'B Squadron trouble area beach craft wa hour Tetrarch craft stuck sand.Flint p. infantry brigade Antsirane squadron Valentines Tetrarch support lead element infantry town	9
invasion force defence trench pillbox dug ridge	9
tank breach rocky ground pillbox trench number target pounder machine-gun fire line infantry assault day	9
tank outflank defence advance island Tetrarchs beach force advance Vichy line defence	9
built World pillbox machine-gun dug-in mm artillery piece latter anti-tank role penetrate armour Tetrarchs Valentines	9
Valentines artillery fire Tetrarchs fate Tetrarch order report resistance machine motor-cycle combination truck way back.Flint pp	9
ndash commander Tetrarch report wa command Valentines Tetrarchs attempt breach defence	9
tank road defensive line out-flank line right-hand side hill cover artillery piece turn face assault Valentine Tetrarch hit destroyed	9
tank volley fire artillery piece positions.Flint p. line wa broken Brigade assault Royal Marines tank 'B Squadron Valentines Tetrarchs defensive position afternoon sporadic artillery fire Valentine	9
squadron played part battle Vichy authority surrender day troop continue engage force guerrilla warfare November.Flint p. 'C Squadron casualty ithe invasion Valentine Tetrarchs twelve tank squadron	9
Madagascar wa part Burma campaign part Brigade.Flint pp	9