Frederick country act opinion inhabitants.Dorpalen p.	7
history liberalism idea intention Victoria others reign	7
Prince Saxe-Coburg-Gotha system p.	7
Frederick wife rule consort liberalize appointment ministers.Farago p.	7
limit office include element liberalism	7
historian Harbutt Dawson Erich Eyck Frederick death put end development liberalism empire	7
longer reign health Frederick country path war.Chalat p. p.	7
claim Frederick World mdash extension Weimar mdash historian Balfour end World state world development Emperor outbreak World II.Balfour p. v. Author Freund state outright world war Frederick longer.Freund p.	7
father year Frederick throne sick man threshold death	7
influence policy height power health popularity success Frederick wa reign	7
life historian Tipton speculate father sooner longer	7
historian Wilhelm oppose idea Frederick	7
oppose father Bismarck change course soldier wa family tradition father army age ten	7
Andreas note Frederick Bismarck policy life change behaviour.Dorpalen p.	7
tendency Frederick Bismarck system p. case Frederick character brought change reigned.Dorpalen p.	7
Sheehan state climate party system period way Frederick overcome liberalization.Sheehan p.	7
observes Frederick persona death movement p. point mistake II paint father light.Dorpalen p.	7
Frederick child mdash mdash held position	7
father horror war family heritage Bismarck tutelage	7
Frederick Victoria way felt bound increase tension parents.Feuchtwanger p.	7
disdain opinion government father death path grandfather	7
reference Frederick III.Kollander p.	7
II father policy idea World I. Bismarck plan Frederick Victoria II tool power downfall	7
Bismarck II wa dismiss Bismarck ’ s resource deployed Empress Frederick use influence son behalf	7
wizard magic spell powerless people respect Kant ’ s command use people end stock loyalty draw	7
Lord Salisbury told Queen Victoria 'The quality Bismarck Emperor order strengthen Emperor Frederick throne quality ha	7
Empress mixture pity triumph told influence son destroyed it.Michael Balfour ''The Times Mifflin p.	7