Selwood wa Football Club selection wa seventh draft pick AFL Draft.Walls R ''The Age recruiting scout pure footballer draft M ''The Age top pick wa concern durability knee	8
highest-ever draft pick Cats Slattery p.	8
Selwood debut opening round AFL premiership season game season. footywire.com Selwood transition AFL drew comment community Slattery p. Brisbane coach Matthews game played .Morton Football League Bigpond coach Mark Selwood youngster tutelage time club.Gullan S ''The J Football League Bigpond Selwood ability influence game appearance teammate game disposal tackle	8
achievement described Gullan p. AFL Star Award nomination	8
staff highlight package performance screen rest team match review week.Gullan p.	8
Selwood impact game first–year player comparison Chris Judd year success	8
conclusion home period Selwood contribution accolade	8
vote wa Ron Evans Medal winner AFL Star Award.Shields J ''The Selwood maximum vote judge	8
meant judge nominee. Football League Bigpond Selwood wa AFLPA Year Player Award % vote peer	8
player win award first–year players. ''The finish ladder win McClelland Trophy Selwood debut North Melbourne Melbourne Cricket Ground MCG .Boulon M ''The Age front spectator Selwood disposal mark clearance tackle score assist club record point victory.Lienert ''Perth Selwood contribute Collingwood week Townley p. form AFL MCG Port Adelaide. ''The disposal mark clearance mdash player mdash tackle score assist ''The Selwood Cats record point win. Football League Bigpond year age Selwood person play team years.Williams R Fox Sports wa win AFL Star Award play premiership side season year player league history.Sherwood M ''The Canberra Times p.	8
Selwood debut year achievement AFL highest-paid first–year player.Barrett ''The Selwood season ranked first–year player category possession disposal game kick handpasses mark tackle mdash first–year AFL player Football League Bigpond mdash tackle game	8
score assist season ranked top ten league	8
Selwood list year honour season end Football Club Year Player Award top Club Champion award. Football League Bigpond medium end year awards. ''The	8