Vrba wa series articles— Leadership Duress Slovakia group historian tie Slovak community Bauer Yablonka Gila Fatran Livia Rothkirchen	3
introduction Amir refers argue Council Nazis bunch mocker pseudo-historians Amir writes baseless accusation wa lent credence Haifa honorary doctorate head mocker Vrba	3
Amir heroism person Alfréd Wetzler wa escape Auschwitz doubt	3
fact wa Auschwitz prisoner heroism ha judge work rescue accuse deeply disturbs u Czech community	3
Bauer Y. Yablonka Jelinek Y. Akiva N. Fatran G. Frider Conway Rothkirchen Spitzer J	3
''Leadership Time Distress Slovakia	3
tension Ruth Linn call survivor discourse expert discourse lie heart criticism Vrba	3
Bauer ha Vrba memoir memoir sense contains excerpt conversation chance accurate ha element second-hand story doe correspond reality	3
experience Vrba account argues Bauer	3
Everything tell action truth document value	3
Vrba resistance thought matter think expert sure	3
Yehuda Bauer letter Ami Hebrew translator Vrba memoir Linn p.	3
part Vrba opinion Holocaust historian example number people Auschwitz Yehuda Bauer doe title think throw figure research	3
List Holocaust Victims Reignites Dispute Figures Agency	3
ha Vrba wa eyewitness account	3
Vrba memoir overheard SS officer Auschwitz discus salami ton reference imminent arrival thousand Jews	3
Vrba mention Vrba-Wetzler report advance mass deportation Jews	3
Czech historian Miroslav writes time Vrba Wetzler escape wa Auschwitz annihilation mechanism order kill thousand Jews	3
wa knowledge Vrba motive escape	3
fact mention Vrba Wetzler report preparation way annihilation Jews	3
Vrba Wetzler record rumor arrival transport rumor—had it—about transport thousand Jews	3
argues Vrba Wetzler view advance imminent ''Endlösung Vrba later—long war wa testify longing force world face magnitude Nazis crime	3
suspicion Vrba longing degree embellishment subsequent account Vrba-Wetzler report knew camp	3
edition memoir Vrba reference imminent deportation wa version Vrba-Wetzler report hand	3
Oscar Council report death speculation order lend report maximum credibility	3
Vrba speculates wa reason reference translation latter wa version wa world	3
version Slovak survive.Vrba p.	3