season year Raptors franchise	8
roster wa selection NBA Draft number pick Andrea acquisition point guard T. exchange Villanueva signing guard Anthony Parker Jorge cbc.ca	8
wa contract extension Maurizio Treviso wa club vice-president assistant manager. nba.com/raptors	8
half season result towards .500 mark.Smalls Anthony nba.com	8
season record seed Conference NBA Playoffs Division title homecourt advantage time franchise history. nba.com/raptors nba.com	8
career-highs ppg rpg wa start NBA All-Star Game	8
Raptors defense ball-sharing team chemistry.Schuhmann nba.com	8
Colangelo turnaround season Feschuk thestar.com wa NBA history term league defensive ranking.Pelton nba.com/sonics	8
wa NBA Coach Year coach Raptors history receive honour nba.com/raptors Colangelo wa Executive Year. nba.com/raptors	8
Raptors won playoff game season victory Nets nba.com/raptors series	8
change roster campaign sought reproduce form campaign	8
Raptors Carlos Delfino trade round draft pick nba.com/raptors Jamario nba.com/raptors three-point specialist Jason agents.Ulmer Mike nba.com/raptors	8
hand veteran swingman Peterson Orleans Hornets. cbc.ca	8
division champion Raptors tipped contender division conference titles.Feschuk thestar.com	8
inability play injury game game game possibility smooth campaign Raptors chalked win season	8
Raptors division title NBA Playoffs sixth seed Orlando Magic games. basketball-reference.com Mike nba.com/raptors	8
Whereas season wa success campaign wa disappointment	8
Weaknesses defence lack brought focus playoff change roster	8
blockbuster trade wa principle campaign six-time All-Star Jermaine O'Neal wa Pacers exchange become emergence Calderón Rasho Nesterovič Maceo Hibbert 17th pick NBA Draft Raptors boost frontcourt.Smith Doug thestar.com	8
spent summer interior game wa bench	8
Raptors alternate road jersey season purple design wa season	8
maple leaf neck jersey Raptors team thestar.com Sept Oct	8
introduction O'Neal brought home rebound block Raptors inconsistent	8
start season wa long-time assistant Triano. nba.com/raptors	8
Triano tweaked line-up avail Raptors All-Star break	8
O'Neal Miami Shawn Marion Marcus Banks Aldridge nba.com loss Raptors playoff picture contention game season remaining. nba.com	8
Raptors record basketball-reference.com season overhaul core Marion become agent become Parker turn breakthrough season	8
Triano wa term position head coach.Smith Doug	8
roster shakeup season wa 76ers veteran Reggie Evans. nba.com	8
DeMar DeRozan‎ pick fill spot wings. sports.espn.go.com	8
wa signing agent Hedo Türkoğlu turn sign-and-trade agreement team player Devean Marco Antoine Marion Humphries Nathan Jawai.Stein Marc sports.espn.go.com	8
time Parker Cleveland Cavaliers news-hearld.com point guard Jarrett wa Nesterovič brought provide cover men	8
Delfino Ukić Milwaukee Bucks Amir Sonny Weems. sports.espn.go.com	8
Colangelo nucleus future wa persuade stay provide fringe benefit Raptors ''The Globe Mail	8