Vyazma front mobile force Panzer group area defense Army line	9
defense setup construction wa overrun spearhead met Vyazma	9
army pocket west city.Vasilevsky p.	9
wa fierce desperate Wehrmacht employ division eliminate army force support towards	9
remnant Fronts retreat consolidate line Mozhaisk	9
force destroyed troop group size platoon rifle division	9
resistance Vyazma time command bring reinforcement army direction 5th transport rifle tank division Far East	9
south Bryansk performance wa Vyazma	9
Panzer movement front Army Orel Bryansk	9
''Luftflotte flew combat mission destroyed vehicle	9
mixture dive-bombers medium bomber destroyed rail line troop movement Sumy-Lgov-Kursk area communication Bryansk Fronts.Bergström p.91	9
army surrender troop escape group intermediate defense line Poniry Mtsensk	9
snow road stretch mud phenomenon ''rasputitsa Russia	9
group maneuver men p.	9
Panzer Division ambush set Dmitri Leliushenko Guards Rifle Corps Mikhail Tank Brigade city Mtsensk	9
built T-34 tank wood panzer past scratch team infantry advance armor flank Panzer IV formation	9
Wehrmacht shock defeat wa investigation wa	9
troop dismay T-34s tank gun	9
T-IV tank mm gun explode T-34 engine	9
''Luftflotte flew attack position support Panzer Division tank artillery piece vehicle kinds.Plocher p.231	9
''Armee operating North force aim Bryansk front counter-attack	9
inferior Luftwaffe loss VVS	9
Stuka sortie medium bomber attack whilst Stuka medium bomber strike flown supply column Brynask area	9
Forces caught Luftwaffe tank vehicle attack	9
estimate soldier Wehrmacht pocket Jukes World — Front Osprey ISBN p. research suggests lower—but enormous—figure prisoner strength % .Jukes p.	9
personnel loss permament command Titans p336 n15	9
desperate Army resistance Wehrmacht	9
Germans sight Mozhaisk line found defensive setup force	9
day Georgy Zhukov wa Leningrad charge defense	9
concentration defense Mozhaisk line move Vasilevsky.Zhukov tome p.	9
''Luftwaffe sky whenever strength	9
''Stukageschwader Stuka bomber group flew sortie vehicle motor vehicle truck artillery pieces.Plocher p.231Bergström p.93 Stalin evacuation Communist Staff government office Samara number official	9
population flee train jamming road city	9
Stalin capital fear pandemonium	9