12th-century historian Henry Huntingdon ''Historia Anglorum relates Siward wa dysentery die cow die soldier clothed armour hand axe shield	7
anecdote doubtful historicity thought saga Siward lost.Mason ''House Godwine pp	7
ndash ''Vita Ædwardi Regis state Siward wa monastery St Olaf Galmanho claim Chronicle Worcester ''Historia Regum .Barlow ed	7
''Life p. = ''Vita Ædwardi i	7
note ''Ibid p. n. Darlington McGurk Bray ed	7
n. Stevenson ''Simeon Durham p. Material source thought attest existence saga kind tradition Siward life	7
source ''Vita et Passio Waldevi history Siward cult-inspiring son Waltheof	7
text contains account Waltheof paternal origin process recount adventure father Siward box article	7
witness tradition Henry Huntingdon ''Historia Anglorum contains extract saga-like material Siward invasion Scotland death .Wright ''Cultivation Saga pp	7
ndash Anglo-Saxonist Stenton Siward wa statesman warrior primitive type .Stenton p. Writers half-century death Siward ruler brought peace brigandage.Aird ''St Cuthbert p. note ndash Siward decade death Confessor ''Domesday Book manor Yorkshire Derbyshire Siward held d'Avranches Chester.See Williams Martin ed	7
ndash Clarke Nobility pp	7
land wa worth £212 son Waltheof wa held £136 worth land counties.Clarke Nobility pp	7
ndash Domesday record incomplete picture Siward	7
property worth £348 Siward son compare £2493 value held family earl Mercia.Clarke Nobility pp	7
ndash latter Morcar Mercia Northumbria day death land worth £968 Tostig earl time land worth £491 possession Siward land course Earls Northumbria.Clarke Nobility pp	7
ndash ndash county become Durham Northumberland Cumberland Westmorland survey land Yorkshire North.Green ''Aristocracy pp	7
ndash Siward built church St Olaf Galmanho	7
record burial church notice lay burial church pre-Norman England.Daniell ''Death Medieval p. Siward Howe ''i.e	7
Hill wa Siward Siward held court wa burial place.Baxter ''Earls Mercia p. Siward son Waltheof mother wa Ælfflæd	7
Waltheof earl East Midlands Northumbria.Lewis Waltheof Waltheof Conqueror act execution subsequent veneration saint Crowland Abbey.Lewis Waltheof Scott Waltheof pp	7
ndash Watkins Cult Waltheof pp	7
ndash Waltheof daughter Scots connection Siward ancestor monarch	7
Ælfflæd Siward woman Godgifu Siward	7
marriage grant territory Stamford Lincolnshire Abbey	7
child source state name Osbjorn mother marriage ha possibility Waltheof Osbjorn born mother Siward Osbjorn inherit territory Waltheof territory north family mother Ælfflæd.Aird ''St Cuthbert p. n. ''Norman p.	7