Gilbert wa born Southampton Strand	4
father wa naval surgeon writer novel story son	4
Gilbert mother wa Ann Bye daughter	4
Gilbert parent distant stern relationship	4
break-up marriage relationship mother strained.Pearson pp	4
Gilbert sister born family travel year Jane b	4
Milan – Weigall miniature painter Anne Maude Florence b	4
Boulogne – married.Ainger p. xxiEden	4
''Gilbert Appearance Reality p. Sullivan Society Gilbert wa Bab baby Schwenck father godparent	4
wa Boulogne age kept servant read Morrison Grammar School Great School head boy play school performance scenery	4
degree examination commission Royal Artillery end Crimean recruit commission Gilbert line regiment	4
Civil assistant clerk Privy Council Office year	4
Militia part-time home service force work rank Captain.Pearson p.	4
5th Yorkshire Militia Royal Aberdeenshire Highlanders	4
Militia Gilbert wa honorary promotion	4
Stedman p. Ainger p. bequest £300 service brief career barrister Inner Temple student practice wa client year.Gilbert W.S	4
Introduction supplement income Gilbert variety story rant grotesque illustration theatre review form parody play Stedman Jane W. ''W	4
ISBN 0-85430-068-6 pseudonym Bab childhood nickname poem magazine ''Fun	4
story article review paper ''Cornhill Magazine Society Tinsley Magazine ''Temple Bar	4
addition Gilbert wa correspondent Russe drama critic Times	4
1860s Hood Christmas ''Saturday Night News ''Savage Club Papers	4
''The Observer newspaper sent war correspondent reporting	4
poem Gilbert book form ''Bab Ballads .Stedman pp	4
''The Bab Ballads etc detail history collection wa drawn	4
return source material play opera	4
Gilbert colleague ''Fun Hood Clement Scott Burnand ''Punch Arundel Club Savage Club Evans café table competition ''Punch 'Round table'.Stedman pp	4
play ''Society Evans café scene	4
Gilbert Agnes Turner wa year junior	4
Gilbert Dyke dinner party others home dinner contrast picture fictionalisation film	4
Gilberts child pet ones.Ainger p. Stedman pp	4