raid Reinhard Scheer planning foray North	9
launch operation mid-May mine damage ''Seydlitz repair mdash Scheer wa embark raid battlecruiser force strength	9
dockyard ship fit duty test night broadside torpedo mine wa watertight leak fore aft transverse bulkhead	9
repair operation wa week time dockyard Scheer ship ready.Tarrant p. noon repair ''Seydlitz ship Group.Tarrant p. night ''Seydlitz battlecruisers lay anchor Jade roadstead	9
morning CET time section CET congruent perspective	9
hour GMT time zone work	9
ship towards Skagerrak speed	9
time Hipper flag ''Seydlitz newer battlecruiser ''Lützow	9
''Seydlitz place center line rear ''Derfflinger ''Moltke	9
II light cruiser Bödicker flagship torpedo boat II VI IX Flotillas Hipper battlecruisers	9
hour half Seas Fleet command Scheer left Jade force wa dreadnought	9
Seas Fleet wa IV light cruiser torpedo boat III V VII Flotillas light cruiser ''Rostock	9
pre-dreadnoughts II Squadron Elbe road battle fleet	9
Hipper force Beatty battlecruiser squadron	9
ship fire range .Bennett p. rangefinder misread range target salvo ship mile past battlecruisers	9
line battlecruisers deployed engage ''Seydlitz duel opposite line .Tarrant p. range ship ''Seydlitz s battery enter fray	9
wa ship 10th Destroyer Flotillas gun engage	9
battlecruisers battery battlecruisers.Tarrant p. Between ''Seydlitz wa struck caliber shell ''Queen	9
shell side ship foot battery deck number fire	9
shell barbette aft turret	9
propellant charge chamber fire turret magazine	9
anti-flash precaution put place explosion Dogger propellant explosion	9
turret wa destroyed gun crew blaze.Tarrant pp	9
ndash alt=A warship column smoke	9
destroyed salvo ''Von der Tann minute Beatty sought turn ship degree order regroup s 5th Squadron scene fire	9
battlecruisers turn ''Seydlitz ''Derfflinger concentrate fire ''Queen	9
Witnesses shell salvo hit ship intense explosion ripped ''Queen half.Tarrant pp	9
ndash destruction ''Queen destroyer torpedo attack line	9
torpedo hit ship fore turret aft month	9
explosion tore hole foot foot m × m slight list	9
damage ship wa maintain top speed kept position line.Tarrant p. ship battle fleet range ship trading shot battlecruisers ''Queen Elizabeth -class battleship	9
Between ''Seydlitz wa hit shell .Tarrant p. shell struck face port turret gun	9
mm shell aft turret cordite charge	9
ship mm gun gunfire rear turret right-hand gun.Tarrant p. wore visibility ship	9
''Seydlitz s commander ''Kapitän zur von Egidy Visibility become	9
wa dense mist rule flash enemy gun ship	9
u hostile line gun mist glimpse flash time time	9
Tarrant p. Beatty force body Fleet delay discovery Fleet location fleet ship towards line order force turn	9
Visibility favor battlecruisers paid price	9
minute ''Seydlitz wa hit time section ship	9
fire Beatty ship Hipper withdraw battlecruisers southwest.Tarrant p. ship withdrew ''Seydlitz water list starboard	9
ship wa middle deck fore compartment buoyancy.Tarrant p. Seas Fleet wa point battlecruisers Fleet	9
Scheer force darkness ship torpedo boat attack.Tarrant p. decision battleship body Fleet	9
development Scheer retreat pre-dreadnought battleship II Squadron dreadnought battlecruisers cover retreat ship fire.Tarrant p. Scheer ship turn point starboard bring pre-dreadnoughts relative safety side battle line.Tarrant pp	9
ndash ''Seydlitz battlecruisers move exception ''Lützow speed wa	9
put astern ''König .Tarrant pp	9
ndash Hipper ship moment respite uncertainty exact location course Scheer ship Jellicoe turn ship eastward towards thought wa path retreat.Tarrant p. fleet wa west Scheer turn course ship center fleet.Tarrant p. fleet intense fire line Scheer sent ''Seydlitz ''Von der Tann ''Moltke ''Derfflinger speed towards fleet attempt disrupt formation gain time force retreat.Tarrant p. battlecruisers point Scheer ship engage lead ship line.Tarrant p. ''Seydlitz hit ''Colossus minor damage ship superstructure.Tarrant p. minute battlecruisers retreat torpedo boat attack.Tarrant p. alt=A gray warship deck	9
Thick smoke pours funnel	9
in-photo caption read Seydlitz nach Skaggerak-schlacht Seydlitz Skaggerack battle	9
pause battle dusk ''Seydlitz battlecruisers cut wreckage gun fire repair fire control signal equipment searchlight nighttime action.Tarrant p. period fleet formation reverse order light force screen	9
gunfire Beatty attention battlecruisers westward	9
battlecruisers drew opening fire p. melee ''Seydlitz wa hit time shell struck rear gun turret hit ship bridge	9
bridge crew wa men tower wounded.Tarrant p. ship fire gun hit ''Lion ''Princess Royal darkness.Tarrant p. maneuvering battlecruisers Squadron turn westward avoid collision	9
brought pre-dreadnoughts II Squadron battlecruisers ship battlecruisers southward	9
battlecruisers fire battleship ship southwest bring gun bear ship	9
Hipper wa transfer ''Moltke ship steam towards head line.Tarrant p. ''Seydlitz ''Moltke condition comply ''Derfflinger ''Von der Tann ship	9
''Seydlitz ''Moltke process front line ship ''Stettin ship avoid collision	9
''Frauenlob ''Stuttgart ''München turn port contact Light Cruiser Squadron range cruiser side	9
Ludwig von Reuter attempt lure cruiser towards ''Moltke ''Seydlitz	9
cruiser broke attack.Tarrant pp	9
ndash light cruiser torpedo struck ''Frauenlob ship exploded.Tarrant p. formation disarray confusion ''Seydlitz sight ''Moltke	9
ship wa longer ''Moltke s knot herself proceed Horns Reef lighthouse	9
''Seydlitz wa thread way fleet wa dreadnought ship Destroyer	9
''Agincourt s captain want risk ship position pass.Battle Jutland Official Despatches p. ''Seydlitz slip fleet wa head safety Horns Reef.Tarrant p. Horns Reef	9
ship gyro-compasses light cruiser wa sent guide ship home	9
''Seydlitz wa condition bow wa buoyancy section ship wa broadside torpedo room	9
Preparations evacuate crew pair pump steamer scene	9
ship ''Seydlitz s ship limp port	9
outer Jade river morning ship Entrance III Lock	9
''Seydlitz water.Staff p. end battle Hipper report Scheer damage ship	9
time ''Derfflinger ''Von der Tann gun operation ''Moltke wa ton water ''Seydlitz wa damaged.Tarrant p. Hipper wa longer value engagement wa return harbor Commander-in-Chief await development Horns Reef battlefleet	9
course battle ''Seydlitz wa hit time heavy-caliber shell battery shell torpedo.Tarrant p. ship crew wounded.Tarrant p. ''Seydlitz herself battery shell hit	9