Leopold Wolfgang set Salzburg testimonial letter Leopold smooth passage	6
wa introduction Count Milan described Milan patron art	6
support vital success undertaking.Halliwell p. pair Innsbruck south Brenner Pass	6
Bolzano Rovereto Verona Mantua west towards Milan	6
Leopold plan journey family tour mdash travel accommodation cost met concert proceeds	6
winter journey Milan week weather stop	6
Leopold letter home inn room dog everything touch ice	6
concert receipt Leopold cost florin week.Halliwell p.146 unwise boasting profit tour Leopold wa detail	6
emphasise expense minimise Solomon p. example accept admiration bravo payment	6
ndash pause wa week spent Verona press Wolfgang concert pp	6
ndash Father son performance Guglielmi ''Ruggiero Wolfgang described letter Nannerl	6
boy portrait artist Saverio dalla Rosa	6
interlude wa shorter stop Mantua Wolfgang concert Accademia Filarmonica programme test ability performance sight reading improvisation	6
press review audience wa miracle music freak Nature cause born .Sadie pp	6
ndash Mantua snub Prince Thurn Taxis servant desire meet	6
Gutman surmise Prince Affligio affair musician place.Gutman pp	6
ndash contrast Count Arco family member Salzburg court Count Arco family Salzburg ten year administer kick Wolfgang appointment Salzburg court Gutman pp	6
pair Milan found monastery Marco Count palace.Halliwell pp	6
ndash Count Nicola Piccini opera ''Cesare Egitto .Zaslaw p. hospitality friendship Wolfgang edition work Pietro Metastasio writer librettist	6
series concert city Habsburg Archduke Ferdinand future patron composer	6
occasion Wolfgang set aria Metastasio text	6
Wolfgang write opening opera winter carnival season Milan Leopold might.Sadie p. p. Wolfgang receive fee florin rehearsal	6
Mozarts left Milan south towards Florence Rome return autumn letter recommendation	6
point tour Wolfgang composition	6
Accademia Filarmonica concert Mantua improvisation Wolfgang music composition phase tour aria concert contract carnival opera	6
''Se tutti i mali miei refers catalogue Mozart work Ludwig von time	6
number number catalogue number revision	6
''Misero ''Ah più tremar	6
Symphony G Rome Milan.Zaslaw p.	6