Supremes hit song artist Ray Drifters sock hop club talent show area	6
guidance group friend performer Jesse Greer quartet fan following.Wilson et al.	6
girl age-appropriate style wa collegiate dress doo-wop group Frankie Lymon TeenagersWilson et al. part Wilson lead song	6
month guitarist Marvin Tarplin wa Primettes lineup move distinguish group act girl lip-synch.Wilson et al.	6
talent contest Wilson et al.	6
Primettes sight set record	6
hope group upstart Motown label neighbor Miracles lead singer Smokey Robinson help group land audition Motown executive Gordy Jr.Wilson et al. proven songwriter.Wilson et al.	6
Robinson girl help guitarist Primettes permission Tarplin guitarist Miracles	6
Robinson Primettes audition ''a cappella Gordy Gordy girl artist return school	6
year Primettes Lupine Records label Tears Sorrow wa Baby .Wilson et al.	6
McGlown left group.Wilson et al.	6
youth Barbara Martin wa McGlown quick replacement	6
impression Gordy join Motown star Primettes U.S.A. studio day school.Wilson et al.	6
Gordy contribute hand clap background song Motown artist Marvin Gaye Wells.Wilson et al.	6
Gordy sign girl label condition change name group.Wilson et al.	6
Primes time Otis Williams Distants sign Motown Temptations.Wilson et al.	6
Gordy list name choose suggestion Darleens Sweet Ps Melodees Royaltones Jewelettes .Benjaminson	6
chose Supremes name disliked felt masculine	6
Rock Roll Hall Fame Museum	6
spring Martin left group start family	6
Supremes trio.Slonimsky Nicolas Laura Diane	6
ISBN 0-0286-5527-3 Between Supremes none position ''Billboard	6
Supremes Motown U.S.A. office Wilson et al. group compensate lack hit work studio hand clap backup Motown artist Marvin Gaye Temptations	6
year member turn lead Wilson ballad soulful hard-driving song mainstream pop song	6
material wa Gordy Smokey Robinson.Bronson	6
''Billboard Hits Songs Song Makers	6
ISBN 0-8230-7738-1 Lovelight Starts Eyes peaked number ''Billboard 100.Adrahtas	6
Lovelight wa Supremes song Motown production team Holland-Dozier-Holland.Wilson et al.	6
Gordy chose official lead singer group	6
Wilson solo Supremes album solo number People concert years.Wilson et al.	6
song wa Holland-Dozier-Holland Marvelettes	6
Supremes disliked song producer	6
Supremes part Clark ''Caravan Stars Did number US pop chart surprise delight group.Wilson et al.	6
wa song UK pop chart number	6
Did wa US number-one hit Baby wa number-one hit UK Me	6
Baby wa Grammy Award Rhythm Blues Me Hangin wa Grammy Pop	6