Plains Trail Native Americans ox cart traffic fur-trading post Fur Company.Gilman ''Red River Trails pp	3
fact company River ox cart haul fur	3
developed trail expedition Selkirk settlement flock sheep Assiniboine found trail well-marked.Gilman ''Red River Trails pp	3
River Settlement trail south upstream River west bank border	3
fur-trading post decade eighteenth century.Gilman ''Red River Trails pp	3
ndash Huck Fur Routes	3
traffic south river cart train west River border south cut corner southwest order intercept southbound trail	3
north-south trail River thirty mile km west.Gilman ''Red River Trails pp	3
upland west River route river confluence kept swampy flood-prone mosquito-ridden bottomland lakebed Agassiz river drained.Hess p. E–3 Gilman ''Red River Trails p.	3
North Dakota trail south-southeast River Fort Abercrombie Breckenridge Minnesota existence consequence passing cart traffic.Gilman ''Red River Trails p.	3
Breckenridge trail upstream east bank de Sioux Rivers continental divide Traverse	3
traffic lakeshore Traverse Gap continental divide side Stone source Minnesota River wa fur post west side Stone Roberts Dakota	3
Gilman ''Red River Trails pp	3
map ndash carter cut south de Sioux prairie Minnesota wet country Traverse Gap.Gilman ''Red River Trails pp	3
trail route side valley Minnesota River past fur post Lac qui Parle downstream location Sioux Sioux Agencies Fort ''Red River Trails pp	3
Fort trail struck prairie Minnesota River Traverse de Sioux modern-day Minnesota fur transshipped flatboats.Norman transship keelboat Traverse de Sioux carter diversion temptation settlement wa grow Saint	3
Gilman ''Red River Trails p.	3
year cart train east bank northeast river bottom upland Fort Mendota Minnesota River Mississippi.Gilman ''Red River Trails pp	3
fur River Saint market	3
trade Fort caravan trader River Mendota	3
effort Hudson ’ s Bay Company enforce monopoly fur trader avoid company jurisdiction border States	3
Norman fur-trading shipping enterprise Plains Trail six-cart train ''Red River Runs North	3
year train ox cart sent ’ s post territory reach Hudson ’ s Bay Company.Hess p. E–4	3
fur traffic wa route fort mission agency traffic Fort kept trail 1850s roads.Gilman ''Red River Trails pp	3