carter wa fur trade spouse	3
conveyance wa River ox cart simple vehicle carts.Gilman ''Red River Trails p. ''The Railway p.	3
cart wa wa material	3
wa wood animal hide	3
parallel oak shaft tram draft animal front frame cart rear	3
Cross-pieces held floorboard front side rear board rail box	3
wooden piece mortice tenon	3
wa cart strip wet bison hide Cree name ''shaganappi shrank	3
axle wheel foot diameter form shallow cone apex wa hub inboard rims.Fonseca	3
Excellent plan section found Brehaut	3
cart drawn horse Nations	3
cattle brought colony ox haul cart	3
strength endurance cloven hoof spread weight swampy areas.Piehl	3
supply shaganappi wood wa cart break half-dozen axle one-way trip	3
axle grease capture dust act sandpaper cart.Piehl ''The Railway p.	3
resultant squeal violin sobriquet North fiddle	3
visitor den wild beast hideousness .Berton ''The Railway p.	3
noise cart website Clay Minnesota Society	3
cart unsprung construction shock hump hollow trail.Gilman ''Red River Trails p.	3
Southbound cart fur packed 90-pound kg bundle fur trade '.Brehaut	3
cart handle pound kg .Fonseca	3
return trader staple trade Fort	3
direction cargo wa hide canvas	3
cart brigade ten cart driver overseer	3
brigade join train mile km length	3
Carts trail 1840s Christianson ''Minnesota Land Waters pp	3
cart train mile km hour twenty mile thirty km day	3
camp morning carter set prairie transit prairie place refuge '.Gilman ''Red River Trails p.	3
word mean wa term carter water point	3
Streams water wa deep cart wheel affixed cart assemblage wa hide form hull makeshift craft wa	3
trader ford stream end day start day time dry overnight	3
Streamside camp wood water protection hazard land	3
prairie time unrest trade time Dakota	3
Prairie fire driven wind risk dry spell	3
Wet weather river torrent approach stream bog worn path morasses.Gilman ''Red River Trails pp	3
Blizzards strand trader threaten starvation.Shepard Insects trader draft animal sleep them.Gilman ''Red River Trails p.	3
Game wa plentiful trader meat	3
saw boundless prairie colourful ocean grass summer storm awe-inspiring dangerous.Gilman ''Red River Trails pp	3
prairie grandeur week travel treeless steppe river lake wood Minnesota welcome relief.Gilman ''Red River Trails pp	3
week trail brigade Saint	3
carter camped bluff town riverfront	3
carter hill devil-may-care aspect garment barbaric adornment .Gilman ''Red River Trails p.	3
trader north host city village drinking whisky occupy half time worth citizen rest stranger	3
benefit trade separation carter camp village relation civil.Gilman ''Red River Trails pp	3
week trading wild carter north laden den blackguard wa Saint felt wa world	3
erstwhile host hand thought visitor frozen wilderness.Gilman ''Red River Trails pp	3
territorial Governor Alexander Ramsey Saint found stark treeless settlement crude building men	3
journeyed north part territory people grain territory	3
River Settlement inhabitant counting Nations stone fort church parsonage school	3
''Red River Runs North	3