1960s sought fleet tank Sherman V Firefly tank M3A1 half-tracks World	9
attempt procure equipment States secure M41 Walker Bulldogs M113 personnel carrier	9
States request equipment Argentine government side Plan Europa Plan action	9
wa technology stimulate Argentine industry country produce armament future	9
AMX-13 light tank F3s government manufacturing home	9
AMX-30 Leopard replacement Argentine Sherman fleet.Mazarrasa pp	9
Argentine Defense drew series requirement tank enter service	9
vehicle weigh tonne ton move maximum speed kilometer hour mph cover kilometer mi road	9
millimeter gun machine gun grenade launcher	9
tank designer account infrastructure railroad capacity bridge road capacity country varied terrain	9
''Proyecto de Tanque Argentino Mediano Medium Argentine Tank Project wa goal tank Argentine Army	9
experience technology Argentine government sought collaboration company contract company Thyssen-Henschel	9
contract transfer technology program tank line government requirement team Argentine engineer	9
wa use hull Marder personnel carrier Mazarrasa pp	9
chassis wa support weight TAM	9
prototype Bishop p. put year road range kilometer mi	9
prototype wa investigation vehicle prototype contract.Miller p. tank firepower requirement met fitting Royal Ordnance L7A1 mm gun	9
gun wa L7A2 Rheinmetall Rh-105-30 mm	9
gun FM ''Modelo p. Rh-105-30 advantage include weight compact size lethality	9
Rh-105-30 FM doe muzzle brake	9
built cannon degree -7 degree TAM.Foss ''Jane Tank Recognition p. gun hydraulic recoil mechanism ha range millimeter absorb tonne recoil force.Mazarrasa p. fire M735A1 armor fin sabot penetrate maximum millimeter meter ft	9
fire anti-tank round squash head smoke rounds.Mazarrasa p. tank armament include millimeter FN MAG purpose machine gun FN MAG TAM turret roofMazarrasa p. anti-air machine gun	9
fire control system Nd YAG laser range meter ft. FLER-HG computer compute gun fire gunner aim hit target	9
tank commander PERI-R/TA panoramic periscope zoom.Mazarrasa p. TAM engine requirement weight volume fast rate acceleration reliability	9
program chose MTU MB-833 diesel engine horsepower rotation minute	9
TAM power weight ratio horsepower tonne maximum speed kilometer hour mph road kilometer hour mph off-road.Mazarrasa pp	9
680-liter fuel tank TAM travel kilometer mi	9
range kilometer mi vehicle fuel tank gal .Miller p. TAM transmission Renk HSWL-204 hydrodynamic torque converter	9
brake system hydraulic disk brake roadwheels suspension torsion bar	9
Foss ''Jane Armour Artillery p. TAM survivability dependent profile turret Leopard Leopard Mazarrasa p. armor arrayed	9
ha millimeter degree glacis plate degree vehicle side	9
offer protection anti-armor shell millimeter guns.Mazarrasa p. turret front millimeter steel armor angle degrees.Mazarrasa p. tank weight armor protection light battle tank ha advantage mobility nation terrain.Schneider p. venture Rheinmetall Landsysteme built prototype	9
PERI R12 periscope Leopard tank commander	9
gunner loader day periscope	9
crew fire night light level television LLLTV camera elevation gun wa mantlet	9
tank wa horsepower kW engine	9
improvement program provision increase thickness armor protection	9