occupation World II development vehicle clandestine research recover ground liberation mid-1944.Ogorkiewicz p. occupation armour program wa state workshop de Construction de Rueil ARL design production ARL wa Mazarrasa p. tank wa Maybach HL-230 engine tank gun.de Mazarrasa pp	9
vehicle wa battle tank firepower engine power distinct disadvantage track design	9
year Tank Regiment Army.de Mazarrasa p. ARL wa stop-gap vehicle Army force inception work tank	9
tank wa manufacturer de Construction d'Issy-les-Moulineaux AMX ''Forges et Chantiers de la Méditerranée FCM Renault ''Societe Lorraine de SLD-Lorraine ''Societé d'Outillage Mécanique et d'Usinage d'Artillerie SOMUA	9
vehicle wa post-war requirement battle tank	9
vehicle wa AMX hull suspension Panther tank Army immediate post-war.Miller pp	9
government specification tank Panther tank heavier Tiger Army wa tank protection firepower latter.Jeudy p. design tank Maybach engine model torsion bar sprung road wheel AMX number unique features.Ogorkiewicz pp	9
example turret trunnions wa kind	9
turret part wa trunnions part turret ring	9
gun wa part gun elevation depression fire control equipment installation system.Ogorkiewicz p. contractor Renault withdrew program government AMX SOMUA continue development	9
prototype M4s AMX prototype SOMUA Mazarrasa pp	9
AMX prototype wa cannon prototype wa gun wa put AMX production standard medium tank reason arrival aid States form M47 Patton Zaloga p. program abandoned.Miller p. wa turn program tank project tank gun prototype built wa failure design engine	9
Char Batignolles-Châtillon demise AMX program thought medium tank.Jeudy p. wa rearm Germans entertain concept force host low-cost light tank quantity lack armament parity medium tank	9
prospect thousand Germans adopt idea plan create light tank Type division wa	9
enterprise design requirement wa Char Batignolles-Châtillon	9
medium tank prototype latter wa produce tank first-rate gun steel equivalence weight constraint	9
interest medium tank concept	9
WEU defence workgroup FINBEL Netherlands Belgium Luxembourg representative Staffs Spielberger p. set specification medium tank tank	9
year workgroup FINABEL ''Allemagne Colomb-Béchar agreement wa collaborate building tank.Jeudy p. FINABEL nation type wa ''Europa-Panzer indicate nature expert country design process.Spielberger p. specification FINABEL p. tank lightweight mobile battle tank weight limit ability armour vehicle.Ogorkiewicz pp	9
engineer conference Bonn requirement future tank	9
maximum width height tank gun developed Franco-German research institute Saint Louis.Mercillon p. tank petrol engine torsion bar suspension hydraulic shock power-to-weight ratio /metric ton road range	9
project material contribution war tank design bureau	9
year ministry defence contract country manufacture prototype separately.de Mazarrasa p. year project setback de power Fifth treaty point development weapon de refuse bomb order interest tank project	9
prototype developed de Construction d'Issy-les-Moulineaux direction Molinié ''Direction de Études et Fabrications d'Armements DEFA ''Direction Technique de Armements Terrestres Foss p. AMX head engineer Heissler prototype wa range finder track	9
vehicle turret deliberate imitation T-54 Sofam petrol engine	9
sleeker turret cast p. Work prototype wa team Team Porsche Maschinenbau Luther Jung.Jerchel p. Team B wa Ruhrstahl Henschel.Jerchel pp	9
Wood mock-up prototype Team .Jerchel p.	9