B movie production house exploitation era company field situation	5
cheap genre picture release cost dollar movie studio production genre movie audience expectation spectacular action sequence effect	5
Intimations trend evident ''Airport mega-schlock ''The Poseidon Adventure ''The Inferno	5
disaster plot dialogue B-grade industry perspective picture tradition star-stuffed extravaganza	5
''The Exorcist power big-budget horror	5
tidal shift focus success film Spielberg creature feature ''Jaws Lucas space opera ''Star Wars turn become highest-grossing film motion picture history	5
''Superman studio spend movie child book character turn profit—it wa top box-office hit part ''Box Office Mojo website	5
Blockbuster fantasy spectacle sway conglomerate rule.See post-system era record sale merger studio Age	5
decade half production cost feature decline inflation	5
inflation rate expense continue soar.Finler p.	5
Prince production cost cost manufacturing exhibition print marketing p.	5
''Box Office Mojo website production figure	5
saturation thousand theater wa outfit secure exhibition commitment turn profit	5
feature history—almost revival house	5
casualty regime wa B studio Artists bankruptcy	5
1970s AIP production film ''Amityville Horror ''Meteor	5
studio wa concern end pp	5
pressure distribution obstacle risk number genre movie studio filmmaker theater	5
Horror wa low-budget genre time slasher mode ''The Massacre feminist author	5
film wa World budget pp	5
Corman World Horizons Concorde–New Horizons primary company	5
Horizons movie set punk scene Penelope Spheeris	5
''The Times review ''Suburbia genre film	5
Note state wa World	5
Cohen twist genre convention picture ''Q aka ''Q Serpent kind movie market low-budget picture resource people job	5
Line put ''Polyester Waters movie budget old-school exploitation gimmick Odorama	5
stylish horror movie le Detroit.Cost Campbell Warren p. writer director producer ''The Book Raimi wa week shy twenty-second birthday star producer Campbell wa	5
''tour de force Chute ''Los Herald-Examiner Warren p. wa picked distribution Line ''The Evil hit	5
B studio wa survivor heyday exploitation era Troma Pictures	5
Troma production ''Class Nuke 'Em ''Redneck Zombies ''Surf Nazis Must Die exploitation absurdist spin	5
Troma production ''The Toxic Avenger hero Toxie symbol Troma icon B movie	5
B studio startup decade wa Empire Pictures production ''Ghoulies theater	5
video rental market wa B film economics Empire model profit rental video store.Morrow p.	5
number Concorde–New Horizon release route briefly theater	5
growth cable television industry support low-budget film industry B movie wound filler material cable channel purpose	5