transformation industry production cost feature film wa million—after inflation le percent	5
twin bill B film subsequent-run film theater	5
genre package wa model	5
Levine sword-and-sandals import ''Hercules neighborhood theater	5
suspense film ''Terror Is Man ran co-feature sort exploitation gimmick dénouement bell eye	5
year Roger Corman AIP road ten-day black-and-white horror film play feature finance horror film color	5
''House Usher typifies ambiguity B picture classification	5
wa film standard director studio schedule budget Corman	5
B movie schedule wa fifteen day budget industry Corman Di Franco p. time thumbnail definition B movie le minute	5
loosening industry censorship constraint 1960s saw expansion viability variety B movie subgenres ''exploitation film	5
combination publicity movie vulgar subject matter imagery decades—the term fringe production depth Poverty Row system	5
wage sin context prudent lifestyle choice hygiene	5
Audiences explicit footage anything birth circumcision.Schaefer pp	5
film part movie theater schedule event roadshow promoter fodder grindhouses schedule	5
promoter Kroger Babb wa vanguard marketing low-budget film % saturation campaign target audience ad medium.Schaefer p.	5
era feature exploitation film B movie	5
B production promotion standard practice end industry exploitation way refer field low-budget genre film	5
1960s theme imagery become realm B	5
Exploitation movie sense Goods cautionary tale lady boyfriend ’ s promiscuity lead venereal disease grotesque closeup VD effect	5
review DVD release analysis Bill part ''DVD Verdict website	5
time concept fringe exploitation wa tradition “ nudie film footage striptease artist Page softcore pornography decade	5
''This Nude World wa Film	5
1950s grindhouse theater adult product filmmaker nudies attention plot	5
wa Russ Meyer nudie ''The Teas	5
year sub- budget Meyer ''Lorna film sex gritty realism violence	5
director Meyer gain renown sexploitation picture ''Faster Pussycat	5
film fringe circuit adult theater AIP teen movie wink-wink title ''Beach Blanket Bingo ''How Stuff Annette Funicello Frankie Avalon played drive-in venue	5
Roger Corman ''The Trip veteran AIP/Corman actor Nicholson show breast flirt nudity	5
Meyer Corman line closer	5
film era Bs wa ''Psycho	5
earnings production cost movie p.	5
mainstream distribution Production Code seal approval weaken film censorship	5
note move horror genre director Hitchcock wa film career star	5
impact wa schlock horror movie second-tier director Castle bill scarier ''Psycho	5
Castle film ''Psycho vein wa ''Homicidal step development slasher subgenre 1970s	5
''Blood Feast movie human dismemberment culinary preparation nudie-maker Gordon subgenre gore splatter film	5
business partner Friedman publicity vomit bag theatergoers—the sort gimmick Castle mastered—and injunction film Sarasota Florida—the sort problem exploitation film Friedman it.Rockoff pp	5
breed gross-out movie typifies sense exploitation —the progressive adoption exploitation nudie element horror B genre low-budget film industry	5
Imports Hammer Film explicit horror movie gialli picture sexploitation ultraviolence fuel trend	5
Production Code wa version rating system	5
year horror film direction cinema decade consequence B movie	5
wa high-budget production Roman Polanski	5
B horror veteran Castle Baby genre up-market time	5
wa success year seventh-biggest hit	5
wa Romero weekend Pittsburgh	5
Building achievement B genre predecessor ''Invasion Body Snatchers exploration issue thriller allegory conflict	5
influence clever subversion genre clichés connection imagery low-cost mean production profitability.Cook p.	5
Code X rating studio film Cowboy show adult imagery market hardcore pornography	5
context work Russ Meyer legitimacy	5
time Meyer film ''Finders Keepers Lovers Weepers	5
wa ''The Times .Canby	5
Corman sexploitation picture ''Private Duty Nurses ''Women Cages	5
exploitation movie Cannes Film Festival	5
significance owes fact wa budget studio	5
project wa cocreators Fonda	5
Fonda become AIP top star ''The Angels biker movie ''The Trip LSD	5
idea Fonda combine proven theme	5
AIP wa collaborator Hopper studio alumnus rein	5
financing distribution deal graduate Corman/AIP exploitation mill project Nicholson cinematographer László	5
film favorite exploitation theme redneck menace fair amount nudity wa brought cost	5
''Easy Rider rental film bridge tendency schlock/kitsch/hack dawn mainstream cinema seventy	5
Quote Cagin Dray p.	5
history Cagin Dray pp	5
figure associate producer Hayward p.	5