production cost feature wa increase ten year	5
number company turn decade firm Producers Corporation PRC Poverty Row hierarchy Monogram	5
feature universal wa exhibition model percent theater double-billing others policy part-time.Schatz p.	5
1940s pressure studio block package picture	5
Restrictions ability enforce blind bidding.Schatz pp	5
factor progressive shift production studio B movie supplier	5
Genre picture cost backbone Poverty Row Monogram budget	5
Poverty Row firm distribution exchange percent rental receipt	5
producer O. Selznick brought bloated-budget spectacle ''Duel market promotion release	5
distribution strategy wa success wa movie quality.Schatz p.	5
''Duel release practice B-movie industry 1950s top studio standard decade B movie hit	5
Considerations beside cost line B movie	5
Films shot B-level budget picture sleeper hit film wa ''Hitler Children RKO thriller fraction	5
rental industry language distributor share box office receipts.Jewell Lasky	5
realm film noir picture echoed style cheaper film	5
Programmers exhibition role definition case confusion	5
B movie star fact part programmer run-of-the-mill movie Bs sense quality	5
feature exhibition mode—it wa standard policy percent theater part-time percent.Schatz p.	5
Poverty Row firm broaden scope Monogram subsidiary Artists distribute film producer	5
time effort rubric.Schatz pp	5
PRC wa Eagle-Lion company entry market	5
Warners Bs Brian Foy wa production chief.Schatz p. p. essay Mike Haberfelner part re Search Trash website	5
1940s RKO stood industry focus B picture	5
perspective studio Age B unit Val horror unit RKO	5
moody film ''Cat People ''I Zombie ''The Body Snatcher Jacques Tourneur Wise others become career retrospect	5
movie described film noir— Stranger Floor B—was RKO release thriller stylish vein	5
studio number movie noir 1940s	5
film noirs A-level production 1940s picture mode programmer type straight bottom bill	5
decade cheap entertainment time become product e.g. Choice DVD ''The Times Choice DVD ''The Times Film Noir Lite Actions Consequences ''The Times Week Review	5
sample year RKO addition noir programmer picture straight B noirs ''Desperate ''The Devil Thumbs Ride	5
Ten B noirs year Poverty Row three—Republic Monogram PRC/Eagle-Lion—and Screen	5
eighteen B noirs dozen noir programmer Hollywood.For consideration B noir Lyons ''Death B Movies Film Noir Da Capo	5
RKO representative output Spitfire Lum Abner comedy series thriller Saint Falcon Westerns Tim Holt Tarzan movie Johnny Weissmuller	5
Jean Hersholt played film	5
''The wa standard entry course hour screen time physician cure spinal meningitis demonstrate benevolence towards set example wayward youth calm passion maid	5
Poverty Row budget le palliative fare	5
major-league respectability cheap Westerns wa studio Monogram exploitation picture juvenile delinquency exposé Are Children	5
prison film ''Women Bondage .Schatz p.	5
PRC ''The Devil Wheels brought teenager rod death	5
studio house auteur crew rein director Edgar G. Ulmer wa Capra PRC	5
Ulmer film generic stripe ''Girls Chains wa month ''Women Bondage end year Ulmer Junction ''Isle Forgotten Sins Seas adventure set brothel	5