ruling suit block theater chain	5
audience television studio production schedule feature vanished theater 1950s	5
studio benefit offering movie feature place B films.Strawn p.	5
television Westerns series market B oaters wa	5
feature production cost 1940s turn decade—a percent rise inflation	5
prominent victim market wa Eagle-Lion film	5
Monogram brand company identity higher-end subsidiary Artists	5
year B series Westerns	5
Non-series B Westerns year Pictures cheap sagebrush saga wa business decade end	5
genre Universal kept Ma series Artists stuck Bowery Boys p.	5
RKO year mismanagement movie industry p.	5
product wa longer—the top ten box-office release minute length top ten wa Finler pp	5
Finler list ''The Country Girl money	5
''The Year Itch replaces analysis film length	5
age feature film wa past minute wa minimum	5
Age–style feature wa ''B movie wa refer low-budget genre film performer B actor	5
term suggestion movie formulaic plot stock character type action comedy	5
time realm B movie wa fertile territory experimentation	5
Ida Lupino actress herself sole female director era	5
low-budget picture production company Filmakers Lupino taboo subject rape ''Outrage self-explanatory ''The Bigamist	5
effort ''The Hitch-Hiker RKO release film noir woman.See e.g. Eddie Muller ''Dark World Film Noir Martin p.	5
year RKO put film cost ''Split concludes test range noir	5
movie ''Kiss Me typifies murky middle ground B picture programmer half neighbourhood theatre double-bill	5
distributor Artists programmer production budget	5
film length minute level star Meeker film	5
source pure pulp Mickey Spillane Mike Hammer novel direction	5
result brutal genre picture evokes anxiety wa spoken Bomb	5
fear war le qualm radioactive fallout test era genre film	5
Science fiction horror hybrid importance low-budget end business	5
down-market film type—like Alland Universal e.g. ''Creature Black Lagoon e.g. ''It Came Beneath simple diversion	5
genre nature cover mordant observation mainstream movie	5
Director Don Siegel ''Invasion Body Snatchers Artists treat conformist pressure evil banality fashion.Lev pp	5
''The Colossal Man Bert I. Gordon monster movie happens depict horrific effect radiation exposure cold-war spin army secrecy post-war growth	5
''The Colossal Man wa company name wa budget	5
Pictures AIP Nicholson Samuel Z. Arkoff reorganization Corporation ARC studio B-cost production	5
original-release bill package film movie low-budget rate percentage basis films.Strawn p. Lev p.	5
''I Was Teenage Werewolf AIP film era	5
title suggests studio genre subject angle	5
''Hot Rod Gang rod horror	5
Result ''Ghost Dragstrip Hollow	5
AIP way exploitation target marketing saturation become standard procedure planning mass-market 'event film p.	5
movie Bros. Youth MGM ''High School Mamie Van Doren	5
filmmaker Roger Corman screen credit writer associate producer Artists Dragnet	5
Corman movie ''The Monster Floor budget schedule.Di Franco p.	5
film Corman official ARC release ''Apache Woman ''Day World half Arkoff Nicholson twin-bill package	5
Corman fifty feature film	5
Bs Corman ha way 'B movie life B movie wa picture	5
prefers describe metier low-budget exploitation film	5
Corman B Arkoff ''Apache Woman displeasure wa feature Strawn p.	5
year Corman AIP head company help launch career Francis Coppola Jonathan Demme Towne Niro others	5
1950s Castle innovator B movie publicity gimmick	5
Audiences ''Macabre production Artists insurance policy cover death fright	5
creature feature ''The Tingler Castle gimmick Percepto film climax buzzer select theater seat rattle audience member appropriate scream appropriate laughter.Heffernan pp	5
film Castle combine saturation advertising campaign Universal Alland package publicity stunt gimmick purview exhibitor	5
postwar drive-in theater boom wa vital B movie industry	5
drive-in States decade p.	5
picture simple plot shock effect film attendant distraction	5
phenomenon drive-in movie symbol culture 1950s	5
time television station B genre film slot notion midnight movie	5
American-made genre film movie cost dubbed market	5
distributor Levine footage actor Raymond Burr wa sci-fi horror film ''Godzilla	5
Hammer Film Productions ''The Curse Frankenstein ''Dracula influence future horror film style	5
Levine Embassy Pictures bought worldwide right ''Hercules cheaply movie bodybuilder Reeves	5
top purchase price Levine spent advertising publicity amount.Cook p.	5
''The Times wa movie drawn yawn film market country barrage publicity	5
Levine first-weekend box office profit film cinema week word-of-mouth withdrew	5
''Hercules theater strategy wa success film rental	5
decade movie exploitation philosophy Levine	5