1960s 1970s generation low-budget film company drew line exploitation sci-fi teen theme mainstay 1950s	5
Operations Roger Corman World Pictures Cannon Films Line Cinema brought exploitation film mainstream theater country	5
studio top product wa inflate time—in ten earner minutes.See Finler p. top film	5
''The Owl Pussycat minute shorter replaces analysis	5
Bs pace Corman producorial hand movie minute	5
played part film AIP World length wa minutes.From ''Apache Woman ''The Beast Million Eyes ''Day World ''The Guns	5
''Angels Die ''Bloody Mama ''The Horror ''Ivanna aka ''Scream Demon Lover ''The Student Nurses	5
purchase ''Ivanna Di Franco p.	5
film turn tidy profit	5
World release biker movie ''Angels Die cost produce box office.Di Franco p.	5
studio low-budget field leader exploitation growth	5
shot director Brian Palma	5
''Sisters Pauline limp technique doe seem matter people want gore e people order simple expository point drabbest picture	5
example blaxploitation genre story drug violent crime prostitution product AIP	5
blaxploitation star wa Pam career bit part Russ Meyer ''Beyond Dolls	5
World picture ''The Doll ''The Bird Cage Hill	5
Hill performance AIP blaxploitation film ''Coffy ''Foxy	5
ha distinction movie climax castration scene	5
Blaxploitation wa exploitation genre studio	5
Artists release ''Cotton Comes Ossie Davis film type	5
movie blaxploitation phenomenon wa ''Sweet Sweetback Baadasssss Song example form experimental borderline manifesto revolution	5
Melvin Van Peebles music film wa loan Bill Cosby.Van Peebles	5
distributor wa Cinemation Industries dubbed version ''Mondo Cane shockumentaries skin flick ''Fanny Hill in-house production ''The Man O.R.G.Y	5
sort film played grindhouses day—many outright porno theater venue manner exploitation cinema	5
day quicky nickel continuity spirit wa evident	5
low-budget crime drama shot mm first-time director Barbara won critic prize Film Festival	5
''Wanda event film movement B picture	5
plot seedy straightforward exploitation film old-school B noir	5
sub- production spent year money wa Vincent Canby absolute accuracy effect decency point view purity technique	5
production cost Schickel p.	5
essay Bérénice Reynaud part ''Sense Cinema website	5
Romero Van Peebles filmmaker era picture gut-level entertainment exploitation biting commentary	5
feature Cohen ''Bone ''Black Caesar ''Hell blaxploitation movie Cohen vehicle examination race relation wage dog-eat-dog capitalism	5
gory horror film ''Deathdream Bob Clark protest war	5
filmmaker Cronenberg low-budget horror film implication ''Shivers ''Rabid ''The Brood	5
''Easy Rider rigor movie way exploitation content treatment film year wa Artists ''Electra Glide e.g. Milne ''Electra Glide ''Time Film ed. ed	5
''The Times reviewer thought intention decent grade-C Roger Corman bike movie—though Corman ha director Guercio	5
1970s practice nonmainstream motion picture show goal building cult film audience brought midnight movie concept home cinema drive-in movie hip.See e.g. Stevenson ''Land Balconies Discoveries Confessions B-Movie Archaeologist Manchester UK Vision pp	5
Joanne Hollows Masculinity Cult Cult Movies Politics Taste ed	5
Mark Manchester UK Manchester Press pp	5
Janet Staiger ''Blockbuster TV Must-see Sitcoms Network Era Press p.	5
film circuit wa three-year-old	5
midnight movie success low-budget picture studio system Waters Flamingos campy spin exploitation development film movement	5
''The Horror Picture Show film Century-Fox spoofed manner B picture clichés hit wa show feature year release	5
''Rocky Horror phenomenon midnight movie	5
martial art film import 1970s	5
kung fu film martial art States movie audience AIP World	5
Roger Ebert review Horror exploitation film turn profit brought right price	5
provide place filmmaker project ground	5
movie consideration wa ''The Chain Saw Massacre	5
Tobe Hooper horror film film cost Rockoff p.	5
influence Sapolsky Molitor p. Rubin p.	5
''Halloween budget worldwide slasher flick horror primary mode decade	5
Hooper Romero work ''Halloween turn model ''Black Christmas ''Deathdream Bob Clark.For film cost worldwide Harper pp	5
influence debt ''Black Christmas Rockoff p.	5
television parallel series mainstay prime-time series film day	5
1970s feature-length echo B movie	5
production TV movie introduction ''ABC Movie Week dedication network slot feature time factor medium B picture territory	5
Television film ''The Ordeal Patty month release prison way movie ''Human Wreckage ''When Grows Cold FBO picture wake celebrity misfortune	5
1970s TV ''The Martin genre picture type B production	5
''Nightmare straight realm road-tripping-girls-in-redneck-bondage exploitation	5
reverberation ''Easy Rider felt picture host exploitation film	5
influence fate B movie wa le	5
studio genre bargain basement	5
Baby hit exploitation style	5
Bros. ''The Exorcist horror film absolute blockbuster wa movie year highest-earning horror movie	5
description film gross-out mode expression mainstream cinema ast exploitation film exploit cruelty virtue marginality	5
end decade exploitation strategy opening film thousand theater standard industry practice	5
Writer-director Lucas Universal production something	5
teenybopper pic lot spit wa film highest-earning movie made.Paul p.	5
movie B theme A-level backing wake	5