studio resistant B feature	5
B unit provide film second-feature market	5
Block standard practice access studio picture theater rent company output season	5
B film fee box office percentage basis film rate set profitability B movie	5
parallel practice blind bidding freed Bs le block exhibitor picture sight	5
studio — Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Pictures Fox Film Corporation Century Fox Bros. RKO Radio Pictures descendant FBO — company theater chain bottom line	5
Poverty Row studio outfit Mascot Pictures Tiffany Pictures Sono Art-World Pictures operation B movie production film	5
position block book distribution exclusivity state right firm turn block movie exhibitor picture star relative status Poverty Row .Taves pp	5
major-minors — Universal Studios Pictures — production line top Poverty Row studio	5
contrast minor theater major-league-level film distribution exchanges.See e.g. Balio pp	5
standard Age model industry top product film number select first-run house city	5
described historian Epstein film review publicity word mouth principal form advertising	5
wa subsequent-run market feature	5
venue movie turn basis	5
thousand theater program time week	5
meet demand B product end Poverty Row stream micro-budget movie sixty minute quicky tight production schedules—as days.Taves p.	5
Brian Taves describes poorest theater house city program action schedule offering quicky nickel show	5
theater saw big-studio film movie state right concern Poverty Row product	5
Millions Americans theater matter course picture trailer screen preview arrival film title marquee listing newspaper advertising movie	5
introduction sound driven cost feature film cost produce.Finler p.	5
range motion picture B category	5
studio clear-cut B film movie programmer in-betweeners intermediate prestige theater material bill programmer show top bottom marquee	5
Taves article adopts usage programmer author Don study ''B Movies Ballantine	5
Taves note term ''programmer wa variety way reviewer p. n.	5
present-day critic employ Miller–Taves usage others refer B movie Age programmer program picture	5
Poverty Row Bs budget petty cash film cost bottom industry	5
mid-1930s feature wa dominant exhibition model	5
B movie production Bros. wa percent studio output	5
unit wa Bryan Foy Bs	5
Fox half production line B territory Sol Wurtzel wa charge twenty movie year	5
number top Poverty Row firm Sono Art company create Monogram Pictures decade	5
Monogram Mascot studio form Pictures	5
Into 1950s Monogram product wa par end output	5
sturdy Poverty Row concerns—with penchant sobriquet Empire churn quickies.See Taves pp	5
Joel Finler ha length feature release studio relative emphasis B production Artists distribution film outfit Finler pp	5
Taves estimate half film B movie	5
film Poverty Row firm percent movie decade thousand picture Bs.Taves p.	5
wa predominant B genre lesser degree p.	5
Film historian Jon Tuska ha 'B product Thirties—the Universal film Mix Maynard feature Buck Tim McCoy RKO O'Brien series Westerns Mesquiteers perfection well-made story	5
end industry Poverty Row Ajax put oaters Carey fifty	5
outfit Range Rider series Rider series Morton action thriller	5
low-budget oater era studio system concept all-midget cast ''The Terror Town wa success picked distribution.Taves p.	5
Series genre recurrent character name actor role decade sound film	5
Fox B series instance Chan mystery Ritz Brothers comedy child star Jane e.g. Taves p.	5
series attract people—a theater part-time feature matinee film mature audience night	5
word industry report afternoon moviegoer housewife child want quantity money crowd want	5
Series film B movie category ambiguity MGM example series Hardy chronicle star budget A-level lesser majors.Naremore p.	5
series lesser standard B budget wa reach Poverty Row Pictures Tarzan Police Dog series proud name Dog Features.Taves p.	5