Jury Gilbert Sullivan opera played act work W. Gilbert spoken dialogue	4
Gilbert Sullivan opera number pattern	4
example ''The Yeomen Guard begin chorus number.Bradley p. Jury opera end finale chorus number solo principal character	4
Comes broken flower part	4
wa string meditative lyric happiness sadness acceptance resignation .Stedman p. point character Savoy opera scene stop life contrast foolishness scenes.Stedman pp	4
ndash tenor aria Jury tenor aria Savoy opera set time comedienne parody Gilbert Sullivan Opera re-issue history Shepherd Marc ''A Gilbert Sullivan Discography tenor tradition ''must aria time instrument	4
Masterworks Mono LP ML4594/ML4733 Jury hypocrisy character motivation held satire Gilbert mock absurdity judicial procedure	4
Gilbert scholar Andrew Crowther explains Gilbert combine criticism entertainment render time truth joke show accept premise	4
Crowther p. become Gilbert work.Crowther pp	4
ndash judge song friend wa Bar wa string patter song epitomise Gilbert Sullivan collaboration.Bradley p. personage supply biography himself.Fitzgerald pp	4
Gilbert play ''The Palace Truth song character reveal innermost thought egotism vanity baseness cruelty .Crowther p. p. Crowther point revelation work Jury people character opera/operetta communicate deeper level truth speech	4
friend judge outline path corruption judge set pattern patter song Gilbert Sullivan opera	4
Gilbert innovation found ''Thespis Jury Savoy opera use chorus part action	4
opera burlesque comedy chorus impact plot noise ornament	4
Gilbert Sullivan opera chorus part action character right.Dark pp	4
ndash Sullivan Gilbert matter hand chorus dummy concern nothing part stage	4
wa 'Thespis Gilbert carry determination chorus play proper part performance	4
moment realise idea chorus anything sort stage audience wa time novelty	4
Gilbert innovation example mentor T. W. wa costume set Stedman p. Gilbert scenery production Clerkenwell Sessions law p. costume bridesmaid wedding attire	4
attention detail careful creation set scene Gilbert stage management Gilbert work.Crowther p. instance set ''H.M.S	4
Pinafore Gilbert Sullivan Portsmouth inspect ship	4
St Vincent model set carpenter work from.Stedman pp	4
Crowther p. wa standard procedure drama naturalism wa concept author influence play libretto staged.Crowther pp	4