Cage underwent crisis 1940s.Nicholls p.	6
addition problem life Cage deal trouble divorce wife ten year change sexuality	6
detail topic Marjorie Perloff Junkerman ''John Cage Press	6
composition public Pritchett p. idea art communication	6
account reason misunderstood composer wa language	6
found people wa wa something .John Cage interview Johnatan Cott	6
Cage met Sarabhai musician States influence music country	6
Sarabhai spend month US music	6
lesson counterpoint music Cage teach taught music return.Cage p.	6
Sarabhai Cage music philosophy	6
purpose music Sarabhai teacher wa sober mind divine influence Cage pp	6
definition cornerstone Cage view music art	6
time Cage art historian Ananda Coomaraswamy	6
idea Cage wa description rasa permanent emotion	6
emotion group humor wonder heroic— experience Cage word anger fear disgust sorrow	6
''navarasas ''navrasas emotion tendency towards ''navarasas tranquility.Cage p.	6
Cage piece relate emotion exists correspondence them.Pritchett p.	6
piece bell-like sound suggest others drum-like resonance suggest East .Cage booklet text cycle ''John Cage Sonatas Interludes Composers Recordings CRI reissue	6
excerpt Sonata II music .Perry p	6
Cage Sonata XVI cycle	6
idea collection piece wa poet Edwin Denby piece piece .Cage Pritchett p.	6
choice material technique piano preparation ''Sonatas Interludes dependent improvisation Cage cycle wa piano difference choice .Cage pp	6
ndash essay ''Composition Process	6
Cage description process time refers piano preparation composition	6
account metaphor process shell beach.Cage p.	6
Work project wa Cage break compose ''The Seasons ballet act idea philosophy	6
''The Seasons Cage ''Sonatas Interludes wa	6
Cage ''Sonatas Interludes Maro pianist friend	6
work time performance cycle Carnegie Hall	6
occasion 1940s 1950s Cage	6
reaction wa ''The Times review Carnegie Hall concert Pritchett p. work left Cage country composer	6
success ''Sonatas Interludes grant Guggenheim Foundation Cage trip	6
met Messiaen performance work student Pierre Boulez admirer work lecture performance salon Suzanne Tézenas Paris.For detail text Boulez lecture Pierre Boulez Cage Samuels Jean-Jacques Nattiez ''The Boulez-Cage Correspondence Samuels Cambridge Press	6
living Cage Quartet Parts work philosophy	6