IV legitimate issue Clarence Throne IV person throne.Ashley p.	7
extravagant brother wa pomp ceremony	7
contrast IV spend time Windsor Castle wa reign walk	7
Reform Crisis wa people saw down-to-earth brother.Allen pp	7
business ten minute IV days.Van der Kiste p.	7
Lord described excellent man business question help understand matter—whereas IV ask question display ignorance III ask wait response.Somerset p.	7
Lady Charlotte accession Hitherto ha effort thing instance	7
diarist Eden immense improvement animal den Windsor	7
man ''wishes everybody everything ha ha benevolent	7
Van der Kiste p.	7
brother chef band public approval	7
IV painting collection nation royal stud	7
IV renovation Palace brother reside palace Army barrack Parliament Houses Parliament p.	7
informality residence Royal Pavilion send hotel list guest invite anyone knew dinner invitee bother clothes	7
Queen doe nothing embroider flower dinner	7
throne forget illegitimate child eldest son Munster child precedence son daughter marquess	7
child opportunity element press impudence rapacity FitzJordans	7
Post Ziegler p.158 relationship son wa series savage painful quarrel money honours.Ziegler pp	7
daughter hand ornament court society way princess	7
time death monarch election election Tories ground Whigs Tories number seat	7
Tories wa Commons Lord government	7
Lord reform system change fifteenth century	7
inequity system example town Manchester member part county constituency boroughs—known pocket Old Sarum voter member Parliament	7
borough aristocrat nominee constituents—who secret ballot wa election	7
Landowners seat sell candidates.Ziegler pp	7
Commons Reform Bill Lord ministry dissolve Parliament lead election	7
exercise prerogative dissolve Parliament election held year country wa state excitement boil violence	7
wa conduct Opposition intention move passage Address resolution Lords dissolution	7
Opposition motion attack prerogative urgent request Lord minister IV person Lords prorogue Parliament.Ziegler pp	7
monarch arrival stop debate prevent passage Address.Ziegler p.	7
told horse notice hackney cab	7
Said ''The Times scene arrival describe scene	7
violent tone gesture Lords spectator lady present alarm	7
Grant p. ''The Times Lord Londonderry whip thrash Government supporter wa held colleague	7
put crown Parliament.Allen pp.121–122 Ziegler p.	7
election Commons victory reformer	7
Commons wa favour reform Lords it.Allen pp	7
crisis saw brief interlude celebration Coronation	7
dispense coronation crown Parliament need.Allen pp	7
celebrate coronation way brother had—the coronation cost £240,000 £16,000 wa hire jewel	7
instruction Privy Council le £30,000 coronation.Molloy pp.72–73 traditionalist Tories boycott Half Crown-nation p. Ziegler p.193 convenience room le heat .Sir Herbert Taylor secretary Lord Ziegler p.	7
rejection Reform Bill agitation reform country demonstration violent Reform Riots	7
face excitement ministry accept defeat Lords Bill difficulty Lords	7
Lords recalcitrance create sufficient number peer passage Reform Bill	7
power create number peer peer Coronation p.	7
creation number peer sufficient secure success bill .Correspondence IV Herbert Taylor Henry Brock difficulty permanent expansion Peerage told creation eldest son collateral heir peer peerage absorbed subsidiary title	7
time Lords reject bill outright change character amendment	7
fellow minister resign agree immediate creation force bill entirety.Allen pp	7
restore office insufficient support form ministry popularity sank all-time	7
Mud wa slung carriage wa	7
reappoint ministry create peer Lords pose difficulty	7
threat creation bill opponent Reform wa	7
mob action influence wife brother popularity recovered.Ziegler pp	7