Willoughby wa ship southeast.James p. ship Guy-Victor Duperré squadron ''Bellone ''Minerve corvette ''Victor prize ''Windham ''Ceylon Comoros Islands	9
month repair Anjouan Duperré Île de opposition return passage wa enter Port channel Île de la Passe.Macmillan p. Duperré wa unaware occupation island Willoughby lure squadron channel presence harbour	9
Willoughby defeat damage break Duperré squadron Hamelin force Port Napoleon harbour prevent blockade squadrons.Clowes p. Willoughby brought Île de la Passe combine fire protect boat men raid Port morning	9
tricolour Île de la Passe Willoughby code island ''L'ennemi croise au Coin de Mire acknowledgement Duperré.Taylor p. use signal Duperré objection Captain Pierre Bouvet ''Minerve wa ship	9
squadron harbour morning ''Victor channel Île de la Passe	9
''Victor fort Willoughby fire Captain Morice corvette volley	9
Willoughby sent boat attempt possession ''Victor reach vessel.James p. corvette ''Minerve ''Ceylon channel Morice fire fort	9
Morice colour ''Minerve explosion Île de la Passe flag brazier wa set fire stack cartridge confines fort	9
men cannon sailor boat board ''Victor	9
fort action number crew boat channel wa block entry Port	9
Willoughby ambush plan boat sought rejoin passing squadron	9
boat danger ship bumped ''Minerve	9
opportunity cause damage narrow channel ''Bellone squadron passing channel minimal resistance	9
addition loss explosion fort men	9
loss ''Minerve casualty ''Ceylon	9
side action wa Willoughby sent boat ''Sirius assistance Duperré sent message overland Lieutenant Morice support Hamelin squadron Morice horse mission wa .Macmillan p. afternoon Willoughby mortar Île de la Passe shell squadron Duperré retreat shallow harbour Port Willoughby sent officer Port flag truce release ''Victor blockade squadron prize	9
Duperré request.James p. ship enter channel Port East Indiaman ''Windham	9
commander shelter Rivière Noire	9
''Sirius merchant ship battery sent boat anchorage ship brought casualty	9
success wa boarding party forgotten weapon wooden foot-stretchers clubs.Woodman p.	9