Operation Crossroads Event explosion World II navy battleship longer dominant asset	9
become apparent longer worth cost construction maintenance battleship wa war HMS	9
war battleship-on-battleship engagement Leyte sinking exception rule role aircraft engagement range longer longer gun armament irrelevant	9
armor battleship wa irrelevant face attack missile range end 1950s minor vessel class opposition battleship	9
battleship met variety end	9
sunk weapon Operation Crossroads	9
battleship resistant air burst underwater explosion	9
''Giulio Cesare wa Soviets reparation ''Novorossiysk wa sunk mine Black	9
''Andrea Doria class ship 1956.Fitzsimons ed	9
assistance Bill Antony Preston Ian Hogg Century Weapons Warfare Phoebus Volume p.114	9
''Lorraine wa ''Richelieu Fitzsimons Volume p.2213 ''Richelieu	9
World Ships ISBN 0-85177-146-7 p. V class ship Fitzsimons Volume p.1636 V ''Vanguard 1960.Fitzsimons Volume p.2554 ''Vanguard battleship broken pp	9
'Petropavlovsk wa ''Sevastopol ''Oktyabrskaya Revolutsiya name ''Gangut Fitzsimons Volume p.1086 ''Gangut	9
''Minas Gerais wa Genoa Fitzsimons Volume p.1896 ''Minas Gerais sister ship ''São Paulo sank storm ''en route breaker	9
kept ''Rivadavia class ship Chile kept ''Almirante Latorre HMS ''Canada 1959.Fitzsimons Volume p.84 ''Almirante Latorre battlecruiser ''Yavuz ''Goeben wa offer sell wa	9
Sweden coastal-defense battleship ''Gustav V p. Soviets incomplete cruiser 1950s whilst plan build number ''Stalingrad -class battlecruisers death Stalin	9
battleship ''Hessen met end	9
''Schleswig-Holstein wa ''Borodino wa target ship	9
''Schlesien wa target ship	9
wa broken p. ''Iowa class battleship lease life fire support ship	9
Radar gunfire pinpoint accuracy target	9
shore bombardment ''New round inch shell round inch projectile tour gunline Polmar p. time round shore target World War.History World Seapower ISBN 0-603-03723-2 p. part effort build response ''Kirov States ''Iowa class battleship	9
occasion battleship support ship carrier battle group battleship battle group	9
carry Tomahawk missile ''New action bombarding inch mm gun land target missile Operation Desert Storm	9
''Wisconsin TLAM strike commander sequence launch marked opening ''Desert Storm TLAMs day campaign	9
primary threat battleship Iraqi shore surface-to-surface missile ''Missouri wa Iraqi Silkworm missile destroyer	9
Defence power development decade ''Iowas battleship service	9
USS ''Iowa USS ''Wisconsin year standard service fire support vessel development fire support vessel	9
Marine Corps belief naval surface fire support gun missile program provide adequate fire support assault onshore operations.The USMC ha Naval Surface Gunfire Support requirement question Zumwalt class destroyer meet Marine qualification	9