burden le unwieldy land resident wa	3
Council held meeting Greengate Inn Tusmore	3
time elect councillor wa council met	3
Dr Christopher Penfold chairman met rest representative Ferguson Glenunga Alexander Ferguson Monreith Townsend Magill Grylls Vue.E p. xxvi ''The Paddocks Beneath wa time Kent Town part enter Norwood-Kensington	3
council wa meet Inn Ferguson home right council chamber built	3
wa operate fulfill obligation Government	3
management minor road administration abattoir licence public house prevention spread Scotch thistle	3
council wa act encourage education	3
road bridgework activity council resident influx development construction	3
time council wa sheer number resident request wa ask ratepayer assistance building bridge area.E p. xxix ''The Paddocks Beneath history ha institution part life resident school church.A.C	3
Hill p. ''The Years school area wa Magill proper statewide education system	3
Magill School wa boy girl taught reading grammar geography history sole teacher	3
teachers.Magill School History http //www.magillps.sa.edu.au/ Osmond School wa Osmond centre community debate learning.E p. ''The Paddocks Beneath School wa built institution.W.J	3
Adey p. ''The Years primary school absence proper library institution collection book town resident	3
Residents advantage school frequent debate future state region discussion drew crowd	3
spirit adult population wa education	3
drive Boer emphasis activity merit society	3
development activity wa centre Tusmore present Council Chambers Centre located.E p. ''The Paddocks Beneath grown wa mix village population	3
comparison Kensington-Norwood area grown person	3
Osmond immense growth expansion mining wa population centre residents.E p. ''The Paddocks Beneath Council council chamber haphazard meeting agreement	3
village Beulah Park North Eastwood boom population growth development housing immigrant investment wealthy Establishment.E p. ''The Paddocks Beneath Parkside Hospital Glenside mental health asylum wa building Parklands	3
ground elaborate façade wa monument.E p. ''The Paddocks Beneath Cooper brewing beer 'Coopers Leabrook.Coopers Brewery Students http //www.coopers.com.au/pdfs/studentInfo.pdf era Stonyfell saw expansion quarry hand Stonyfell wa p. ''The Paddocks Beneath century wa time development	3
development wa brought abrupt end decade depression stuck economy Australasia decade reckless expansion	3