V physician Dawson Penn injection morphine cocaine death	7
Queen eldest son Prince Wales throne VIII	7
wa Queen Mother use title wa ''Her Majesty Queen	7
year crisis desire marry mistress Wallis Simpson	7
Queen divorce wa Church thought Simpson wife king	7
advice Dominion government remain king marry Simpson	7
loyal supportive son Queen comprehend neglect royal duty favour	7
Simpson V Queen court HRH Windsor p. Queen meet public privately.HRH Windsor p. Queen saw duty provide support son Prince throne place name VI	7
coronation dowager queen p. abdication lessen love disapproval damage Crown.Edwards p. p. Queen interest granddaughter Princesses Elizabeth excursion art gallery museum	7
Princesses parent thought taxed regime	7
Edwards p. World II VI mother	7
wa reluctant Gloucestershire niece Somerset Duchess Beaufort daughter brother Lord p. belonging seventy piece luggage	7
household servant house Duchess suite war	7
people complain arrangement royal servant found house Queen annoyed niece ancient ivy torn wall hazard	7
support war effort troop factory gathering scrap material wa offer lift soldier roads.Pope-Hennessy p. son Prince Kent wa air crash service	7
Queen war defeat Nazi	7
Queen wa eager collector object picture royal connection.Pope-Hennessy p. paid above-market estimate purchasing jewel estate Dowager Empress Marie Feodorovna paid time estimate buying family Cambridge Emeralds Lady mistress brother Prince Francis.See Record Office Ireland	7
architect Edwin Lutyens Queen Dolls collection miniature pieces.Pope-Hennessy pp	7
ha acquisition ''objets d'art Royal Collection	7
occasion express host others something possession expectation owner donate	7
knowledge research Royal Collection artefact artwork astray years.Pope-Hennessy p. Royal lent object generation	7
item inventory write holder returned.The Windsor p. VI Queen child predecease eldest granddaughter Princess Elizabeth throne	7
Queen year lung cancer gastric problem ''The Times p. age ten week Elizabeth II coronation	7
event death coronation wa	7
remains lay state Westminster Hall number mourner past coffin	7
beside husband nave Chapel Windsor	7