Domnall II wa man ''rí Alban i.e	3
Alba Dunnottar meant king Scotland	3
predecessor bore style Picts Fortriu	3
apparent innovation chronicle spell birth Scotland nothing reign confirm	3
meant madman law man control function hence Law p.92	3
fact reign ndash Domnall successor Causantín key formation Medieval Alba.e.g	3
BBC documentary ''In Search Scotland ep	3
setback wa half-century reign Scots saw danger Vikings expand territory Isles Caithness area	3
period accession Máel Coluim Máel Coluim II wa marked relation Wessex ruler intense disunity policy	3
king Máel Coluim Strathclyde part deal Edmund event offset Máel Coluim loss control Moray.A.O	3
i p. reign king Idulb ndash Scots fortress ''oppidum Eden i.e	3
Edinburgh.Hudson Kings p. control wa Máel Coluim II victory Northumbrians Carham	3
Scots authority Strathclyde part century kingdom kept ruler Scots enforce authority.Hudson Kings pp	3
ndash reign wa adventure wa Mormaer Moray mac king Kings p. seventeen year wa pilgrimage Rome	3
wa Máel Coluim son eighteen month successor Lulach become king Máel Coluim III	3
subsequent medieval propaganda reign wa portrayed wa vilified	3
Shakespeare history men play Macbeth	3
wa Máel Coluim III father create dynasty Scotland century	3
Part resource wa number child dozen marriage widow daughter Thorfinn Sigurdsson Orkney afterwards princess granddaughter Edmund Ironside	3
royal wife Máel Coluim spent reign slave raid woe people aftermath Norman North	3
Marianus Scotus tell u Gaels hunger eat human flesh .A.O	3
Máel Coluim raid attempt claim successor kingdom interference Norman ruler kingdom	3
sister claimant throne Edgar child marriage royal name	3
Conqueror sent son invasion Scotland Máel Coluim authority king son hostage	3
Tradition brother Domnall Bán Máel Coluim successor eldest son wa chosen heir	3
Máel Coluim battle son Scotland Domnall wa king	3
II Máel Coluim eldest son wife support Rufus throne Chronicle follower Chronicle MS. E s.a. A.O	3
Anderson Annals p. II wa year Domnall Máel Petair Mearns	3
Rufus sent Máel Coluim son Edgar kingship	3
death Domnall Bán kingship Edgar period relative peace	3
reign Edgar successor Alexander obscure comparison successor	3
act wa send camel elephant fellow Gael Muircheartach Ua Briain Ireland.Annals s.a. ndash Edgar Alexander kingship brother Prince Cumbria ruler	3