post-World Treaty Versailles design manufacture deployment tank Reichswehr	9
paragraph twenty-four treaty fine imprisonment month anybody vehicle tank machine use ''Achtung-Panzer	9
p. manpower limitation Army Treaty Versailles Reichswehr officer clandestine Staff study World future strategy	9
concept tank mobile weapon war met apathy industry wa look tank design cooperation wa Union.Gander ''Tanks Armour Panzerkampfwagen II p. wa minor cooperation Sweden extraction data tank design.Perett ''German Light Panzers p.4 company Rheinmetall prototype 75-millimeter cannon ''Großtraktor tractor wa veil purpose vehicle .Franco ''Panzer El Inicio de una Saga p.3 year prototype ''Leichttraktor light tractor company L/45 guns.Franco ''Panzer El Inicio de una Sage p.3 Gander ''Tanks Armour Panzerkampfwagen II p.7 ''Großtraktor wa put service brief period Panzer Division ''Leichttraktor	9
tank theory wa figure Oswald Lutz chief staff Lieutenant Colonel	9
Percy Hobart corp ''panzerkorps type tank	9
infantry tank small-caliber cannon machine gun	9
infantry tank wa defend enemy anti-tank gun artillery	9
fast breakthrough tank cruiser tank wa enemy anti-tank weapon 75-millimeter cannon	9
need tank cannon defeat enemy fortification armor	9
tank require weight tonne wa manufacturing capability ''Achtung-Panzer	9
power Adolf Hitler creation panzer division	9
proposal design combat vehicle developed Panzer III breakthrough tank Panzer IV.Gander ''Tanks Armour Panzerkampfwagen II p. design	9
stopgap Army vehicle train tank crew	9
Panzer I.McCarthy ''Panzerkrieg p.31 Panzer design history Schlepper S vehicle	9
S wa train panzer troop prepare industry mass production tank future engineering feat time.Franco ''Panzer p. prototype ''Landswerk LKA front glacis plate casemate design Carden Loyd tankette	9
tank wa obsolescent 7.92-millimeter .312 MG-13 Dreyse machine guns.Franco ''Panzer II p.4–5 Machine gun useless tank armor time Panzer training anti-infantry role design.McCarthy ''Panzerkrieg p. version LKA wa collaborative team Henschel MAN Rheinmetall casemate turret	9
version wa service ''German Light Panzers p. tank S LKA start production official designation wa ''Panzerkampfwagen Ausführung	9
'model 'batch .Franco ''Panzer p. fifteen tank include turret crew training.Franco ''Panzer p.6 production wa combat version tank	9
wa steel plate millimeter thickest	9
tank design flaw suspension problem vehicle pitch velocity engine overheating.Gander ''Tanks Armour Panzerkampfwagen II p. driver wa chassis lever control tank commander wa turret gunner	9
crew member communicate mean voice tube.Perrett ''German Light Panzers p.5–6 Machine gun ammunition wa bin number wa magazine bin turret bin hull magazine	9
information Perrett ''German Light Panzers p. Author Lucas Franco suggests ''Panzerkampfwagen Ausf	9
tank built Franco ''Panzer p. author Bryan Perrett offer number ''German Light Panzers p. Terry Gander units.Gander ''Tanks Armour Panzerkampfwagen II p. problem Ausf	9
engine wa six-cylinder Maybach NL TR gearbox wa model	9
engine extension vehicle chassis cm improvement tank suspension bogie wheel tensioner.Franco ''Panzer pp	9
B writes Franco ''Panzer p. note combat model Franco ''Panzer p. Perrett suggests number number Ausf	9