force Tulagi Islands Solomon Islands	9
island meant deny use base supply route secure island point campaign goal base Rabaul Guinea campaign	9
campaign.Hogue ''Pearl Harbor p.	9
Solomons aircraft carrier USS ''Enterprise wa travel Harbor Hawaii month repair carrier task force area	9
task force carrier USS ''Wasp USS ''Saratoga USS ''Hornet respective air group surface warship battleship cruiser destroyer Solomons Hebrides Vanuatu island	9
location carrier line communication base Caledonia Espiritu Santo ground force Tulagi counteroffensive movement supply ship warship carrier range	9
area ocean carrier task force wa Torpedo Junction p. force concentration submarine area.Hammel Strike p.	9
''Saratoga wa torpedoed submarine wa action month repairs.Hammel Strike p. incident carrier task force commander Fletcher wa command shore duty remainder war	9
p. ''Wasp wa hit torpedo submarine reinforcement resupply convoy carrier ''Shōkaku ''Zuikaku withdrew adversary range aircraft	9
power torpedo damage ''Wasp ’ s damage-control team contain fire wa scuttled.Evans p. Hammel Strike p.	9
Battleship USS ''North destroyer USS ''O'Brien hit torpedo attack	9
''O'Brien sank result torpedo damage ''North wa repair Harbor	9
carrier ''Hornet Allies air superiority Solomon Islands aircraft Field	9
night aircraft operate operate ship	9
stalemate battle developed Allies supply reinforcement day supply reinforcement warship Express Allies night side deliver troop island secure decisive advantage	9
mid-October side number troop island.Hammel Strike p.	9
stalemate wa briefly large-ship naval action	9
night warship force warship force wa enroute bombard Field Cape Esperance	9
night force battleship ''Haruna ''Kongō Field aircraft damage field facilities.Frank p.	9
week airfield recover damage destroyed aircraft	9
time move try break stalemate battle	9
''Enterprise air group left Harbor Hammel Strike p.	9
''Hornet rest naval force mile km northeast Espiritu Santo.McGee ''The Solomons Campaigns p.	9
Chester Nimitz Commander Chief Forces Halsey Commander Area position force Solomon Islands campaign	9
McGee ''The Solomons Campaigns p.	9
Nimitz felt become myopic lead force struggle	9
Halsey wa naval fleet fighter	9
command Halsey plan draw naval force battle Nimitz begin punch	9
Fleet wa draw naval force wa decisive battle	9
fleet carrier ''Hiyō ''Junyō light carrier ''Zuihō naval base Truk ''Shōkaku ''Zuikaku	9
carrier air group battleship cruiser destroyer Fleet Isoroku Yamamoto wa confident defeat Midway.Hammel Strike p.	9
couple air raid Field carrier warship stayed battle area Solomon Islands chance approach engage carrier	9
Army ground attack force set Yamamoto warship position towards Solomons support army engage ship carrier support defense	9
force Solomons Island area read report Press States wa sea air battle Pacific.Hara Destroyer Captain p.	9