Nazi Molotov-Ribbentrop non-aggression pact	9
border troop caught guard Bagramyan commander Mikhail Kirponos invasion wa inevitable.Erickson	9
''The Road Stalingrad Stalin Volume	9
Connecticut Yale Press p. ISBN 0-3000-7812-9 Kipronos chose ignore Bagramyan viewpoint employ speed Blitzkrieg campaign 1940.Jukes	9
''Stalin Generals p. winter Bagramyan battle plan counter threat Ukraine wa revision	9
''The Days p. morning wa tasked transfer convoy Ternopol	9
column wa passing airfield city Brody air strike hit aircraft ground	9
hour Ternopol strafed planes.Salisbury	9
''The Days p. day invasion plan disorder engulfed troop counter-attack	9
Bagramyan Ivan ''Тak Шли Mы Пoбeдe Went Victory	9
Bagramyan part tank battle Ukraine defensive operation Kirponos wa Front Germans	9
wa handful officer Front	9
Bagramyan wa chief staff Marshal Semyon Timoshenko future premier officer Rostov	9
memoir described Bagramyan precise person everything wa	9
Pennsylvania State Press p. ISBN 0-2710-2332-5 detail account Marshal Semyon Budyonny sent chief operation department capital STAVKA Bagramyan	9
''Memoirs p. wa staff officer field unit command	9
Bagramyan astonishment Budyonny attempt convince agree execution	9
argument wa place abundant feast cognac day kind conversation	9
time wa men rank judging enemy people Army	9
''Memoirs p. Bagramyan wa planning counter-offensives Germans push force battle wa rank Lieutenant	9
month wa chief staff operation group oversee Army Groups Bryansk Fronts	9
Timoshenko present plan city Stalin	9
Stalin plan operation Bagramyan Chief Staff Front	9
army Front launch inopportune moment Barvenkovo Salient region force closing.Jukes	9
force found army closing Barvenkovo	9
Bagramyan Timoshenko alter plan Timoshenko Stalin request	9
''Այսպես է Սկսվել Պատերազմը	9
loss 57th army division portion Front destroyed Bagramyan wa post STAVKA	9
Bagramyan wa immense loss men operation wa burst tear	9
W. W. Norton Company p. ISBN 0-393-32484-2 failure operation staff work wa chief staff Army.Tompson J	9
MacMillan p. ISBN 0-3121-6360-6 day letter Stalin serve front capacity Jukes	9
''Stalin Generals p. historian Erickson contends Bagramyan wa Stalin attempt hunt culprit mismanagement operations.Erickson	9
''The Road Stalingrad p.	9