IGH Area Army Fleet decision withdraw	9
Fleet Area Army staff plan Operation ''Ke mora execute evacuation.Miller p. p. Morison p. Rottman p. Griffith p. p. Hayashi p.	9
Imamura Jinichi IJN commander Rabaul withdrawal order Emperor endorsement	9
plan battalion army infantry land destroyer act rear guard evacuation	9
17th Army wa begin end island	9
air superiority campaign Solomons begin	9
17th Army picked lift destroyer week target completion date	9
time air naval asset conduct maneuver minor attack Guinea Marshall Islands deceptive radio traffic try confuse Allies intentions.Frank p. Morison p.	9
Yamamoto aircraft carrier ''Junyō ''Zuihō battleship ''Kongō ''Haruna cruiser destroyer force Nobutake provide distant cover ''Ke Java Solomons	9
evacuation Mikawa Fleet cruiser ''Chōkai ''Kumano light cruiser ''Sendai destroyer	9
Yamamoto half Mikawa destroyer sunk operation.Frank p. Morison p. Rottman p. Griffith p. p.	9
destroyer include ''Suzukaze ''Hatsukaze Express	9
''Suzukaze wa Slot miss bomb CAF aircraft	9
''Hatsukaze wa PT boat torpedo Doma Tassafaronga	9
Express mission deliver ton supply boost 17th Army store	9
force carrier ''Zuiho ''Junyō battleship ''Kongo ''Haruna cruiser ''Atago ''Takao ''Myōkō ''Haguro light cruiser ''Jintsū ''Agano ''Nagara destroyer ''Kagero ''Asagumo ''Shigure ''Suzumaze ''Samidare ''Ōshio ''Hatsuyuki ''Shikinami ''Arashio ''Arashi support ship ''Nippon Maru ''Kenyo Maru	9
air superiority portion operation IJN Fleet IJA Division Rabaul aircraft	9
addition aircraft carrier ''Zuikaku air group Rabaul	9
floatplane IJN R Area Force Rabaul Shortland Islands brought number aircraft operation	9
warship naval air unit area Southeast Area Fleet Jinichi Rabaul.Frank p.	9
command US Halsey commander force fleet carrier ''Enterprise ''Saratoga escort carrier fast battleship battleship cruiser destroyer	9
air Force fighter bomber US Army Nathan CAF aircraft US Marine Francis P. Mulcahy	9
Fitch wa commander Aircraft	9
air unit fleet escort carrier aircraft	9
addition bomber Guinea sufficient range conduct mission Solomon Islands	9
Allies aircraft oppose ''Ke operation.Frank p.	9
battleship Halsey fleet ''Maryland ''Colorado ''New ''Mississippi p.	9
B-17 B-24 bomber range reach Fifth Force Guinea time p.	9
week disease starvation battle Hyakutake command troop sick fight	9
17th Army field cannon shortage artillery shell	9
contrast commander island US Army Alexander Patch force US Army US Marines XIV Corps men	9
Patch disposal artillery weapon gun plentiful stock shells.Frank p. Rottman p.	9
artillery include anti-aircraft coastal defense gun p.	9