Suffolk Punch registry breed society.Ryder-Davies Suffolk ''The Horse p. mention Suffolk Punch Camden ''Britannia Edwards ''The Horse p. describes horse county Suffolk Punch	1
description breed horse form today	1
developed Norfolk Suffolk east area	1
farmer developed Suffolk Punch farm work horse power stamen health longevity docility Suffolk comply need	1
farmer horse land seldom sell bloodline pure	1
foundation sire Suffolk Punch breed wa hand stallion Crisp Ufford	1
time breed wa Suffolk Sorrel.Hall ''Two Years Livestock pp	1
ndash horse wa Crisp horse	1
thought wa horse breed 1760s male line breed bottleneck	1
breed wa described hand compact bony leg light sorrel color gentle shoulder flesh .Dohner ''Encyclopedia Livestock Poultry Breeds p. development breed wa Norfolk Trotter Norfolk Cob	1
uniform derives part stallion Blakes Farmer	1
breed cross attempt increase size stature Suffolk Punch shoulder influence breed remains wa place	1
Suffolk Horse Society promote Suffolk Punch stud book ''Cyclopedia Agriculture pp	1
ndash official export Suffolks place	1
Suffolks States begin breeding Suffolk Punches US	1
Suffolk Horse wa stud book	1
Suffolk Austria Russia Sweden part country	1
time World Suffolk Punch become work horse farm East Anglia temperament excellent work	1
World combination need wartime food production horse sent slaughterhouse farm mechanisation war population numbers.Ryder-Davies Suffolk ''The Horse pp	1
ndash foal Suffolk Horse Society ha revival interest breed 1960s number risen	1
breed remain rare breeding mare foal year	1
States Suffolk Horse war year draught horse market recover	1
1970s registry Belgians Suffolk Punches cross registry Suffolk Horse Association.Dohner ''Encyclopedia Livestock Poultry Breeds pp	1
ndash horse bloodline breed wa rarest horse breed Britain.Dohner ''Encyclopedia Livestock Poultry Breeds p. Suffolk Punch population ha increase Breeds Survival UK considers survival status horse States	1
Livestock Breeds Conservancy list breed	1
Suffolk Horse Society birth foal foal	1