Bloody Valentine record Studios Southwark month use time conceptualise sound album.McGonigal p. Shields Creation album day	6
p. month band basement studio Elephant spent week	6
In-house engineer Nick Robbins Shields outset Robbins wa press button	6
Robbins wa Harold Burgon Shields Burgon contribution wa show group use in-studio computer	6
Burgon Shields spent week Woodcray studio Berkshire ''Glider EP Shields Creation owner McGee advance album	6
Moulder wa mix ''Glider song Trident studio Victoria song reappear closing track ''Loveless	6
p. group work album Moulder wa sole engineer Shields perform task amplifier engineer told top work	6
p. Shields ha engineers—with exception Moulder Anjali people studio everything wa	6
p. spring Anjali Dutt wa Moulder left work band Shakespears Sister Ride	6
Dutt guitar tracks.McGonigal p. period band studio spending day studio wa	6
Bloody Valentine Protocol Holloway primary location work earnest album EP ''Tremolo .McGonigal p. ''Glider ''Tremolo song— Knows ''Loveless	6
band summer order tour support release ''Glider .McGonigal p. Moulder project wa work	6
point Creation Records wa album wa costing.McGonigal p. Moulder left work noise pop band Jesus Chain.McGonigal p. track taped Row Protocol studio	6
wa time vocalist Butcher wa	6
Shields Butcher hung curtain window studio control room booth engineer acknowledge opening curtain	6
engineer Guy Fixsen listen	6
watch meter tape machine anyone wa	6
knew stop tape top	6
day couple lyric song record	6
Dutt track tape write word thought sung .Cavanagh p. Creation relocate production Eastcoate studio complaint Shields	6
cash-poor Creation Records wa pay bill time Row studio return band equipment	6
Cavanagh p. Shields random behaviour delay studio change material effect Creation finance health staff	6
Dutt desperate project Creation second-in-command breakdown time	6
wa year album Shields tear	6
wa 'You deliver record	6
time Shields Butcher tinnitus delay number week	6
friend band member wa result loud volume group played show	6
McGee wa upbeat investment time wa opening label morning post fear concern co-worker	6
Publicist Laurence label inability cover studio bill hair grey overnight	6
track mix album wa engineer Meany Church End autumn p. wa nineteenth studio ''Loveless	6
album wa machine cut dialog movie 1970s	6
computer threw album phase	6
Shields wa put memory album Creation dismay day day.Cavanagh p. prolific band UK music press speculate	6
''Melody Maker cost £250,000 McGee Shields dispute	6
Shields cost Creation wa myth McGee Creation owner thought cool	6
Shields amount spent nobody	6
ourselves studio cost engineer cost	6
thousand pound wa money wa spent	6
p. opinion ''Melody Maker estimate side £20,000	6
act EQ-ing etcetera week	6
interview Shields money claimed spent album wa money year album thousand	6
claimed album month work years.Gabriel	6
Shields money spent wa band money Creation spent fifteen twenty thousand pound money	6