present Theatre Royal Drury Lane Dean Wyatt behalf committee Whitbread production ''Hamlet Elliston title role	4
theatre concession intimacy people building size theatre	4
portico stand theatre front entrance Catherine wa year gas wa interior underwent	4
colonnade side building wa detail paragraph p.	4
Productions scenery effect dialogue commonplace facility	4
production ''Cataract Ganges finale horseback escape cataract fire	4
Effects production hydraulic apparatus discharge ton water.Bradby et al	4
theatre wa role show legitimate drama	4
Management theatre Samuel overseen amateur board director subcommittee theatre centre culture	4
Lord wa briefly subcommittee	4
Actor Edmund wa on-stage highlight Macklin reputation Shylock role	4
popularity effort appeal culture turn profit failure theatre right Elliston	4
Elliston bankrupt wa renew lease	4
Price ndash remainder century Drury Lane set hand	4
colonnade wa frontage architect Samuel pp	4
Bunn control Drury Lane Covent Garden	4
actor-manager Samuel Phelps company Drury Lane Macready actor-manager number Shakespeare play	4
role Captain Channel Jerrold melodrama ''The Prisoner Lord Tresham ''A Blot 'Scutcheon	4
Macready wa briefly manager ndash reform place	4
scene performance Shakespeare theatre News	4
monopoly Royal Letters Patent year wa Theatres patent toothless decade immediate effect	4
hand theatre entertainment Drury Lane venue legitimate theatre	4
19th-century failure Drury Lane wa play period Dion Boucicault ''The Queen Spades ''Eugenie ''Formosa ''The Shaughraun	4
period decline Chatterton resignation word Shakespeare spell ruin bankruptcy	4
century Drury Lane ballet performer Carlotta Grisi	4
director Drury Lane wa conductor composer light music Jullien Berlioz visit concert Theatre	4
house fortune management Augustus	4
theatre production Rosa Opera Company	4
Productions spectacle norm Drury Lane part century management Augustus ndash Collins ndash	4
Examples include ''The Whip train crash steam horserace twelve horse jockeying on-stage treadmill	4
pantomime comedian Leno performance success	4
design designer Wilhelm spectacular drama ''Armada pantomime Mr	4
Pitcher Art ''The Times interior renovation wa theatre seat people. show-and-stay.co.uk	4
wa interior specialist ornamental plasterwork company Clark Fenn. Friends Norwood cemetery Composer performer Ivor Novello time today Drury Lane theatre wa World II	4
war theatre headquarters Entertainments minor bomb damage	4
theatre Noel Coward ''Pacific	4
post-war year number Rodgers debut Drury Lane ''Oklahoma	4
import Lerner Loewe ''My Fair Lady	4
Comedy troupe Monty Python reunion show	4
Today theatre part End theatre scene production	4
Theatres division Andrew Lloyd	4
production include ''42nd ndash ''Miss Saigon ndash	4
Mel ''The Producers theatre adaptation ''The Lord Rings	4
show way production ''Oliver	4
present building wa Grade Heritage	4