brother resource film production Jennings p.	5
lent support filmmaker Laemmle Independent Motion Picture Company challenged control Edison	5
year job film splicer Millner p. brother production film ''Dante Inferno Millner p.	5
film success box office threat Edison	5
broke Laemmle sent film exchange Millner p.	5
brother exploit movie market.Thomas p.	5
wa sent film exchange Millner p.	5
opportunity produce film film right ''My Years bestselling novel wartime atrocity	5
ndash brother studio Millner p.	5
studio co-head production brother Millner p.	5
capacity brother script story line film production way production cost	5
Bros. success ''My Years ''The Tiger Claw	5
year studio wa le effort promote Eyes tract danger venereal disease sole screen appearance.Thomas p.	5
period studio profit Millner p. Warners bank loan debt	5
Warners production studio Culver lot corner Sunset Avenue.Thomas p.	5
location facility studio image low-budget comedy racy film morality.Thomas p.	5
studio Shepherd Rin Tin Tin	5
canine debut North Begins film pup wolf befriends fur trapper.Thomas p.	5
biographer doubt project met Rin Tin Tin display intelligence	5
Rin Tin Tin studio asset introduction sound.Behlmer p.	5
Screenwriter Darryl Zanuck script Rin Tin Tin vehicle year half studio features.Thomas p.	5
Between Zanuck right-hand man executive producer position responsibility day-to-day production films.Behlmer p. xii	5
success Rin Tin Tin project Bros. wa compete ndash Universal studio	5
studio operation theater company Millner p. year brother sign agreement series developed Vitaphone technology.Thomas ndash	5
pneumonia feature-length picture ''The Jazz Singer sole head production.Warner Jennings pp	5
biographer writes life sunshiny optimism thirst excitement mind nature	5
buffer stern eldest brother Harry.Thomas p.	5
year ran Bros. Burbank studio iron hand	5
brother death deal resentment employee	5
family passing success ''The Jazz Singer Bros. studio	5
Bros. film studio reaped Millner p. studio nation movie theater block growth picture .Thomas p.	5
face opposition Bros. talkie	5
year Academy Motion Picture Arts Sciences Bros. industry sound .Thomas p.	5