create alien creature look man suit Terry Nation script Dalek legs.Howe p. wa performance State Ballet dancer skirt glide stage.Howe p. show Daleks played ballet dancer sock Dalek	5
Raymond Cusick wa task Daleks Scott designer BBC debut serial.Howe p. account Jeremy ''Doctor — Years Nation script Cusick wa hour design Daleks wa sketch pepper shaker table	5
Cusick state man chair pepper shaker demonstrate move.Walker p. Nation told Mirror reporter Dalek name encyclopedia volume spine read Dal Lek .Peel pp	5
book origin Dalek name wa anyone check story found	5
name reality typewriter.Howe p. Nation wa discover word dalek mean distant .Davies director	5
''More Years TARDIS UK BBC Video	5
Nation World II fear bombing	5
Daleks Nazis specie faceless figure conquest conformity.Howe p. allusion Dalek story Nation ''The Dalek Invasion Earth ''Genesis Daleks .Miles pp	5
p. Dalek Nation wa chief scriptwriter comedian Tony Hancock	5
Nation wa fired.Miles p. Hancock left BBC series proposal wa ''From Plip comedic history world apocalypse survivor living dustbin-like robot radiation stay	5
biographer Cliff Hancock saw Daleks screen bloody Nation — robot	5
Dalek ''The Survivors pre-production title ''The Mutants official title time production broadcast story ''Beyond ''The Planet ''The Daleks	5
instant appeal Daleks caught BBC guard ''Doctor tea-time child programme must-watch phenomenon	5
Children alien look monster ''Doctor production office wa letter call creature	5
Newspaper article attention series Daleks popularity	5
Nation property right Daleks BBC money-making concept sell anyone wa dependent BBC produce story production note ''The Dalek Invasion Earth UK BBC Video	5
fan adoration Daleks ''Doctor attempt market Daleks series unsuccessful.Peel p. p. Nation death share right belong estate agent Tim Hancock	5
plan ''Doctor television movie Daleks case spider legs.Segal pp	5
concept Spider Daleks wa picked ''Doctor spin-off	5
series wa fan Daleks return programme	5
negotiation BBC Nation estate point break agreement wa	5
medium report disagreement wa Nation estate level control Daleks appearance script BBC	5
talk Hancock BBC Daleks series	5