hour poll Kennedy claimed victory state primary	3
a.m. PDT campaign supporter Ambassador Hotel Embassy Room ballroom Mid-Wilshire district	3
time government protection incumbent president candidate	3
Kennedy security wa agent bodyguard athletes.Moldea pp	3
campaign Kennedy contact public people touch excitement.Witcover pp	3
Kennedy walk ballroom way gathering supporter hotel.Witcover p.	3
deadline fast reporter press conference	3
Campaign aide Dutton Kennedy forgo gathering kitchen pantry area ballroom press area	3
Dutton clearing way Kennedy left door kitchen corridor Kennedy crowd hotel maître d Uecker exit.Witcover pp	3
Uecker Kennedy kitchen area Kennedy right wrist Kennedy shook hand encountered.Moldea Chapter	3
Uecker Kennedy passageway ice machine right wall steam table left	3
Kennedy left shook hand busboy Juan Romero Sirhan Sirhan tray-stacker beside ice machine past Uecker wa .22 caliber Iver-Johnson Cadet revolver.Witcover p.	3
Kennedy floor security man Bill hit Sirhan face others maître d Uecker writer Plimpton Olympic gold medal decathlete Rafer football player Rosey Sirhan steam table	3
Sirhan grabbed revolver bullet	3
Kennedy lay jacket candidate head knew wa .22 caliber saw hole Senator head knew .Witcover p.	3
Reporters photographer area direction chaos	3
Kennedy lay Juan Romero senator head rosary hand	3
Kennedy Romero Is everybody OK	3
Romero yes everything OK	3
''Life photographer Bill Eppridge Yaro ''Los Times moment iconic image assassination	3
Ethel Kennedy stood crush people scene help	3
wa husband knelt beside	3
minute attendant Kennedy stretcher exclaim .Witcover p.	3
Kennedy wa mile Hospital death	3
doctor face Bob Bob Kennedy heart	3
heartbeat doctor stethoscope Ethel Kennedy hear husband heart beating relief	3
minute Kennedy wa block Hospital Samaritan surgery	3
Surgery a.m. PDT hour minutes.Witcover pp	3
Ten half hour p.m. PDT spokesman Mankiewicz Kennedy doctor failure show improvement condition life .Witcover p.	3
bullet range right ear fragment brain	3
others rear right armpit chest neck.Moldea p.	3
neurosurgery Samaritan Hospital bullet bone fragment brain Kennedy a.m. PDT hour	3
people Weisel News Schrade Auto Workers union activist Elizabeth Evans News Kennedy campaign volunteer Irwin Stroll	3
singer Clooney Kennedy supporter wa present ballroom pantry breakdown	3