brought service year World II ''Iowa -class battleship operate provide anti-aircraft aircraft carrier perform shore bombardment	9
None ''Iowa -class battleship enemy capital ship World II ''Iowa ''New engage enemy surface ship operating World II	9
end war ''Iowa ''New ''Wisconsin mothball fleet part post World II drawdown ''Iowa -class battleship Truman ''Missouri	9
advice Defense Sullivan Chief Naval Operations Denfeld Truman ''Missouri fleet fondness battleship battleship daughter Truman	9
construction wa incomplete ship ''Illinois ''Kentucky .Construction ''Illinois cancellation construction work ''Kentucky wa cancellation	9
''Iowa s outbreak naval artillery support force duration war mothball hostility	9
help alleviate US air loss North VietnamNeubeck p. ordnance war ''New wa battleship world gunline coast	9
''New water Zone shell round shell communist target gunline Polmar p. wa year	9
''Iowa s part plan rebuild create	9
cruiser worn mileage ''Iowas brought fill bombardment role	9
ship counter ''Orlan -class missile cruiser ''Kirov -class battlecruisers.Bishop p. p.	9
battleship wa carry warfare suite CIWS self-defense system reactivation played idea gun turret battleship facility STOVL jumpjets	9
centerpiece battleship battle group BBBGs .A Battleship support ship	9
mission intervention Civil Beirut barrack bombing ''Desert Storm part Operation ''Desert Shield part Operation ''Desert Storm	9
time restraintsA Government Accountability Office report operating cost ''Iowa -class battleship cost States operate battleship	9
inflation battleship cost operate dollar	9
number doe consideration cost specialty item unique component battleship	9
''Iowa s split group States reserve fleet mothball fleet use museum ship	9
Defense Authorization ''Iowa ''Missouri struck Naval Vessel Register	9
''Missouri wa Missouri Harbor Hawaii use museum ship	9
''Iowa wa set ''Missouri wa Naval Vessel Register Strom Thurmond Defense Authorization ''New museum ship	9
''Iowa -class battleship mothball fleet transfer use museum ship	9