chronicle contains reference Gediminas son	7
name son found source identity eighth remains	7
Alvydas Nikžentaitis suggests son wa Trakai Veliuona	7
Trakai wa position held second-in-command	7
19th-century historian wa Gediminas Veliuona advertises place Gediminas burial	7
Nikžentaitis postulate name son Vytautas record mention Yuri son Vytautas deputy Andrei son Algirdas	7
position youth grandson Gediminas	7
others dispute theory note chronicle wa misinterpreted.Rowell ''Lithuania p. Jaunutis middle son source coup d'état brother wa Gediminas heir Vilnius ''Lithuania pp	7
brother Kęstutis Trakai wa Samogitia	7
help Narimantas Jaunutis wa brother Algirdas Kęstutis year Gediminas death	7
Jaunutis solicit help brother-in-law Simeon Russia wa ''Iwan process	7
wa reconcile Algirdas compensation Duchy Zasłaŭje death	7
Algirdas wa son heir Gediminid line	7
brother Jaunutis pagan Maria daughter prince Vitebsk	7
collaboration historiography rise theory tradition co-rule diarchy wa arose	7
Algirdas wa east Kęstutis Duchy interaction Teutonic Knights entity	7
Algirdas marriage Uliana Tver chose son Jogaila	7
Jogaila chapter history country Christianity signing union	7
union form partition Commonwealth	7
Jogaila branch Gediminids Jagiellon dynasty	7
Kęstutis Trakai autonomy province duchy wa loyal Algirdas superiority	7
Kęstutis wa pagan life Teutonic Knights	7
legend arose marriage pagan priestess Birutė Palanga	7
Algirdas death son Jogaila	7
Kęstutis son Vytautas Jogaila rule Jogaila Treaty Dovydiškės Teutonic Knights Kęstutis Vilnius	7
Vytautas fight supremacy conflict descendant Algirdas Kęstutis 15th century.Rowell ''Lithuania p. Manvydas wa eldest son Gediminas territory Slonim father	7
wa Strėva brother Narimantas	7
Narimantas wa son Gediminas	7
wa Gleb rule Pinsk Polotsk – patrimony invitation Novgorod – Ladoga Oreshek	7
tradition mercenary service north Novgorod border Novgorod fall ''Lithuania p. bay.Rowell ''Lithuania p. Narimantas supporter brother Jaunutis Jani Beg Horde ask support Algirdas Kęstutis	7
rumor Narimantas Tatar princess lack credibility	7
year brother Narimantas Strėva name Algirdas	7
left son family Galitzine	7
Karijotas wa Mikhail Navahrudak Black Ruthenia	7
wa sent Algirdas Jani Beg negotiate coalition Teutonic Knights wa ransom	7
Liubartas Dymitr wa Gediminas son	7
daughter Andrew Halych Lutsk	7
Andrew brother Leo Halych death Halych-Volhynia power vacuum	7
Liubartas war Gediminas daughter Eufemija Bolesław Jerzy II Halych	7