publication ''Maggie Girl Streets wa critic novelist	4
''Maggie wa publisher true-to-life depiction class warfare clashed sentimental tale time	4
middle class novel character lower-class denizen p. chief character descends prostitution astray lover	4
novel plot simple mood quick pace portrayal Bowery life	4
''Maggie account slum life meant representation symbol	4
draft character proper name	4
epithet example wa girl seducer wa knight .Knapp p. novel bitter irony anger destructive morality sentiment	4
Critics call novel dark flower Naturalism distinctive element fiction	4
thirty year end Civil experience battle ''The Badge Courage wa	4
described war novel focus le battle character psyche reaction response wartime situation.Gibson p. Told third-person point view experience Henry soldier flees combat world	4
''The Badge Courage vivid description prose help create suspense story.Knapp p. epithet character name youth soldier injects quality work character point man.Knapp pp	4
ndash novel ''The Badge Courage ha ironic tone increase severity novel progress	4
title work ironic Henry wish wound badge courage wish battle	4
wound doe receive rifle butt soldier badge courage badge shame.Gibson p. connection novel humankind nature frequent prominent concern fiction poetry career	4
Whereas writer Waldo Emerson Nathaniel Hawthorne Henry Thoreau bond element perspective human consciousness human nature	4
''The Badge Courage distance number reference animal men people howl squawk growl snarl .Gibson p resurgence popularity ''The Badge Courage ha text	4
novel ha time Hemingway collection ''Men Stories Time	4
introduction Hemingway novel book literature include piece poem	4
success ''The Badge Courage chose write tale set Bowery	4
''George Mother le novel focus conflict church-going temperance-adhering woman thought mother dreamer.Knapp p. response novel wa	4
''The Violet romance wa publication ''The Badge Courage attempt appeal audiences.Gibson p. story detail character stereotypical.Knapp pp	4
ndash novel revolves author wa	4
passionate work nineteenth century novel wa	4
critic work point speed order meet expenses.Knapp p. novel suspenseful picaresque work ''The O'Ruddy wa Barr p.	4