publication ''A Voyage round World brought Forster recognition	1
Royal Society member Fellows Royal Society wa year	1
wa title Academies Madrid	1
Stanisław Introduction Jerzy Forster ''Podróż naokoło świata translation Michał Ronikier selection ''A Voyage Round World Czytelnik appointment money	1
position History professor Collegium Carolinum met Heyne philologist daughter	1
wa left child marriage wa	1
time Forster wa correspondence figure Enlightenment Herder Wieland Goethe	1
cooperation Carolinum Göttingen friend Georg Christoph	1
journal ''Göttingisches Magazin der und Litteratur .Saine p. Forster closest friend Samuel von Forster Rosicrucians	1
Forster saw involvement Rosicrucians science deeper debtSaine p. wa money reason Forster wa accept proposal Edukacji Narodowej Education Chair History Vilnius p. wa Vilnius felt time	1
contact scientist dispute Immanuel Kant definition race.Saine pp	1
Forster thesis plant doctorate medicine.Richard P. ''The Voyages Captain Cook	1
Vilnius Forster ambition build history centre appropriate support authority	1
event tension community.Leslie Bodi ''Georg Forster Expert eighteenth-century ''Literatur Politik Identität Literature Politics Identity pp	1
Röhrig Universitätsverlag Ingbert broke contract year completion Catherine II Russia offer part journey world honorarium position professor Saint Petersburg.Robert J	1
conflict Forster scientist Jędrzej Śniadecki	1
proposal wa withdrawn Forster left Vilnius	1
Mainz head Mainz position friend Johannes von Müller held sure Forster Müller administration Elector Josef von Erthal.Saine p.59 Forster essay discovery expedition time prolific translator instance Cook journey Bounty expedition Cook journey German.Robert J	1
“ Seas Georg Forster expedition Lapérouse Mulovsky ” Band XIII year Forster wa contact scholar Banks initiator Bounty expedition participant Cook journey	1
Vilnius article Neuholland und die brittische Colonie Botany-Bay ''Allgemeines historisches prescient essay future prospect colony Wales	1
translation http //web.mala.bc.ca/Black/AMRC/index.htm home.htm http //www.australiaonthemap.org.au/content/view/47/59/ field interest wa indology goal expedition Catherine II reach	1
Sanskrit play Shakuntala Latin version Herder interest culture India.Ackerknecht p.85	1