television work wa ITV	4
script ITV wa one-off play ''Murrain network Midlands franchise holder TeleVision ATV	4
play horror piece witchcraft year series ''Beasts six-part anthology tale horror macabre	4
''Beasts gain network ITV region episode timeslots sequences.Murray ''Beasts mdash Programme Notes pp	4
mid-1970s attempt stage play	4
''Crow wa memoir real-life Manx slaver Captain Crow	4
wa backing produce play stage script ATV put pre-production television	4
wa order ATV director Lew Grade mdash wa told	4
cancellation ''Crow work ITV company Thames Television production script ''Quatermass Euston Films subsidiary film company	4
production wa work four-episode transmission UK film version cinema release mdash something	4
Mills Quatermass budget £1 mdash fifty time budget ''Quatermass Pit p. mdash wa predecessor	4
le awesome Mr science-fiction essay BBC Television ITV debut ha so-so affair wa verdict ''The Times episode	4
series prose fiction full-length novel ''Quatermass novelisation	4
television series wa departure style mdash ''Kinvig sole attempt sitcom Television broadcast ITV autumn	4
out-and-out comedy wa keen stress element humour present script press reaction ''Kinvig wa	4
idea ''Hitch-Hiker found realization prefer relaxed wit	4
Cast splendid direction deft wa ''The Times preview episode	4
one-off diversion work movie script ''Halloween III Season Witch	4
director Landis work screenplay remake ''Creature Black Lagoon wife spent time living Sheraton Hotel project	4
''Black Lagoon script production met director Joe Dante script film ''Halloween series Dante wa	4
proviso concept film heard	4
treatment film met approval producer ''Halloween series wa write script week	4
director film Tommy Wallace film backer Dino Laurentiis inclusion violence rewrite script Wallace result name film	4
script television ''Gentry Roger ITV adaptation Hill novel ''The Woman Black transmission ITV Christmas Eve	4
Lynne Truss repeat broadcast production Channel ''The Times Clip-clop noise upset	4
test today people whisper saw ''The Woman Black night	4
People bold decision watch excellent drama respond air neck	4
adaptation unmade script ten day agent wait producer Independent Television think	4
submit script week cancel production work age	4
Hill herself change ''The Woman Black	4
ha occasion double-standard adaptation others change story change story wa script form	4
''The Woman Black adaptation writer critic Newman wa notion Hill name HG Wells hero ''The Woman Black use change hero name	4
sure somebody thought Quatermass wa name	4
adaptation four-part version novel ''Stanley Women met approval author adaptation work.Murray ''Into p.	4
''Sharpe Gold ITV part series adaptation Cornwell ''Sharpe novel	4
wa assignment agent think want bother	4
radio time 1950s ''The Quatermass Memoirs BBC Radio p.	4
event ''Quatermass material wa strand series set ITV ''Quatermass Andrew star Hammer version ''Quatermass Pit	4
audio commentary film ''Quatermass prequel set	4
''The Independent storyline Quatermass rocketry experiment woman escape country Olympics	4
wa write science-fiction series ''The X-Files ndash offer	4
work wa episode ITV drama ''Kavanagh QC Thaw	4
episode Ancient History wa woman World horrific experiment concentration camp	4
programme episode brought career fifty year	4
interview subject television documentary audio commentary release production DVD	4
consultant digital television channel BBC remake ''The Quatermass Experiment	4
Barnes death age series stroke	4