''Note story place inn road Norwich play call costumery	4
summary name play note change plot play story	4
change order event described	4
''For example story Jenny Sergeant miser	4
play order Sergeant Pipette Jenny name play miser	4
Pigeons inn day miser Boomblehardt ha rent tenant Sergeant hero Johannesburg ha inn flirt lady chooses need pretend relative order Colonel	4
day Martha landlady inn strange lady fairy refuse pay need food water	4
enlists Boomblehardt farmer shy niece Pipette help solve problem	4
fear woman power threatens fairy chase	4
doe fairy power cast spell force threaten anyone encounter fight enemy	4
flees trouble anyone challenge	4
Sergeant approach woman try use charm win	4
turn hate soldier strike stick duck dodge	4
cast spell permanent reputation coward	4
Pipette arrives watch behaviour astonishment	4
fought enemy Johannesburg Gilbert p. exclaims lady reply dear	4
Pipette try coax lady nature	4
lady attempt punishment story Gilbert p. compels kiss cuddle meet	4
cry protest shy behaviour lady assures shyness year sort thing	4
Boomblehardt approach Pipette herself cry	4
box ear confusion retreat inn tears.Gilbert p.	4
miser ha heard strange lady doe need eat offer help stay inn teach secret avoid money food	4
fairy decides someone compels continue passing guinea meets.Gilbert pp	4
Boomblehardt Sergeant curse decides money sergeant	4
shy Pipette throw herself Sergeant duck dodge avoid	4
arrives fight sergeant surprise brave sergeant cowers dodge duck	4
Boomblehardt passing guinea fortune	4
Martha chase customer inn broom ha	4
Everyone ha fairy ironic curse behave manner nature	4
lady mistake Gilbert p. explicit error part	4
head downstairs check mischief group beg relent	4
behave curse threatens Pipette try kiss sergeant duck miser offer money landlady chase broom	4
chaos Old Lady wa match wa number	4
left choice relent release spell vanquished	4
story bit explicit element play part story everything course action none personage	4
annoyed fool inn direction heard	4
nothing courage kept Pigeons end days.Gilbert p.	4
marries end play wa innovation theatre reviewer ''Era surprise	4
Synopsis note story nephew	4
story Boomblehardt equivalent Verditter landlady inn ha fine silver try bribe fairy order money elsewhere.Gilbert pp	4