advent Balkan Wars Prince Andrew wa army Princess Andrew nurse operation field hospital work V Royal Cross	7
World brother-in-law Constantine neutrality policy government Venizelos Allies	7
Princess Andrew child shelter palace cellar bombardment Athens 1916.Vickers p. neutrality policy become member royal family exile brother-in-law	7
year royal family Switzerland.Van der Kiste pp	7
naval career father Prince war face anti-German sentiment	7
request V title Prince Duchy Hesse style Serene Highness family name Mountbatten	7
day Marquess Milford peerage Kingdom.Princess Alice Mountbatten surname courtesy title daughter marquess Royal	7
year aunt Alix Russia Duchess Elizabeth Fyodorovna Bolsheviks revolution	7
end war empire Princess Andrew uncle Hesse wa deposed.Vickers pp	7
Constantine restoration briefly residence Mon Repos Prince Andrew father ’ s assassination	7
defeat Army leadership Colonels Nikolaos Plastiras Stylianos Gonatas power Constantine exile again.Vickers p. Prince Andrew commander Army Corps war wa	7
minister time shot diplomat Prince Andrew wa mortal danger	7
show trial wa banishment Prince Princess Andrew child aboard cruiser HMS ''Calypso protection naval attaché Commander Talbot.Vickers p. family house Princess outskirt Princess Andrew charity shop refugees.Vickers pp	7
winter husband defence action English.Vickers pp	7
wa divine message powers.Vickers p. breakdown Princess Andrew wa paranoid schizophrenia Dr Ernst Simmel sanatorium Tegel Berlin.Vickers p. wa family Dr Ludwig Binswanger sanatorium Kreuzlingen Switzerland.Vickers p. wa institution celebrity patient Vaslav Nijinsky ballet dancer choreographer wa time Princess Andrew.Vickers p. Princess Andrew convalescence Prince Andrew daughter prince attend wedding Prince stay uncle Lord Mountbatten Mountbatten Marquess Milford grandmother Dowager Marchioness Milford Haven.Ziegler p. Princess Andrew Kreuzlingen year brief stay clinic Meran wa itinerant incognito existence	7
contact mother broke tie rest family end 1936.Vickers pp	7
daughter Cécile son-in-law grandchild air accident Ostend Prince Andrew met time year Prince Lord Mountbatten Hermann .Vickers p. Henceforth contact family Athens work living Benaki Museum.Vickers pp	7
resume maternal responsibility son visit Athens brother felt repatriate fact royal family wa future service	7