theory explanation decline Roman Empire date fall onset decline centuryGoldsworthy ''In Name Rome p. fall Constantinople ''The Enemies Rome p. Empire overrun people heart troop revolt	9
historicity exact date historian Empire point	9
Empire le nature Empire assault overthrow Emperor Romulus Augustus wa troop Roman army troop	9
sense Odoacer title Emperor Empire name	9
identity wa longer Roman – wa people	9
Roman people fifth century ''bereft ethos Matyszak ''The Enemies Rome p. Roman army supplement troop Goths Huns Franks others behalf	9
Rome gasp Visigoths AD.Jordanes ''The Origins Deeds Goths Procopius ''History Wars Book Pt Ch	9
seize Constantinople Gibbon ''The Decline Fall Roman Empire p. rebuffed Thrace Greece.Matyszak ''The Enemies Rome p. AD Mediolanum capital Roman Emperor Honorius Roman troop	9
arrival Roman Stilicho army relieve siege move towards Hasta Asti Stilicho Pollentia Gibbon ''The Decline Fall Roman Empire p. 563Jordanes ''The Origins Deeds Goths camp	9
Stilicho return prisoner exchange Visigoths Illyricum Verona retreat	9
Stilicho VeronaGibbon ''The Decline Fall Roman Empire p. Matyszak ''The Enemies Rome p. withdraw	9
AD number tribe advantage Rhine cross ''en masse Vandals Suevi Alans Burgundians swept river met resistance Sack Moguntiacum Sack Treviri Grant ''The History Rome p. over-running Gaul	9
grave danger Roman army wracked usurpation Stilicho Rome foremost defender period wa put death.Grant ''The History Rome p. climate setback sack Rome.Jordanes ''The Origins Deeds Goths ''The Enemies Rome p. ''The Decline Fall Roman Empire p. Roman capital time city Ravenna Gibbon ''The Decline Fall Roman Empire p. historian view alternative date fall Roman Empire.Wood ''In Search Civilizations p. possession Rome province nature Roman Empire Empire	9
AD Roman troop Gibbon ''The Decline Fall Roman Empire p. ''A History English-Speaking Peoples p. AD wa longer part Empire wa beset ''by kind calamity disaster Churchill ''A History English-Speaking Peoples p. barbarian kingdom Vandals Suebians Visigoths Heavens p. remainder Rome territory nature wa decade Flavius Aëtius play Rome barbarian invader	9
army Visigoths Arles Narbonne	9
army enemy Visigoths Huns Plains Matyszak ''The Enemies Rome p. ''The Decline Fall Roman Empire p. 489Jordanes ''The Origins Deeds Goths beating Altinum Mediolanum Jordanes ''The Origins Deeds Goths Ticinum Patavium Rome	9
champion Empire point Aëtius wa slain Emperor III hand Sidonius observe ''I ignorant sir motif provocation man ha cut right hand left .Gibbon ''The Decline Fall Roman Empire ch	9
Carthage city empire wa North AD Vandals Gibbon ''The Decline Fall Roman Empire p. ''History Wars Book Pt Ch	9
Empire wa hand troop Odoacer Emperor Romulus AugustusJordanes ''The Origins Deeds Goths wa nobody stop	9
Odoacer hold part Empire Rome part Empire Visigoths Ostrogoths Franks Alans others	9
Empire remnant wa longer Roman nature	9
Byzantine Empire Goths fight Rome area year point Rome importance wa	9
year war city wa AD desolate environment marsh end city world	9
point time Roman Empire stand event Roman history fall category Byzantine history	9