wa support commander emperor meant commander sole control army usurp throne	9
Crisis Century describes turmoil murder usurpation in-fighting murder Emperor Alexander Severus ''The History Rome p. Cassius Dio mark wider decline AD ascension Commodus throne Matyszak ''The Enemies Rome p. judgement Gibbon Gibbon ''The Decline Fall Roman Empire p. Matyszak state rot become	9
crisis century wa absolute Rome decline mark strain empire Romans war day	9
space century officer claimed emperor part empire month day meeting violent end.Matyszak ''The Enemies Rome p. time wa Roman army wa invader point AD.Gibbon ''The Decline Fall Roman Empire p. wa usurpation break Empire crisis wa strength frontier empire force arm	9
situation wa usurper existence	9
Septimius Severus Pescennius Niger rebel emperor troop clashed time AD Cyzicus Niger wa	9
defeat Nicaea year Issus year Niger	9
Niger hope crown laid rest Severus wa deal rival throne person Clodius Albinus Severus	9
Albinus wa emperor troop Gaul Severus Virius Lupus battle turn Lugdunum Severus	9
turmoil Severus threat rest reign Gibbon ''The Decline Fall Roman Empire p. reign successor Caracalla wa Macrinus himsef emperor place	9
Macrinus position Roman senate troop Varius Avitus emperor met battle Antioch AD Macrinus wa defeated.Gibbon ''The Decline Fall Roman Empire p. Avitus – name Elagabalus – wa afterwards Alexander Severus wa emperor Guard senate reign wa turn	9
murderer behalf army lot rule place Maximinus Thrax	9
army Maximinus wa brought Carthage senate II wa murderedGibbon ''The Decline Fall Roman Empire p. force candidate throne III	9
III fate successor Arab year army emperor time Decius Verona seize throne.Gibbon ''The Decline Fall Roman Empire p. battling usurper throne chiefly virtue troop battle commence empire manpower loss strife	9
lone exception rule wa Gallienus emperor AD AD saw array usurper battle	9
army wa AD usurper Tetricus Chalons	9
decade saw number usurper time throne	9
battle turmoil time usurper Carinus Margus become emperor	9
measure stability point empire split Tetrarchy lesser emperor system war time AD	9
year relation tetrarchy Constantine Licinius Maxentius Maximinus jostled control empire	9
Turin Constantine Maxentius Tzirallum Licinius Maximinus	9
AD onwards Constantine Licinius Cibalae Adrianople Hellespont Chrysopolis	9
Constantine Maxentius beating Verona Bridge year	9
Constantine son Constantius II father rule usurper Magnentius Mursa Mons Seleucus	9
emperor Valens Theodosius usurper Thyatira battle Frigidus	9