Tallon form saw Ashes tour part side become cricket history ''Invincibles	8
Tallon wa first-choice wicket-keeper Saggers deputy.Pollard p.	8
spent majority life sunny Queensland cold climate caught Tallon guard	8
wet inner glove wa custom temperature	8
ball meant ball state fast bowling more.Perry p.	8
result strategy wa spinner Test match	8
McCool wa play Test tour Tallon opportunity show ability stump Queensland team-mate.Perry pp	8
tour Tallon struck damp pitch low-scoring match Yorkshire wicket	8
wa closest tourist defeat tour.Fingleton p.	8
Tallon difficulty condition season right finger sight Ray Lindwall bouncer misty morning tour match Surrey Oval wa hit put hand face protection ball bye	8
result injury Tallon wa match	8
bye inning Saggers warm-up match injury error Tallon wa Test Trent Bridge	8
catch dismiss key batsman start innings.Washbrook Edrich men	8
seize initiative start wa eight-wicket victory.Perry p.	8
Tallon tail wag recover position clichéd pun cricket lesser batsman number	8
Tail cricket tailenders inning Bill Johnston Ernie Toshack	8
Tallon concede bye inning wa	8
catch stood Washbrook Toshack toss downwards Tallon ankle	8
described catch Tallon reach order catch	8
dive stop leg glance left finger	8
won Test Tallon wa Test finger recover	8
team played draw match Manchester Tallon Emmett bowling Ray Lindwall catch.Lemmon p.	8
Compton time batsman held host inning together.Fingleton pp	8
Tallon left finger Test injury tour match Middlesex ruling Fourth Test won secure series	8
Saggers stood percentage bye match wicket-keeper tour %	8
Tallon Fifth Test Oval catch catch Len leg side wa catch season.Perry p.	8
series ndash inning win	8
match tour Scotland Aberdeen position Tallon dispense wicket-keeping pad try luck bowling leg spin.Perry p.	8
Tallon Test career first-class cricket ball approximate workload specialist bowler match	8
Tallon moderate success batting Test series	8
team strategy pace bowling saw Tallon catch Tests lead pace bowler Lindwall tour game energy Tests spinner work Tallon catch tour	8
Tallon wa Saggers bye rate Tallon agile catch	8
Tallon performance summer saw ''Wisden Cricketers Year	8