Maharaja Krishnaraja III successor ndash Chamaraja IX Krishnaraja IV ruler Jayachamaraja Mysore court patron music.Weidman p. Tanjore Travancore court patronage preservation art unique combination royal patronage musician music school public interest patronage music publisher producer set Mysore apart.Weidman p. Maharaja Krishnaraja III musician musicologist merit number ''javalis light lyric devotional song title ''Anubhava pancharatna	3
composition bear nom de plume ''mudra Chamundi Chamundeshwari honour Wodeyar family deity.Pranesh p. successor Chamaraja IX house music book phonograph musician palace library	3
Krishnaraja IV art patronage	3
distinct school music importance ''raga ''bhava evolved.Pranesh p. xiii author noteKamath p282 Royal School palace institutionalise art	3
composition staff notation royal musician	3
music wa ndash Cousins piano concerto Palace Orchestra marked celebration centenary	3
Maharaja Jayachamaraja composer ''kritis composition series composer Nikolas Medtner others	3
court music kept time	3
Gramophone palace band commercially.Weidman p. Attention wa paid technology concert	3
sum spent instrument horn violin theremin calliaphone music player.Weidman p. Mysore court wa home expert ''vidwan time	3
Veena Sheshanna court musician rule Maharaja Chamaraja IX Pranesh p. exponent veena.Bakshi p. Kamath p. achievement music won Mysore premier place art music wa honorific Shikhamani Maharaja Krishnaraja Wodeyar IV.Pranesh pp	3
ndash Mysore Vasudevacharya wa musician composer Sanskrit Telugu Mysore.Subramaniyan p. Kamath p. hold unique distinction generation Mysore king ruler court musician them.Pranesh p. p.	3
Muthiah Bhagavatar wa musician-composer Mysore court.Subramaniyan p. Kamath p. composer post-Tyagaraja period Pranesh p. composition Sanskrit Telugu Tamil name Harikesha	3
violinist T. Chowdiah exponent time	3
violin.Pranesh p. p. Chowdiah wa court musician Maharaja Krishnaraja Wodeyar IV title Sangeeta Ratna Sangeeta	3
composition Telugu Sanskrit name Trimakuta .Pranesh p.	3