king vassal Vijayanagara empire decline latter	3
time kingdom village force soldier	3
Timmaraja II chiefdoms Kamath p. ''Bola Chamaraja IV ''lit ruler significance withheld tribute Vijayanagara monarch Aravidu Ramaraya Subrahmanyam p.	3
death Aravidu Ramaraya Wodeyars assert Raja Wodeyar control Srirangapatna Vijayanagara governor ''Mahamandaleshvara Aravidu Tirumalla ndash development ''ex post facto tacit approval Venkatapati Raya incumbent king Vijayanagar empire Chandragiri.Subrahmanyam p. Raja Wodeyar reign saw territorial expansion annexation Channapatna north Jaggadeva RayaSubrahmanyam p. 68Venkata Ramanappa N. p. – development Mysore factor reckon with.Shama Rao Kamath p. Ramanappa N. p.201 ndash Wodeyars deal autonomy overlordship Aravidus tribute transfer revenue Chandragiri	3
wa marked contrast chief ''Nayakas Tamil country pay Chandragiri p. Chamaraja V Narasaraja expand Sultanate Maratha subordinate army Ranadullah siege Srirangapatna.Subrahmanyam p. Kamath p. Ramanappa N. p. Expansionist ambition southward Tamil country Narasaraja Wodeyar Satyamangalam Coimbatore district successor Dodda Devaraja Wodeyar capture Tamil region Erode Dharmapuri chief Madurai	3
invasion Nayakas Malnad wa dealt	3
period wa change 1670s Marathas Mughals Deccan.Subrahmanyam p. Kamath p. Ramanappa N. p. Chikka Devaraja r. ndash Mysore king period survive exigency territory	3
alliance Marathas Mughals.Subrahmanyam p. pp	3
ndash kingdom include Salem east west Chikkamagaluru Tumkur north rest Coimbatore south.Subrahmanyam p. Kamath pp	3
ndash expansion kingdom fair share land heartland Ghats boundary Coromandel plain coastal access	3
Chikka Devaraja attempt remedy brought Mysore conflict ''Nayaka chief Ikkeri king ''Rajas Coorg coast coastal area hill region respectively.Subrahmanyam p. conflict brought result Mysore Periyapatna reversal Palupare.Subrahmanyam p. kingdom ''Mukarasu Narasaraja II survival expansion kingdom wa delicate game alliance negotiation subordination occasion annexation territory direction	3
historian Sanjay Subrahmanyam Sethu Madhava Rao Mysore wa Mughal empire	3
Mughul record claim tribute ''peshkash wa payed Mysore	3
historian Suryanath Kamath feel Mughals Mysore situation brought Mughal ndash Maratha competition supremacy India.Subrahmanyam pp	3
ndash Kamath p. Mughal empire decline complication arose Mughal resident Arcot Sira tribute.Subrahmanyam p. year saw Krishnaraja Wodeyar tread matter chief Marathas bay	3
wa Chamaraja Wodeyar VI reign power hand prime minister ''Dalwai ''Dalavoy Nanjarajiah Nanjaraja chief minister ''Sarvadhikari Devarajiah Devaraja brother town Nanjangud rule decade Wodeyars titular heads.Pranesh pp	3
ndash p. latter part rule Krishnaraja II saw Sultanates Mughals confusion Haider Ali captain army prominence	3
victory Marathas annexation territory iconic figure	3
honour achievement king title Nawab Haider Ali Bahadur .Kamath p.	3