weather Normandy preparation counter stroke harassment aircraft artillery fire start time afternoon	9
number reinforcement VIII Corps sector Jackson p. reconnaissance VIII Corps commander O ’ Connor Germans	9
XXX Corps wa way north VIII Corps right flank O'Connor attack Corps VIII Corps adopt defensive posture	9
Miles Dempsey Army privy ULTRA decrypts signal traffic knew counterattack O'Connor precaution	9
defensive VIII Corps reorganise order meet attack came.Jackson p. Supply echelon division Évrecy ndash Noyers-Bocage ndash Villers-Bocage area focus RAF fighter-bomber attention morning afternoon RAF claimed destruction vehicle	9
armour artillery barrage battalion SS Panzer Division panzergrenadiers battalion dug Caen ndash Villers-Bocage road.Clark pp	9
ndash Division Brigade swept wood orchard Tourville-sur-Odon river north Baron-sur-Odon bank.Clark p. initiative le	9
attempt 15th Division Brigade advance towards Odon link force Gavrus bridge position Clark p. salient Battalion Royal Tank Regiment capture Hill north Évrecy Clark p. 10th SS Panzer tanks.Jackson p. strengthen position element Division attack Esquay-Notre-Dame west Hill infantry tank attack slope hill wa Germans position	9
II SS Panzer Corps SS Panzer Division mdash Weidinger left flank mdash cut right salient north Odon 10th SS Panzer Division wa retake Gavrus Hill south river.Clark p. SS Panzer attack artillery	9
regiment division Panthers Panzer IV assault gun le Haut du Bosq le Valtru Cheux objective.Reynolds p. company wa overrun tank infantry le Valtru anti-tank gun tank village artillery fire infantry withdraw	9
time hand-to-hand combat place	9
Panzergrenadiers key wood counterattack	9
panzergrenadiers claimed source support nightfall infantry firm control village	9
p. officer SS Panzer DivisionWilmot p. wa reconnaissance mission	9
wa found map notebook detail attack	9
Germans strike 15th Infantry Division right flank.Williams p. unit wa process confusion tank infantry defence unit Williams p. resistance	9
SS Panzer stopped.Reynolds p. attack flank tank concentration Carpiquet area RAF fighter-bombers afternoon attack	9
10th SS Panzer Division attack schedule	9
clash day hour intense combat infantry Gavrus pocket bridge north village	9
artillery bombardment Germans withdraw reoccupy village	9
towards Hill element 10th SS Panzer ran tank infantry Évrecy attempt occupy hill	9
obstacle remainder day division attack Hill wa postponed.Clark p. Germans claimed destruction tank record loss 12.Reynolds pp	9
ndash action counterattack day Dempsey Odon bridgehead brigade division perimeter	9
Infantry Brigade Division wa command 15th Infantry Division Ellis pp	9
ndash O ’ Connor ’ s wish infantry Dempsey Welsh Infantry Division VIII Corps lead brigade Epsom start line night.Jackson p. order retain possession Hill Dempsey need hold Évrecy Hill task moment resource for.Hart pp	9
ndash Brigade abandon hill	9
key position retain wa Rauray Odon Hart p. dark Dempsey withdrew Brigade north river Jackson p. position meet offensive.Ellis p.	9