Field Marshal Erwin Rommel force Normandy wa Hitler launch counteroffensive line town Caumont Saint-Lô	9
objective wa cut corridor army city coastline beyond.Wilmot p. SS Panzer Divisions ''Heer Panzer Division task	9
attack wa 10th SS Panzer Divisions II SS Panzer Corps Ukraine Reynolds p. SS Panzer Divisions Panzer Division.Wilmot map p. vast majority tank formation Panzer IVs assault gun Panthers Tigers mdash latter lethal vehicles.Williams p. Montgomery commander ground force Normandy directive Miles Dempsey capture CaenClark pp	9
ndash pincer attack.Ellis p. plan XXX Corps attack west Caen day VIII Corps launch attack Orne bridgehead east Caen	9
wa VIII Corps perimeter Orne bridgehead plan wa	9
plan operation place day assault	9
Highland Infantry Division wa strike south Orne bridgehead element Panzer Division	9
Operation MartletClark p. Operation Dauntless Ellis p. wa commence day Epsom XXX Infantry Division Brigade wa secure VIII flank ground right axis advance	9
role Operation Epsom wa VIII Corps men command O'Connor.Jackson pp	9
VIII Corps launch beachhead Infantry Division	9
operation split phase Corps advance capture ground Bretteville-sur-Laize south Caen.Clark pp	9
ndash fire artillery piece cruiser monitor H.M.S	9
Royal Force provide air support bombardment bombers.Clark p. 15th Infantry Division lead assault	9
Phase tasked village Sainte Manvieu Cheux	9
Phase II ''Hangover division exploit capture Odon River village Mouen Grainville-sur-Odon	9
alternative resistance opening phase prove light Division rush bridge Odon River ''coup de .Jackson p. opening phase Wessex Infantry Division mdash Guards Division infantry brigade mdash wa remain start line provide firm base .Jackson pp	9
ndash Epsom phase ''Impetigo Division move relieve infantry north Odon	9
15th Division river bridgehead key village	9
operation phase ''Goitre element Division cross river hold area 15th Division continue expand bridgehead	9
addition Division attempt force River Orne advance objective Bretteville-sur-Laize	9
Brigade Division wa operation Odon Orne protect Corps flank position attack westward towards Caen	9
success VIII Corps attack Corps launch operation ''Aberlour ''Ottawa	9
Infantry Division infantry brigade attack north Caen latter move Infantry Division Brigade village airfield Carpiquet.Stacey p. Epsom wa deficiency manpower material.Jackson p. opposition Epsom wa SS Panzer Division Hitlerjugend Hitler Youth element Panzer Division Panzer Lehr.Clark p.	9