Between troop Hyakutake troop employ	9
loss position east side Matanikau attack US defense coast	9
observation defence Lunga Point staff officer Hyakutake thrust attack south Field	9
Division troop Division Lieutenant Masao Maruyama soldier infantry regiment battalion wa march jungle attack defence south east bank Lunga River	9
Division wa split unit Unit Yumio Nasu Infantry Regiment Unit troop Infantry Regiment Infantry Division division reserve Maruyama Infantry Regiment.Jersey ''Hell Islands p. p. Rottman Army p. p. ''Pearl Harbor p. Griffith ''Battle p.	9
state force Battalion 124th Infantry Regiment wa part Infantry Brigade Edson Ridge	9
state wa Battalion 124th battalion Infantry Regiment part Independent Trench Mortar Battalion Independent Rapid-Fire Gun Battalion Independent Rapid-Fire Gun Battalion Independent Mountain Artillery	9
Maruyama force jungle reach line	9
initiative shift right unit east defense weaker area	9
Maruyama staff officer attack plan	9
wa command Colonel Toshinari Shōji commander Infantry Regiment	9
left right force reach line Hyakutake attack	9
Americans unaware approach Maruyama forces.Griffith ''Battle p. p. Rottman Army p.	9
Maruyama force US Lunga perimeter	9
night Maruyama force frontal assault position troop Battalion 7th Marines Lieutenant Colonel Chesty Puller US Army Battalion 164th Infantry Regiment Lieutenant Colonel Hall	9
US Marine Army rifle machine gun mortar artillery canister fire mm anti-tank gun wrought carnage Japanese.Frank p.	9
Maruyama troop attack Americans	9
Shōji right unit attack remain place cover Nasu right flank attack area US force materialized.Hough ''Pearl Harbor p. p. Griffith ''Battle p. p.	9
Hyakutake attack force retreat	9
Maruyama left division reserve survivor retreat Matanikau River area right unit Shōji wa told head Point east Lunga River.Frank Zimmerman Campaign p. Griffith ''Battle p. ''Pearl Harbor p. Rottman Army p. p.	9
provide support right unit Shōji Detachment towards Express night land troop company Infantry Regiment mountain gun provision ammunition Point	9
radio intelligence communication effort Marine command try intercept	9
unit operation west Matanikau Vandgrift spare battalion	9
Battalion 7th Marine Regiment Lieutenant Colonel Herman east Lunga Point Point dark day	9
Metapona River mouth deployed troop wood beach await arrival ships.Zimmerman Campaign p. Griffith ''Battle p. ''Pearl Harbor p. p. p. Hammel p. p. ''Hell Islands p.	9
state troop Company Infantry Lt Tamotsu Shinno Battery Mountain Artillery Regiment gun	9
provision bale rice ten bale miso	9