Bertin textbook ''The Game Chess play understood attack	8
consistent view virtue move begin initiative try extend middlegame Black strive neutralize initiative attain equality.Evans p	8
Chess book Black goal opening equality	8
variant Black secure equality search chance gain advantage	8
Books half century need	8
begin initiative minor mistake lead loss initiative mistake Black consequence	8
case face position Black	8
Sveshnikov Black player afford slightest mistake point view task Black chess ha strive win draw	8
Adorján Sveshnikov hypocrite statement p. father Sveshnikov Variation Defense opening de p.	8
Chess theorist initiative side play game end win draw	8
Walker move advantage move worth	8
book Walker ha move ha advantage measure choose plan attack whereas player Openings act defensive move advantage move cease	8
Steinitz World Champion father chess briefly Emanuel Lasker lengthy tribute Steinitz Lasker pp	8
expert proper play side legitimate issue game draw	8
Lasker Capablanca World Champions	8
resource side advantage move sufficient force defence resignation	8
Capablanca complain foremost master absorbed principle technique longer hope win game chess played	8
Capablanca thought chess wa demise human mind wa ability choose move multitude combination variation extent respect draw	8
Reuben Fine world player chess Fine wa player world	8
Hooper Whyld p. opening advantage sufficient win error Black	8
fact side play draw result	8
opening advantage nature error win	8
view game chess end draw play prevails	8
fact position drawn doe seem assumption point view	8
point view Rowson mean viewpoint omniscient observer perfect chess	8
level hypertheory concept advantage side meaningless assessment position win win Black draw	8
agrees proper result played chess game draw	8
course prove doubt player disagree	8
last-round draw reporter 'Well chess draw	8
Rowson quote chess draw	8
World Champion Bobby Fischer thought wa so.Fischer think definite game draw	8
Pal Benko writes Fischer believed—as player first-move advantage amount win	8
nineteen game played Fischer win Black	8
Lasker Capablanca chess suffer draw death top-level player drew games.Saidy p.	8
Fischer game ha become played	8
rule chess number drawn game	8
Lasker le half point draw half point opponent king	8
Capablanca Capablanca chess chess variant played board piece	8
Fischer Fischer Random Chess chess variant position piece random	8
Today sharpest opening variation deeply weapon	8
example level Black Marshall Attack Ruy Lopez line Black sacrifice pawn chance endgame Black pawn draw correct play.Watson pp	8
article view Marshall Attack end	8
top level game draw 'White ha nothing	8
Bogdan Marshall Attack weapon Spassky Candidates Match World Champion Mikhail Tal	8
Donner Marshall Attack sacrifice pawn nowadays played purpose	8
GMs Georgiev Atanas wa Pawn Variation Najdorf arises c5 d6 cxd4 Nf6 a6 e6 Qb6	8
ha sharpest foolhardy opening lines.Watson Qb6 move chess principle reject beginner mistake	8
Pawn Variation brilliant grandmaster Salo Flohr 'In chess rule opening haste piece move piece time queen	8
ancient law hold Bobby Fischer	8
p. Pawn Variation wa GMs crazy Bent	8
Siegbert Tarrasch treatise ''The Game Chess raid Queen game	8
capture Queen pawn Queen brings revenge	8
game Qxb2 Qa3.Watson p.	8
Georgiev seldom level line variation lead play draw check.Georgiev p.	8
game remain word theory Georgiev p.	8
Vallejo Pons – Page mention Vallejo Pons – game	8
c5 d6 cxd4 Nf6 a6 e6 Qb6 Qxb2 Qa3 Nc6 fxe6 bxc6 dxe5 gxf6 Qxa2 Be7 O-O Ra7 Rd7 Rf7 Rxd1+ Qa5 Qd8 Qxd1+ Qxc2+ Qd1+ Qc2+ Bc5+ Qxc5+ Qf2+ Qd4+ Qf2+ Qd4+ escape check	8
Georgiev assessment ha question ha line high-level game	8