studio sequel ''Frankenstein preview film wa Henry Frankenstein survival.Curtis p. Whale idea dry Vieria p. film	5
success Whale ''The Man producer Laemmle Whale wa director Whale advantage situation studio ''One River .Curtis p. Whale sequel top hoot	5
studio publicist Whale Universal studio psychiatrist Monster mental age boy age lad fifteen	5
Screenwriter Florey treatment ''The Adventures Frankenstein ndash Monster Lives	5
Universal staff writer Reed treatment title ''The Return Frankenstein title	5
acceptance Reed script wa Hays office review	5
script review Whale stink heaven .Curtis p. G. writer Whale found work unsatisfactory	5
Whale set work version wa incident novel creature demand mate	5
novel Frankenstein creates mate destroys life	5
month Whale wa work project playwright Hurlbut Edmund Pearson	5
script element number version wa Hays office review pp	5
Newman report Whale Elizabeth heart donor bride film historian Scott MacQueen state Whale intention	5
Sources report Lugosi Claude Rains degree seriousness role Frankenstein mentor Pretorius Lennig p. others report role wa Thesiger.Skal p. Clarke ill health Valerie Hobson Henry Frankenstein love interest Elizabeth	5
production Whale actress cast play play Shelley film prologue represent story ndash horror ndash spring dark side imagination.Vieira p. Brigitte Helm Phyllis Elsa Lanchester	5
Lanchester husband met moderate success	5
fame film Whale ''The Old Dark won Academy Award role ''The Life Henry VIII	5
Lanchester Whale offer role.Curtis pp	5
sequence Whale shot multiple angle Lanchester herself sore throat codeine.Vieira p. Colin role ''Frankenstein creator creation	5
Hobson alcoholism Whale recast role quality wa film	5
argument wa monster impact charm wa wa inarticulate – inarticulate creature	5
moment spoke play straight	5
Gifford p. decision meant dental plate cheek sunken look film	5
Whale studio psychiatrist simple word Monster test paper studio	5
Dwight Frye play doctor assistant played hunchback Fritz	5
Frye scene villager role Nephew Glutz man uncle death Monster	5
wa Universal custom height career	5
Elsa Lanchester Shelley nod film Monster bride	5
Universal makeup artist Pierce paid attention Monster appearance film	5
design display after-effects mill fire scar Monster hair.Curtis p. course Pierce Monster makeup indicate Monster injury film	5
Pierce makeup input Whale iconic hair style Nefertiti	5
Lanchester hair wa Marcel wave wire frame achieve style	5
Lanchester disliked Pierce feel people wa god morning hospital perform operation	5
Vieira p. play Shelley Lanchester wore net dress sequin butterfly star moon actress heard woman week	5
Strickfaden number machine ''Frankenstein use Ray Diffuser p. Nebularium .Goldman p. bolt Strickfaden equipment ha become stock scene number film television shows.Picart ''et al	5
p. man film effect wa P. head effect department Universal Studios time.Picart ''et al	5
p. homunculus course day actor full-size jar velvet perspective on-set jar	5
foreground film plate wa rotoscoped rear plate	5
actor Barty briefly film homunculus infant chair Whale cut infant reveal film release	5
Whale met Franz party score picture	5
Nothing picture end destruction scene	5
distinctive theme Monster Pretorius	5
score Whale suggestion dissonant chord convey idea explosion wa theater film wa wa it.Curtis p. Constantin Bakaleinikoff musician record score session.Curtis p. p. xvii budget US – budget – schedule.Curtis p. day water destroyed windmill rubber suit costume	5
day broke hip stunt	5
film wa ten day schedule Whale shut picture ten day Heggie play Hermit.Curtis pp	5
Whale survival Hobson laboratory	5
Whale cut time minute re-shooting re-editing day film date	5