opera D'Oyly Carte sent company province	6
D'Oyly Carte company played ''Pinafore Carte aegis year revival	6
opera wa rest repertory time 1940.Rollins Witts pp	6
Gilbert revival lifetime death D'Oyly Carte Opera Company right Savoy opera	6
hew Gilbert direction period Gilbert plot book licensee closely.Bradley p. revival opera dress.Rollins Witts Appendix p. VII designer Percy Anderson Sheringham Goffin costume designs.Mander pp	6
winter ndash D'Oyly Carte Opera Company scenery costume ''Pinafore opera destroyed bomb World II.Rollins Witts p. opera wa summer 1947.Rollins Witts pp	6
wa D'Oyly Carte repertory season company closure 1982.Rollins Witts pp	6
supplement D'Oyly Carte company ''Pinafore Queen Elizabeth II royal family Windsor Castle royal command performance Gilbert Sullivan opera	6
D'Oyly Carte Opera Company company present Savoy opera copyright end amateur school society century. theatre programme ''The Gilbert Sullivan company production opera	6
Tyrone production Stratford Ontario p. Sadler Wells Opera Company production Sadler Wells Theatre production Gilbert Sullivan wa York.Traubner	6
''The Times Opera Welsh Opera opera company production D'Oyly Carte Opera Company closure chapter ''passim year Rosa Opera Company ha ''Pinafore time Dido Aeneas/ Acis Galatea ''The Times Opera della Luna company continue mount piece	6
success ''Pinafore wa first-hand Williamson	6
arrangement D'Oyly Carte present opera production opening Theatre Royal Sydney	6
opera company played frequent season work subsequent Savoy opera ''Sydney Gilbert Sullivan website	6
''A Gilbert Sullivan Discography piece popularity	6
Internet Database link forty production	6
Internet Database repertory company present ''Pinafore Opera la Carte Ohio Light Opera Gilbert Sullivan Players tour opera seasons.Smith	6
''The Times ''Pinafore world opera company Royal Theatre Copenhagen Opera Essgee Entertainment others Samarkand Uzbekistan.Bradley chapter table show history D'Oyly Carte production tour Gilbert lifetime	6