''The News opera dialogue joke song wa public joke	6
Savoy ha brilliant success	6
Playhouses ''The News col. ''The Theatre opera ha heard part globe occasion descant	6
Omnibus-Box ''The Theatre Series revival ''The Athenaeum praise piece establishment critique Sullivan	6
hand ''Pinafore sound fresher	6
world ha become – – hear merry piece music character … way display ability order	6
hand Sullivan path music symphony result manner ''Pinafore set u composer libretto kind scope exercise gift	6
''The Athenæum opera – stage play sort – wa ''Pinafore … ha success wherever theater – Buenos Aires Cape Town Shanghai Madrid Ottawa Melbourne Rome	6
''Baltimore Evening Gilbert Sullivan death Gilbert Sullivan D'Oyly Carte Opera Company right perform opera Great year season month	6
''The Times company production review audience wa ''Pinafore played week	6
cast Leo Sheffield Captain Henry Elsie Griffin Josephine Hay Bertha Buttercup splendid tone	6
opera climax season ''H.M.S	6
Revival Princes Theatre ''The Times p. year report season performance Derek Oldham ideal hero Sydney brought house song Fancourt Deadeye wa piece caricature wa pleasure hear principal ''H.M.S	6
Sullivan Opera Season End ''The Times p. review company ''Pinafore	6
Novelty Tradition Savoy Operettas ''The Times p. Williamson right ''Pinafore	6
Williamson played wife Moore played Josephine	6
production performer ''Sydney production fun wa precise number laughter applause immense audience wa	6
''Sydney Williamson company produce ''Pinafore tour 1960s success	6
Williamson need money put G S .Bradley p. ''Pinafore garner praise	6
1950s version Copenhagen example wa performance packed house H.M.S	6
Pinafore Again Delights Danes ''The Times p. Translations language production place remote Samarkand Uzbekistan successful.Bradley Chapter production	6
Gilbert Sullivan performance copyright wa force Approach ''H.M.S	6
Pinafore ''The Times p. ''Pinafore amateur company	6
''The Times review production 6,000-seat Hippodrome royal entertainment	6
opera mammoth spectacle chorus Hippodrome tank harbour	6
Buttercup entrance Pinafore sight Deadeye wa thrown overboard splash	6
''Times hearty subtlety dialogue need	6
production liberty music Sullivan work	6
paper mild satire ''Pinafore universal ''H.M.S	6
Pinafore la Hippodrome Sail Tank Saucy Ship Beauty ''The Times p. paper Winthrop Ames production ''Pinafore spectacular .Atkinson G. ''The Times p. X1 production continue	6
''The Times review Gilbert Sullivan Players season Gilbert theme class inequality nationalism incompetent authority remain relevant	6
appeal ''Pinafore ilk matter genius Sullivan ’ s supply melodies.Smith	6
''The Times expiry copyright company world produce Gilbert Sullivan work adapt please year	6
Productions ''Pinafore amateur range D'Oyly Carte vein Essgee Entertainment Simon Gallaher Opera della Luna	6
Pinafore ha Gilbert Sullivan operas.Bradley p.	6
CultureVulture.net Productions continue number world	6
D'Oyly Carte Opera Company set orchestra part production ''Pinafore ''Pirates ''Mikado	6
doe account rental company theatre company borrow score use piano orchestra	6
production ''Pinafore year worldwide	6