process reform Roman consul Gaius Marius programme reform Roman	9
BC citizen wealth class entry Roman army.Boak ''A History Rome A.D. p. Santosuosso Heavens p. move process century property requirement service.Gabba Rome Army Allies p. distinction ''hastati ''principes ''triarii become wa Scullard ''A History Rome p. infantry imagination wa	9
drawn citizen stock time Roman Latin citizenship ancient Cisalpine Gaul.Luttwak ''The Strategy Roman Empire p. Lighter citizen infantry ''velites ''equites ''auxilia consist mercenaries.Santosuosso Heavens p. concentration citizen legion force infantry Rome army cavalry attachment support	9
necessity legion number lighter troop Tacitus ''Annals IV drawn non-citizens Empire territory	9
exception legion province period wa legion wa province Galatia	9
Marius legion drawn volunteer citizen citizen duty.Luttwak ''The Strategy Roman Empire p. Volunteers citizen city Rome countryside town Roman control.Santosuosso Heavens p. Whereas veteran experience service campaigns.Santosuosso Heavens p. legion legion Empire Roman origin number troop incorporated.Smith ''Service Roman Army p. army higher-level officer commander drawn Roman aristocracy	9
longer basis protect land	9
standard pay state basis	9
consequence duty appeal poorest section society guaranteed salary wa attractive.Gabba Rome Army Allies p. army proportion poor—than previously.Boak ''A History Rome p. consequence development wa proletariat position state	9
professionalisation wa provide permanent garrison distant territory something army citizen militia	9
note wa need raise legion emergency repel threat	9
argues type legion.Smith ''Service Roman Army p. legion deployed troop army	9
legion contrast men experience adventure plunder	9
distinction pay discipline armour type legion	9
practice veteran troop signing legion meant army archetype	9
legion sub-unit wa ''cohort infantrymen.Luttwak ''The Strategy Roman Empire p. cohort wa unit ''maniple sub-unit wa centuriae men	9
centuria wa tent group Latin ''contubernia men	9
Legions body men Roman cavalry Latin ''equites legionis	9
''equites scout dispatch rider battlefield cavalry.Webster ''The Roman Army p. Legions group artillery crew men operate device ''ballistae	9
legion wa number ''auxiliae troops.Luttwak ''The Strategy Roman Empire p. addition troop Roman army wa formalisation arrangement light troop Socii Roman citizenship War.Smith ''Service Roman Army p. troop light cavalry ''alae light infantry ''cohors auxiliae mixture ''cohors equitata	9
Cavalry type archer Latin ''sagittarii shock cavalry Latin ''cataphracti ''clibanarii lancer Latin ''antesignani ''lancearii	9
Infantry bow spear sword spear	9
unit chief period organisation wa left commanders.Webster ''The Roman Army p. deficiency Roman army shortage cavalry cavalry Luttwak ''The Strategy Roman Empire p. troop infantry	9
Luttwak argues force Cretan archer slinger infantry fought foot.Luttwak ''The Strategy Roman Empire p. Rome border adversary troop Roman army disadvantage East	9
size subjugation Mediterranean Roman navy underwent revitalisation meet demand	9
Caesar invasion fleet wa Channel invasion ''Britannia Pompey fleet wa Mediterranean sea pirate	9
war thousand ship service city	9