distinction frontier guard troop mobile reserve force use troop man frontier ''Britannia century AD use provincial emergency legion	9
Empire demand frontier reserve force division type troop	9
Border fortification hereditary militia Latin ''limitanei ''riparienses post ''.Vogt ''The Decline Rome p. rear lay mobile troop field army ''comitatenses held reserve.Boak ''A History Rome AD	9
p. Vogt ''The Decline Rome p. provincial reserve ''cunei cavalry ''auxilia time infantry cavalry units.Luttwak ''The Strategy Roman Empire p. time emperor Constantine reserve Latin ''scholae held rear ''comitatenses presence emperor East respectively.Vogt ''The Decline Rome p. core troop Emperor bodyguard field army AD seem simple bodyguard force campaign vexillation support.Campbell ''The Army p. troop type ''limitanei border guard quality Boak ''A History Rome AD	9
p. Grant ''A History Rome p. Santosuosso Heavens p. peasant-soldiers inferior legion inferior counterpart mobile field armies.Luttwak ''The Strategy Roman Empire pp	9
''limitanei deal action low-intensity incursion duty incident provincial troop	9
scale incursion scale wa task ''comitatenses mobile field troop emperor ''scholae	9
border field army mix infantry cavalry Scullard ''A History Rome p. weight cavalry wa authority mobile field army	9
quarter army cavalry troopsBoak ''A History Rome AD	9
work Eleventh Edition ''Encyclopedia state Roman Empire wa marked predominance horseman century Ages author infantry predominant.Elton ''Warfare Roman A.D. pp	9
Treadgold ''Byzantium Army pp	9
dispute structure wa put place Emperor Constantine Roman Army century degree.Southern ''The Roman Army pp	9
predecessor thirty year Gallienus mobile reserve assist empire border force Campbell ''The Army p. ''The Roman Army pp	9
Constantine nascent force permanent field armies.Southern ''The Roman Army pp	9
Recruitment amongst Roman citizen become consequence population Boak ''A History Rome AD	9
p. Scullard ''A History Rome p. Vogt ''The Decline Rome p. category service spread Christianity pacifist message	9
Gibbon ''The Decline Fall Roman Empire Chapter XXXVIII p. Grant History Rome p. Santosuosso Heavens p. factor withdrawal class form activity	9
Vogt ''The Decline Rome p. place Rome people living empire border	9
people barbarian semi-barbarians land empire Alfoldi ''The Crisis Empire p. Boak ''A History Rome AD p. Vogt ''The Decline Rome p. colony ''Carpi ''Bastarnae ''Sarmatians .Gibbon ''The Decline Fall Roman Empire Chapter VI p. unit described ''legiones 5th century border field army Luttwak ''The Strategy Roman Empire p. system wa principate empire	9
term legion structure role legion	9
century legion role elite infantry wa reducedBoak ''A History Rome AD	9
p. Vogt ''The Decline Rome p. entirely.Luttwak ''The Strategy Roman Empire p. legion longer drawn Roman citizen	9
Campbell ''The Crisis Empire p. Constantine legion infantry unit source forebear	9
lighter armament consent wear weight body armour Scullard ''A History Rome p. instance armour order increase mobility.Alfoldi ''The Crisis Empire p. Fourth-century legion time sixth size legion combination spear bow dart sword emphasis fighting.Alfoldi ''The Crisis Empire p. Luttwak ''The Strategy Roman Empire p. ''auxilia ''numeri disappeared.Alfoldi ''The Crisis Empire p. Constantine proportion troop army Grant ''A History Rome p. impact wa dress	9
start reign Roman army men end reign number men.Treadgold ''A History Byzantine State Society	9