Shackleton wa crew expedition ''Nimrod Joyce wa recruit	3
story Shackleton saw Joyce bus wa passing expedition office sent someone fetch spot told true.Riffenburgh p. Fisher p. Huntford p. tell story	3
Fisher cite Shackleton biographer H R Mill Huntford story	3
join expedition Joyce bought release year claim Shackleton recompense promise so.Riffenburgh p126 wa dispute money relation pp	3
ndash describes Joyce claim Shackleton member expedition experience basis ''Discovery exploit Joyce wa put charge store sledge dog	3
departure crash course printing Causton printing firm Shackleton publish book magazine p. ''Nimrod left wa towed towards pack ice tug ''Koonya .Riffenburgh pp	3
ndash power Ice Shelf Great Ice Barrier Barrier Shackleton base headquarters inlet ''Discovery voyage	3
inlet Scott Shackleton balloon flight become bay ndash Bay Whales	3
Shackleton ice wa secure	3
year base Pole expedition	3
alternative site VII Land Shackleton wa break agreement Scott ''Nimrod McMurdo Sound.Riffenburgh pp	3
ndash site chosen base wa Cape Royds north Scott ''Discovery headquarters Hut Point	3
process ship Joyce ashore dog pony build expedition hut.Riffenburgh p. call process store shore base	3
wa combination adverse weather over-caution Nimrod captain Rupert	3
ndash party ascent Mount Erebus climb himself.Mills p. winter Joyce help copy expedition book ''Aurora Australis Shackleton.About copy book sewn bound Mills p. ndash source	3
Copies existence worth sum	3
facsimile edition wa SeTo	3
wa equipment store season journey Pole view experience	3
mishap number pony Shackleton cut party number	3
wa Joyce advice expedition doctor Marshall Joyce liver problem stage heart disease.Riffenburgh p. wa journey party bid reach Pole Joyce Marston useless grub-scoffing beggar ndash Marshall Jameson Adams ndash	3
p. Joyce resentment preparatory work polar party southward march days.Riffenburgh p. month charge depot adequate supply party	3
cache luxury Minna Bluff life-saving food fuel praise.Riffenburgh pp	3
ndash Shackleton party ''Nimrod date home	3
prime S mile statute mile km Pole	3
Joyce remain base rearguard wait party fate return.Riffenburgh p. ''Nimrod wa Joyce direction exhibition polar artefact	3
Shackleton paid salary £250 year equivalent approx	3
Joyce absence paid employment expedition	3