village birthplace people astronomer Alcock MBE discoverer nova comet vol.111 no.2 pp.64-66	2
Clare poet nineteenth century Robinson ''Oxford Biography Oxford Press subscription	2
artist Christopher Perkins Collins J	2
Biography vol.4 Auckland Press Henry Royce Baronet Seaton engineer co-founder Rolls-Royce.Jeremy J	2
''Oxford Biography Oxford Press subscription	2
Physician actor author Hill work Biography botany born Peterborough.O'Connor ''Oxford Biography Oxford Press subscription	2
socialist writer illustrator Horrabin wa born city wa member parliament rev	2
Amanda ''Oxford Biography Oxford Press subscription	2
philosopher Cumberland wa 14th Lord Bishop death Jon ''Oxford Biography Oxford Press subscription	2
nurse Edith Cavell part education Laurel Minster Precinct plaque name hospital.Daunton Claire ''Oxford Biography Oxford Press subscription	2
prominent figure born Hereward outlaw resistance Norman lends name place business Mellows ed	2
''The Chronicle Candidus p.41 History Scientific Society Payne group prominent Catholics Forty Martyrs Wales wa Pope Leo XIII Pope VI	2
''Omelia del Santo Padre Paolo VI	2
Musicians include organist conductor principal Royal Academy Stoker ''Oxford Biography Oxford Press subscription	2
lead vocalist pop duo Erasure ''BBC News Online	2
Forgie leader BBC Band Vinyl Vulture	2
Don Lusher OBE trombonist professor Royal College Royal Marines School Voce ''The Independent	2
Nicholas actor singer Internet Movie Database	2
Palmer Maxim Reality MC dance act ProdigyMontalbano ''The Independent	2
mdash 'Gizz played guitar Prodigy life area mdash Sixsmith keytar player founder member Art Sound SoundClick	2
Skins actor Luke Pasqualino Reinis Nick Evening Telegraph Jonathan Gill Arishay fellow bandmate Merrygold lead singer X Factor Series runner-up JLS Peterborough. Evening Telegraph	2
living personality include television presenter Sarah Cawood Maxey ''Liverpool Post BBC presenter Jake wa born city. Evening Telegraph	2
Durham football journalist radio broadcaster Terry	2
''The Independent biologist author broadcaster Prof. Brian School life Eastrea Whittlesey.Pearson Mark Evening Telegraph facsimile p.23 Brian	2
businessman Boizot MBE OMRI founder Pizza Express restaurant chain ha life accolade freedom city.Muir Jonny Evening Telegraph	2
Tottenham footballer wa born city ESPNsoccernet	2
Stoke midfielder Matthew Etherington career youth academy Football Database	2
team wa Simon Davies Etherington joint transfer Tottenham Hotspur. Football Database	2
Former goalkeeper Seaman MBE name club. ''The	2
Motorcycle racer city death high-speed crash Brands Hatch Evening Telegraph doe Great gymnast win Olympic medal century	2