country wa Zaire army wa FAZ	9
Mobutu FAZ intervene Angolan Civil Liberation Front FNLA fight Marxist Popular Movement Liberation MPLA	9
policy MPLA won Front Liberation Congo Zaire Province Shaba resistance FAZ	9
invasion Shaba I. Mobutu request assistance wa Morocco form troop MPLA Cuban advisor	9
humiliation episode unrest Zaire FAZ put down.John World Armies Facts File pp	9
performance Zaire Shaba evidence chronic weakness extend day .Ed	9
W. Meditz Tim Merrill problem wa soldier area pay period	9
officer kept money soldier inept leadership FAZ	9
month Shaba invasion Mobutu sought solution problem army dismal performance	9
reform command structure wholesale high-ranking officer	9
staff staff chief staff addition position minister defense supreme commander held	9
redeployed force country case	9
Division Division wa North	9
Infantry Brigade Infantry Brigade 14th Infantry Brigade	9
Michela Emperor Mobutu Transition—Issues Volume pp	9
time army formation president wa Shaba	9
addition change army strength wa percent	9
Zaire influx equipment adviser force	9
army structure Mobotu rule IISS Balance FAZ wa infantry battalion Guard battalion infantry battalion parachute commando unit parachute brigade	9
car regiment infantry battalion	9
army wa brigade group parachute division.IISS Balance p.45 addition unit tank battalion wa World Armies Facts File p.	9
state discipline force apparent	9
Foreign assistance Zaire end Cold Mobutu condition deteriorate threaten hold power	9
wage lack pay paratrooper intervention 'Operation 'Operation Beam Cooper Pit Weinert Combat Information force	9
Country Studies FAZ ground force infantry division infantry brigade brigade parachute battalion support battalion force commando/counterinsurgency brigade Division brigade infantry brigade infantry battalion support battalion	9
unit deployed country concentration Shaba Region half force	9
Division infantry brigade Shaba Region Infantry Brigade wa Lubumbashi Infantry Brigade wa deployed Shaba battalion Brigade stayed	9
concentration force wa Brigade wa deployed Ndjili Airport outskirt capital Division DSP adjacent compound Brigade wa Mbanza-Ngungu Bas-Congo kilometer southwest	9
list unit overstates capability force time	9
privileged formation Division Brigade unit paid	9
ability force destroyed politicisation force tribalisation division force purge disloyal group Mobutu divide rule.Jacques Ebenga Thierry N ’ Landu Evolutions Revolutions Security Studies Pretoria p.66–70 background deterioration state structure Mobutu regime	9