ibericus Chiffchaff brighter greener rump yellower ''P	1
brehmii type specimen taxon Chiffchaff	1
specie found Portugal west line Pyrenees Salomon Marc ''Behaviour	1
mountain Mediterranean Common Chiffchaffs co-occur narrow band line	1
Alfonso Cuesta Miguel Ángel Caballero José María	1
northernmost section precise course contact zone	1
long-distance migrant specie winter	1
c. collybita vocalisation Salomon Marc Hemim Y	1
morphology Salomon Marc Helbig Andreas Riofrio J	1
Morphometric differentiation male Common Chiffchaffs ''Phylloscopus collybita Vieillot Chiffchaffs ''P	1
brehmii Homeyer contact zone Aves Sylviidae	1
Helbig Andreas Salomon Marc Seibold	1
hybridization contact zone male ''P	1
c. collybita hybrid show fitness hybrid female sterile Haldane Rule	1
Helbig Andreas Salomon Marc Joël ''C	1
latter aspect note Chiffchaff lineage chiffchaffs distinct Common Chiffchaff	1
canariensis Islands Chiffchaff specie Islands ''P	1
collybita morphology vocalisation course sympatric chiffchaffs	1
c. canariensis El Hierro Palma Gomera Tenerife Gran Canaria Common Chiffchaff ha shorter rounder	1
ha buff breast flank ha deep song call nominate race	1
c. exsul Lanzarote Fuerteventura paler le relative harsher call distinct specie extinct	1
reason extinction scarce Haria Lanzarote	1
sindianus Mountain Chiffchaff found Caucasus ''P	1
s. lorenzii Himalayas ''P	1
s. sindianus migrant level winter	1
c. tristis finer darker bill browner upperparts buff flank song ''P	1
s. lorenzii warmer darker brown nominate race sympatric Common Chiffchaff area Caucasus occurs	1
Mountain Chiffchaff differs ''tristis vocalisation Martens Jochen Ringförmige Arealüberschneidung und Artbildung beim Zilpzalp ''Phylloscopus collybita	1
''Zeitschrift für Zoologische Systematik und Evolutionsforschung	1
Martens Jochen Hänel Sabine Gesangformen und Verwandtschaft der asiatischen Zilpzalpe ''Phylloscopus collybita abietinus und ''Ph	1
subspecies distinct show difference mtDNA sequence subspecies rank research	1