law code survive date Æthelberht Kent reign Documents p.	7
code wa name Eadric Kent	7
king issue law Kent Ine.Whitelock Documents pp	7
date ’ s Ine ’ s law reason ’ s law Whitelock Documents p. Ine ’ s law	7
Ine peaceful term compensation death Mul indication ruler degree law	7
addition coincidence timing clause form codes.The law chapter Ine code chapter	7
Ine version read man distance foreigner wood track doe shout blow horn thief	7
version man distance foreigner track shout blow horn thief	7
sign collaboration ’ s law use ''gesith Saxon term place term ''eorlcund	7
Ine law code act prestige authority period disruption kingdom	7
Ine ’ s law survive Great code laws.Whitelock Documents pp	7
manuscript copy Corpus Christi College Cambridge MS contains ’ s Ine ’ s law code extant text Chronicle	7
wa copy Ine law part MS Cotton Otho B xi manuscript wa destroyed fire Chapters Ine law destruction	7
fragment Ine ’ s law found Museum MS Burney	7
Ine ’ s law seventh-century form	7
mention prologue law law disliked	7
specify law longer relevant time version Ine law	7
prologue Ine law list advisor	7
people bishop Eorcenwald Hædde Ine ’ s father	7
Ine wa king intent encourage Christianity law	7
oath communicant example carry weight baptism observance	7
Significant attention paid issues—more laws.Kirby Kings p.	7
law state land ceorls name Saxon freeman	7
ceorl fails fence share allows cattle stray someone field held damage	7
doe mean land wa held ceorl strip land	7
king law minor issue law mention role lord compliance ceorls.Stenton pp	7
law tenant held land tenure lord king involvement indicates relationship lord tenant wa king control.Stenton pp	7
law deal cattle provide documentary evidence open-field system	7
show open-field agriculture wa Wessex Ine time wa prevalent method midland north east Lindsey Deira	7
Wessex system wa example	7
law mention yard land mention unit	7
yard wa unit land quarter hide hide wa place place	7
yard sense standard medieval villein wa virgate	7
historian ha manorial economy Ine law	7
fine fyrd obligation service king set nobleman half ceorl ceorls serve army	7
Scholars disagreed value ceorl surprising men fight defeat meant slavery.Stenton p.	7
law anyone murder high-ranking person oath-helpers	7
oath-helper swear oath behalf man suspicion crime	7
Ine requirement implies trust oath sworn peasant	7
represent change time man kin support oaths.Stenton pp	7
law provision Ine subject	7
evidence provide incomplete integration population research placename history history house archaeology indicates part Wessex wa newcomer time law	7
Saxon king Saxon kingdom term law define Ine subject ''Englisc	7
existence date identity people Bede ''Bretwaldas origin ''Gens Anglorum ''The Times Bede study society historian Oxford pp	7