campaign force Tulagi Islands Solomon Islands time colonial possession	9
meant deny island use base supply route secure point campaign neutralize base Rabaul support Guinea campaign	9
Tulagi airfield ''Pearl Harbor p.	9
nightfall troop Tulagi island airfield construction Lunga Point Field	9
aircraft operating Cactus Force CAF code name	9
protect airfield US Marines perimeter defense Lunga Point	9
reinforcement month number US troop Lunga Point men.Morison ''Struggle p. p. p. p.	9
response Headquarters Army 17th Army command Rabaul command Hyakutake task	9
Units 17th Army drive force island	9
Griffith ''Battle p. Dull p. pp	9
threat CAF aircraft Field use transport ship deliver troop supply island	9
warship Rabaul Shortland Islands	9
warship light cruiser destroyer Eighth Fleet command Mikawa round trip Slot night exposure CAF air attack	9
troop manner soldier equipment supply artillery vehicle food ammunition	9
speed warship campaign Express force Rat Transportation	9
attempt recapture Field force wa Tenaru	9
attempt place defeat men command Edson Ridge.Frank p.	9
recapture Field army men Infantry Division	9
addition troop equipment Express convoy transport ship	9
approach transport convoy wa nighttime bombardment Field battleship airfield runway destroyed half CAF aircraft aviation fuel	9
spite damage personnel restore runway service replacement aircraft fuel CAF pre-bombardment level weeks.Frank p. Morison ''Struggle p. ''Pearl Harbor p.	9
attempt retake island troop wa loss Field.Frank	9
time Isoroku Yamamoto commander Fleet naval force Cruz Islands area	9
carrier retreat loss carrier aircraft aircrews.Hara Destroyer Captain	9
Yamamoto ship base Truk Micronesia headquarters Rabaul carrier repair refitting.Hammel Decision p.	9
army attack reinforcement operation proceed	9
army assistance Yamamoto deliver reinforcement island support force Field	9
support reinforcement effort Yamamoto transport ship carry army troop Infantry Division ammunition food equipment Rabaul	9
sent warship support force Truk battleship	9
battleship ''Hiei ''Kirishima fragmentation shell bombard Field night destroy aircraft order transport reach unload day	9
Morison ''Struggle p. Hammel Decision p.	9
transport ship carry troop equipment provision ''Arizona Maru ''Kumagawa Maru ''Sado Maru ''Nagara Maru ''Nako Maru ''Canberra Maru ''Brisbane Maru ''Kinugawa Maru ''Hirokawa Maru ''Yamaura Maru ''Yamatsuki Maru	9
warship force wa ''Hiei Hiroaki Abe	9
threat aircraft warship wa force resupply force attack land sea force area.Hammel Decision p.	9
intelligence try retake Field.Hammel Decision p.	9
sent Task Force reinforcement resupply convoy split group Richmond Turner	9
supply ship task group Admirals Callaghan Norman Scott aircraft Field ''Naval Night Battles p. Hammel Decision p. Morison ''Struggle p. p.	9
reinforcement men Marine Aviation Engineer Battalion replacement ground air unit Marine Replacement Battalion battalion US Army Infantry Regiment ammunition supply	9
transport group TF wa Captain Ingolf N. ''McCawley ''Crescent ''President Adams ''President Jackson	9
transport group part TF ''Betelgeuse ''Libra ''Zeilin	9
transport ship time aircraft Buin Solomons damage	9
Twelve aircraft shot anti-aircraft fire ship fighter aircraft Field	9
p. Hammel Decision p. Morison ''Struggle p.	9