Black female tender year force nature time caught tripartite crossfire male prejudice hate Black lack power	4
Maya Angelou ''I Bird Sings Angelou p. course Bird Maya ha described symbolic character girl victim racism inferiority self-aware responds racism dignity sense identity	4
Feminist scholar Maria state formation female identity book Maya role model Black woman .Lauret literature scholar McPherson state Angelou demonstration passage childhood adulthood myth present theme death regeneration rebirth	4
Scholar Liliane call presentation Angelou identity theme motif Angelou	4
Maya life Bird suggests sense self process reborn ramification .Arensberg p. indicates Angelou female writer 1960s 1970s autobiography reimagine way woman life identity society	4
connection Angelou autobiography call fiction subjectivity feminist first-person first-person ''The Women Room Marilyn ''The Notebook Doris period	4
genre employ narrator protagonist illusion presence mode signification .Lauret girl Maya pain awareness displacement	4
forgotten child term reality McPherson p. life hostile world defines beauty term whiteness reject girl	4
Maya internalizes rejection ha – belief ugliness wa absolute .McPherson p. McPherson belief concept family kinship concern Angelou book understood light child displacement Bird .McPherson p. sent parent wa rejection quest love acceptance self-worth Maya Bailey.Smith p. agrees scholar Angelou role incarnation identity book illustrate oppression history	4
example Bird Angelou demonstrates racist habit Americans employer insists	4
Angelou describes employer hellish horror name .Angelou p. Scholar Debra Walker call racist insult assault Maya race self-image.King p. scholar Sidonie Ann emphasizes Maya inadequacy denigrates identity individuality uniqueness	4
Maya understands rebel Cullinan favorite dish.Smith p. incident book solidifies Maya identity trip father ha drive car time	4
experience Stamps Maya control fate .Smith p. experience Maya growth incident period homelessness father girlfriend	4
incident Maya knowledge self-determination confirm self-worth	4
Bird motherhood theme Angelou autobiography	4
Scholar Burgher belief female autobiographer Angelou debunked stereotype mother breeder matriarch role .Burgher p. belief Angelou plot construction character development mother/child motif found work Renaissance poet Jessie Fauset.Lupton year life Maya think herself orphan comfort thought mother wa	4
Maya relationship mother blame abandonment express ambivalence violent aggression .Arensberg p. example Maya brother destroy Christmas gift sent mother	4
end book Maya becomes mother herself mother becomes presence Maya ha longed.Arensberg p.	4