Anderson Sherman principal responsibility border state Confederate troop held Columbus Bowling present Cumberland Gap.For discussion period Marszalek ''Sherman pp	9
Hirshson ''White Tecumseh pp	9
outlook command D.C. shortage estimate strength rebel force	9
press report visit Simon Sherman relieved.Sherman McClellan W. Sears ed. ''The Civil Papers McClellan Correspondence p. note Marszalek ''Sherman pp	9
wa Don Carlos Missouri	9
wa put Maj. Gen. Henry W. Halleck commander Missouri unfit duty	9
Sherman Lancaster Ohio recuperate	9
Missouri Sherman wa midst today described breakdown	9
wa home wife Ellen brother Senator Sherman advice melancholy insanity family subject	9
Sherman concern command “ broke suicide .Sherman Sherman Simpson ''Sherman ’ s Civil	9
problem ''Cincinnati described insane .See ''Cincinnati Marszalek ''Sherman pp	9
mid-December Sherman wa return service Halleck Missouri Halleck command wa unify command	9
Sherman assignment rear-echelon command barrack command Cairo.At point Halleck General-in-Chief McClellan Sherman command expedition Cumberland River Fort Donelson wa Edwin Stanton Lincoln expedition prove charge Sherman	9
Operating Paducah support operation Brig	9
Gen. Ulysses Grant capture Fort Donelson	9
Grant commander Cairo won victory Fort Henry command Tennessee	9
Sherman wa officer time Grant feel facility concentration mean River R Road faith — Command way	9
WTS USG Papers Ulysses Grant pp	9
Grant Fort Donelson Sherman wish Grant wa Army Tennessee commander 5th Division.Eicher p. test Grant wa Shiloh	9
Confederate attack morning commander surprise	9
Sherman intelligence report militia officer Confederate Sidney Johnston base Corinth	9
precaution picket line entrench build abatis push reconnaissance patrol	9
Shiloh avoid order escape kind criticism	9
wife precaution call crazy .Daniel p. caught attack Sherman division retreat avert rout	9
Grant end day oak tree darkness smoking cigar word wise instinct mention retreat	9
become conversation war Sherman Grant devil day	9
puff cigar Grant calmly	9
Shiloh Sherman wa mdash hand shoulder mdash horse shot	9
performance wa Grant Halleck battle wa volunteer	9
force Corinth Halleck command Grant role found unsatisfactory second-in-command Halleck Sherman division extreme right right	9
force Corinth Sherman Grant command difficulty wa commander Halleck	9
Sherman Grant example life battle Shiloh wa cast newspaper assertion 'crazy battle life feather	9
told Grant army accident restore favor place	9
Grant situation Halleck left East become general-in-chief Sherman governor Memphis.Marszalek ''Sherman pp	9