designer lash-up BT19 Formula career hand	8
BT19 wa non-championship Formula race world championship season	8
non-championship Prix East BT19 wa car present	8
time session race ndash pole position start race ndash majority event fuel injection pump	8
problem car lap Syracuse Prix Trophy Silverstone circuit set pole position lap record race win champion Surtees work Ferrari.Henry pp	8
ndash world championship season Monaco Prix	8
wa cold BT19 gearbox failed.Henry p. Surtees race Ferrari differential lap race wa won Jackie BRM P261	8
Prix Spa circuit mile hour km/h slide rain lap	8
shower half field miss race injury	8
BT19 tyre condition Henry p. Unique p.	8
Sources differ problem wa	8
Henry state wa reluctance wet weather tyre work temperature track surface report Unique wa tire dry-weather compound	8
Surtees won race Ferrari quit team	8
Prix held speed circuit race leader Lorenzo start race slipstream Ferrari tow faster straight BT19 manage	8
consolidate lead Ferrari driver Formula novice Mike Parkes	8
lap car wa delayed broken throttle cable lap finish win Parkes become man win Formula World Championship race cars.Unique pp	8
ndash BT20 car Reims BT19 win championship race	8
Ferrari championship race point present Prix	8
race wa held tight Brands Hatch circuit track slippery oil car drizzle	8
set pole race.Brabham Nye pp	8
ndash championship round Dutch Prix speed Zandvoort circuit Brands	8
Nye p. won race Clark le litre Lotus lead mid-race wa delayed problems.Henry p. Prix wa held Nordschleife described Brands Hatch steroid	8
opening lap lead Surtees	8
won fight Englishman rain.Brabham Nye pp	8
ndash win finish championship rival point lead driver championship caught championship Surtees won point race	8
Hill Jochen Rindt point score driver result Hill Rindt drop point race	8
BT19 Prix Monza speed circuit	8
BT20 wa track practice race race ''Old Nail felt wa engine	8
Reims race leader oil leakage car lap	8
Surtees race clinched world championship.Brabham Nye pp	8
ndash BT19 season pole position victory non-championship Oulton Park Gold Cup BT20 race championship season	8
BT19 wa championship race Formula season Repco engine Monaco Prix pole position Dutch Prix.Henry p. reason competitiveness Brabham-Repcos Formula motorsport historian Doug Nye ha score weight Ferrari BRM Eagle-Weslake Honda form sheer 'grunt interim stop-gap car Climax BRM Lotus BRMs	8
Nye p. BT19 race Tasman Series wa pre-1961 Formula regulation engine capacity limit litre	8
Tasman wa purpose Repco engine involvement wa promote version	8
Hallam head Repco-Brabham organisation building Repco engine ha version put power litre litre engine Pinder p. wa unit	8
engine BT19 retirement place series	8